<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-6888" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: DAIRY
        Method:

        1. Assemble all ingredients.

        2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

        3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes.

        4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

        5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

        6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size required
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients and tools
        2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

        2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

        3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

        4. Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and
        the rest with romano oil. Shake it.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

        2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

        3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26105" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic and lemongrass puree and saute until
        fragrant, about 2-3 minutes. Add green curry paste and saute until frgrant, about 1 minute more.

        2. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer. Allow to simmer for 15 minutes, then add fish
        sauce. Thicken with corn starch if necessary.

        3. Remove from heat and strain through fine chinois.

        4. Cool. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergens:

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find
        it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

        2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the
        water to a FULL boil.

        3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not
        stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
        APPROX 7 MINUTES

        4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure
        to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir

        5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26231" image="">1) Chop thyme and rosemary finely. Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon
        juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Dairy
        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Preheat oven to 375*F. Pull out garlic butter to soften, or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic
        wrap until it is spreadable.

        2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

        3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter. Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet
        for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

        4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

        2) Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes. Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and
        store in appropriate vessel.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1) Prepare and Ice bath

        2) Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes. Immidiately put into ice
        bath. Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

        3) Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans. Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p
        mix. Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1) Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F. Cook until bacon
        is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

        57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1) Blend the hell out of it.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34892" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Scale out ingredients.

        2. In a sauce pot combine water and buuter and bring to a simmer, Add powder and stir for a minute.

        3. Place in container and hold for service in a WARM place.

        Portioning:NA

        Utensils needed:scale pot whisk bowl container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1) Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray. Place egg in egg poacher cup. Steam for 8
        minutes until cooked.

        Allergens:

        Soy, Egg
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41321" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: EGG

        Method:

        1. Prepare all Mise En Place items that are dry, and combine. Sift together if you have time.

        2. Add Egg, and 50% of the water, and mix with a whisk.

        3. Then, add the vinegar, and continue mixing. A chemical reaction will occur at this point between the vinegar
        and baking soda.

        4.If necessary, add the remaining water. Otherwise, do not, and let the mixture be by itself. It should be
        roughly the consistency of soft serve ice cream.

        NOTE: This batter should be stored in the freezable containers in the Vegetable Containers, meant for squeeze
        bottles and other things that stand at room temperature.

        [This is where I would normally write &quot;Label/Date/Store!&quot;, but since this is made several times per
        day, and never stored overnight - the container NOTE was written instead.]

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

        2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41913" image="">1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

        2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

        3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

        4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

        5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The
        oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42365" image="">
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE
        WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Method:
        1. Mix all ingredients with a whisk to fully incorperate
        2. Season with Pickle juice to taste
        3. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        *NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT
        ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET
        CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

        2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

        3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10
        minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

        4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them
        on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their
        blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form
        balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44527" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Clean, prepare and chop the herbs as needed.

        Use any combination (or even just a single herb) in a quanitity adding up to 8 grams total weight.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44528" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        This recipe is for costing and portioning purposes only.

        Make associated sub recipes as indicated in those particular recipes

        The portion of sauce is 200ml or 6 fl. oz
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Assemble all the ingredients.

        2. Saute the onions and pureed lemon grass until translucent, add ginger and garlic and cook out for another 5
        minutes. Add sugar and cook for another 5 minutes.

        3. Add Green Curry Paste and cook out for another 5 minutes to develop flavour.

        4. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer, add lime leaves and season.

        5. Thicken with slury, thicken so that sauce coats the back of a spoon and sticks.

        6. Add lime juice just before you take it off the heat.

        7. Throw in the thai basil and cilantro and blend in the sauce to give it it&apos;s green color.******

        ****** If you are making the sauce for the next day, DO NOT add the cilantro/thai basil as it will go brown and
        discolor.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Products related to this Prep recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1.gather igredients
        2.chop leaves
        3.wash and dry
        4.label and fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45193" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:

        Method:

        1) Make green curry sauce as per recipe.

        2) In large rondeau or tilt skillet over medium high heat, add oil. When oil is hot, add onion, green pepper and
        celery and saute for 4-5 minutes or until beginning to soften.

        3) Add tofu, zucchini and green curry sauce and bring to a simmer.

        4) Adjust seasoning with fish sauce.

        6) Hold hot for service, OR

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergens:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46824" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        This recipe is for costing purposes only.

        Please make all of the associated sub recipes as indicated in those recipes.

        Any blend of the listed vegetables will suffice, or just one vegetable.

        The important part is that 180g/ 6oz (by weight) of vegetables are provided.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Method:

        1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
        2. Save tops for soup/sauce
        3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
        4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-48321" image="">Allergen:

        egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        Cook Eggs, Hollandaise,

        Place English muffins on plate, top with bacon, sliced tomato, add an egg and top with hollandaise.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-48357" image="">Allergen:

        egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten, fish (salmon)

        Icon:

        oceanwise

        Method:

        Cook Eggs, Hollandaise,

        Place English muffins on plate, top with smoked salmon, add an egg and top with hollandaise.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-48359" image="">Allergen:

        egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten

        Icon:

        vegetarian

        Method:

        Cook Eggs, Hollandaise,

        Place English muffins on plate, top with sauteed spinach feta, add an egg and top with hollandaise.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn
        heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

        Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

        ***Note***

        This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a
        *free* by-product.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

        Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done.

        Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-49262" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50509" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

        1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft.

        2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

        3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes.

        4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with
        the heat off.

        5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

        2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme
        is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems

        2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this
        until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to
        prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

        2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano
        until desired texture achived (course or fine)

        3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

        4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

        combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

        remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

        cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

        shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

        remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess
        oil.

        use is associated recipes
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53056" image="">average roma tomato weighs approx 90g

        this recipe makes 26 x 1/2 tomatoes

        1 portion = 2 tomato 1/2&apos;s or 1 whole tomato
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut okra into slices.

        2. Mix water and eggs.

        3. Cover okra in flour.

        4. Dip okra in egg wash.

        5. Coat with cornmeal.

        6. Deep fry until crispy.

        7. Season as soon as it comes out of fryer.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53993" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Toss diced Zucchini with oil and salt and pepper and roast on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned and hot
        throughout.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until
        lightly browned and hot throughout.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53995" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Toss mushrooms with salt and pepper and oil.

        Roast on a parchment lined sheet pan in a hot oven until the water from the mushrooms cooks away and the
        mushrooms are browned and flavorful
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53996" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Toss the onion with oil and salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned
        around the edges and hot throughout

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54455" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:
        1. Dry prawns as best you can, and lightly coat in rice flour.

        2. Dip cleaned prawns into batter.

        3. Deep fry until cooked through and golden brown.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-54456" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Toast cut side of bun.

        2. Sauce the bun with tartar sauce and layer the sandwich with fried prawns, shredded iceberg, tomato slices and
        pickle slices.

        Portioning:
        90 g prawn

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55167" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-56699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut cauliflower into 1&quot; flourettes.

        2. Toss in batter until completly coated.

        3. Toss in 3/4 of panko. Take remaining 1/4 of the panko and bltz in robocoup until fine ( about 5 min).

        4. Toss the wings in the fine blitzed panko and spread out on a sheet pan lined with parchment.

        5. Bake in 350f oven for 20 min, remove from heat, stir, bake for an additional 15 min or until just golden.

        6. Hold hot for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56700" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine flour, spices and wisk together.

        2. Add soy milk and stock, wisk together to create batter.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Gather inredents.

        2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

        3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57182" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Fry ocra in small batches to ensure freshness


        Portioning:
        120 grams

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. In a large pot bring the water to a boil. Add the rice, lentils, bayleaf and 1/2 the salt. Bring back to a
        boil, turn heat down to medium and lid, leaving lid slightly ajar.
        Simmer for 30-35 minutes or until the rice and lentils are tender. Drain, reserving at least 1 1/4 C (281g) of
        cooking liquid (it will be used later to make the sauce). Place the rice and lentils back in their cooking pot,
        lid and set aside off heat.

        2. *A note about the veggies. Be sure they&apos;re diced small, otherwise they&apos;ll be crunchy-ish at the end
        of cooking. We&apos;re looking for them to be soft.

        3. In a large Rondeau add the oil and heat until shimmering. Add the bell pepper, onion and celery. Turn the
        heat to low. Stir. Cook, stirring occassionally for about 12-15 minutes. The veggies are done when the they&apos;re
        tender/soft and brown bits (fond – the brown bits that stick to the bottom of the pan) are just starting to
        appear in the pan.

        4. To the pan of veggies, add the tomato paste, garlic, Cajun or Creole seasoning and remaining 1/2 salt. Stir
        to coa the veggies. Pour in 3/4 C (180g) of the reserved cooking liquid from the lentils and rice. Stir.

        5. To the pan, add the drained kidney beans. Stir. Heat should be on medium-low to low. Lid the pan and gently
        cook the beans through for about 8-10 minutes. Check on the beans a few times while cooking and If needed, add
        just a bit more cooking liquid from the reserved liquid. Your beans should be saucy, and moist, not dry.

        6. Turn the heat to low and transfer the drained rice and lentils to the bean mixture. Add Worcestershire sauce.
        Add the lemon juice and to taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary; then gently fold all the ingredients
        together.
        If needed, to loosen the mixture or if it starts to get too dry, add a splash of cooking liquid - you&apos;ll
        probably not use it all - thats okay. Taste for salt. Lid. Leave on low heat for 3-5 minutes just to warm
        though, checking to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking - the pan should be almost dry, with a moist (but not
        sticky) rice mixture.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57279" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. In a large pot bring the water to a boil. Add the rice, lentils, bayleaf and 1/2 the salt. Bring back to a
        boil, turn heat down to medium and lid, leaving lid slightly ajar.
        Simmer for 30-35 minutes or until the rice and lentils are tender. Drain, reserving at least 1 1/4 C (281g) of
        cooking liquid (it will be used later to make the sauce). Place the rice and lentils back in their cooking pot,
        lid and set aside off heat.

        2. *A note about the veggies. Be sure they&apos;re diced small, otherwise they&apos;ll be crunchy-ish at the end
        of cooking. We&apos;re looking for them to be soft.

        3. In a large Rondeau add the oil and heat until shimmering. Add the bell pepper, onion and celery. Turn the
        heat to low. Stir. Cook, stirring occassionally for about 12-15 minutes. The veggies are done when the they&apos;re
        tender/soft and brown bits (fond – the brown bits that stick to the bottom of the pan) are just starting to
        appear in the pan.

        4. To the pan of veggies, add the tomato paste, garlic, Cajun or Creole seasoning and remaining 1/2 salt. Stir
        to coa the veggies. Pour in 3/4 C (180g) of the reserved cooking liquid from the lentils and rice. Stir.

        5. To the pan, add the drained kidney beans. Stir. Heat should be on medium-low to low. Lid the pan and gently
        cook the beans through for about 8-10 minutes. Check on the beans a few times while cooking and If needed, add
        just a bit more cooking liquid from the reserved liquid. Your beans should be saucy, and moist, not dry.

        6. Turn the heat to low and transfer the drained rice and lentils to the bean mixture. Add Worcestershire sauce.
        Add the lemon juice and to taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary; then gently fold all the ingredients
        together.
        If needed, to loosen the mixture or if it starts to get too dry, add a splash of cooking liquid - you&apos;ll
        probably not use it all - thats okay. Taste for salt. Lid. Leave on low heat for 3-5 minutes just to warm
        though, checking to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking - the pan should be almost dry, with a moist (but not
        sticky) rice mixture.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

        2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hot hold for service.

        3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thaii basil.


        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57350" image="">1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

        2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hold for service.

        3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thai basil.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57351" image="">1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

        2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hold for service.

        3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thai basil.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58405" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, lemongrass and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

        2. Add rice, sautee 1 minute

        3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is
        reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

        4. Sfter 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. Small dice the tofu and fry until very
        crisy - incoporate into the congee for texture.

        5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-60385" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

        2. Add rice, sautee 1 minute

        3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is
        reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

        4. After 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. Add the shrimp and chopped kimchii at
        the end.

        5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-60387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, lemongrass and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

        2. Add mushrooms and rice, sautee 1 minute

        3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is
        reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

        4. Sfter 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed.

        5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-62016" image="">completely thaw block of frozen spinach

        in small batches, squeeze out excess water from spinach

        place squeezed spinach in perforated pan or basket strainer to allow any excess water to drip away

        place in appropriate container

        label, date, refrigerate
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
