<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

        2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

        3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

        4. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9738" image="">
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9863" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Tip/tail the leeks save the green tips for other preps
        2. Soak in cold water to rinse off dirt
        3. cut to desired shape
        4. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

        2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

        PREP RECIPE

        1. Over medium heat, heat oil

        2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

        3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions
        begin to soften

        4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and
        distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

        5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in
        bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
        2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

        Allergens:

        No known priority allergens
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink.
        Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs
        clear

        2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice
        and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

        3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1) In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high
        heat. Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot. Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not
        overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown. Taste for seasoning.

        2) Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

        2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer. On lowest setting using a
        paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes. Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of
        potatoes.

        3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then
        pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

        4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.

        5. Taste for seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

        2) Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes. Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and
        store in appropriate vessel.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26318" image="">1) Preheat oven to 350*F

        2) Cut puff pastry with largest size of ring mold so it will fit on the top of serving bowl.

        3) Brush circles with garlic butter, and season with herbs de provence and salt and pepper.

        4) Par bake puff pastry in oven until about 80% cooked. Reserve for service.

        5) Just before serving, finish puff pastry in oven. Brush with garlic butter and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-26809" image="">Allergens:
        gluten, wheat, egg, soy, sulphites, mustard

        Icons:
        N/A

        Method:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-28363" image="">serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-29007" image="">1) Combine all well. Store in appropriate container.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32656" image="">1) Bring water up to a boil. Add concentrate. Stir throughly to combine. Use
        immidiately or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32747" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. ***This is a neutral base for any number of quiche flavourings.

        2. Whisk together the eggs, milk, cream, and salt until frothy

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1) Prepare and Ice bath

        2) Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes. Immidiately put into ice
        bath. Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

        3) Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans. Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p
        mix. Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1) Blend the hell out of it.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-43729" image="">1) Combine lemon juice, orange juice, soy sauce, brown sugar, ginger and garlic puree&apos;s.
        Mix very well. Add chicken thighs and marinate for 4-6 hours.

        2) Preheat oven to 400*F. Add chicken thighs skin side up to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way
        up chicken thighs. Do not cover skin. Roast chicken thighs until biggest thigh registers 150*F on an instant
        read thermometer.

        3) Remove thighs and add to hot holding vessels. Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining
        marinade and pour over chicken.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43730" image="">1) Combine all well and reserve for salad.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43731" image="">1) Combine brown sugar, S+P mix, soy, lime, and oil. Mix well. Add pineapple and allow
        to marinate for 30 minutes.

        2) Preheat oven to 400*F, add pineapple to parchment lined tray and roast until charred and tender, approx. 15
        minutes.

        3) Reserve for salad. Can be made the day before.

        Allergens:

        Soy
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43732" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Remove kale from stems and cut into bite sized chunks.
        2. Combine with remaining ingredients and hold cold for service.


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingedients
        2.pick leaves
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1) Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along
        the stem to remove leaves.

        2) Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-45150" image="">Average raw weight of a bone in chicken thigh is 170g</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-45151" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-45153" image="">
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Start with rice

        2. Sides

        3. Chicken

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50386" image="">1) Combine all ingredients. Store in appropriate container, lable date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50389" image="">1) Cut tofu into 150g slices.

        2) Place tofu in container with Shoyu Marinade, let sit for 2-3 hours.

        3) Preheat oven to 425*F. Add marinaded tofu to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up the tofu
        slices. Roast tofu for 20 minutes, or until tofu temprature reads 65c on thermometer.

        3) Remove tofu and add to hot holding vessels. Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining
        marinade and pour over tofu.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

        2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme
        is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-51196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:


        1. Preheat oven to 350 degrees.

        2. Dock the bottom of the pastry (to allow air to escape so it doesn&apos;t bubble) Bake the crust for about
        5-10 minutes.

        3. Remove from the oven and allow to cool. The crust will be golden. but not not too dark. (as it will bake
        again with custard/filling

        4. Prepare the egg custard mixture by adding the eggs to a large measuring cup. Add the heavy cream, then add
        the milk, salt and pepper.

        5. Blend with a hand mixer to ensure the egg and cream mixture is completely homogenous (mixed thouroughly)

        6. Spread the desired fillings on the bottom of the pie crust. Pour the egg mixture on top (leave a 1/2 cm of
        head space at the top of the quiche as the eggs will souffle and expand) Bake at 350 degrees for about 20-25
        minutes (check after 15 mins) The quiche will be slightly wobbly in just the center.(this allows for carry over
        cooking and will set up within a few minutes of exiting the oven)

        7. Allow to cool for about 20 minutes to room temperature. Quiche can be served warm, cold, or room temperature.


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54743" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        Peel and dice the russet potatoes. Use in recipes.

        Store in a pail of water to prevent oxidation/browning.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56560" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Steam edamame &amp; peas until tender (5 minutes).

        2. Place edamame, peas, cilantro, garlic, jalapeno, lime juice &amp; fish sauce in blender.

        3. Puree, adding water as needed to achieve a smooth consistency.

        4. Season to taste with fish sauce..

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56970" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. In Rondo or tilt skillet add butter and dry thyme.

        2. Add flour and stir to combine.

        3. Slowly add warm stock while whisking to avoid lumps. Bring to a simmer.

        4. Stir the bottom to avoid sticking and cook 20-25 mins at a LOW simmer to thicken.

        5. While cooking veloute in a new rondo or tilt skillet add butter, onion, leek, carrot, celery, celeriac &amp;
        garlic and sweat stirring occasionally until fragrant.

        6. When slightly soft add vegetables to veloute plus add peas, parsley and chives and season to taste.

        7. Hot hold for service or...

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57153" image="">1. Sauce goes on side so cutlet doesn&apos;t get soggy.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57154" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Whisk all ingredients together ensuring sugar is dissolved. Warm ever so slightly if needed to melt sugar.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57157" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        Preheat deep fryer to 350F

        1. Slice sweet potato width wise into 1/2 - 1 cm thick slices.

        2. Toss evenly in flour, then liquid egg then panko and reserve on full sized sheet pans.

        3. Working in batches deep fry slices 1-2 minutes until sweet potatoes are golden brown and just cooked through.

        4. Remove from fryer, shake off excess oil, place on wire rack and season immediately so the salt will stick to
        the sweet potatoes.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57582" image="">1. Place rice on one part of the plate and place deep fried pork cutlet on top.

        2. Put edamame on another portion of the plate.

        3. Place sauce on plate and garnish pork with green onion.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57583" image="">1. Place rice on one part of the plate and place deep fried pork cutlet on top.

        2. Put edamame on another portion of the plate.

        3. Place sauce on plate and garnish pork with green onion.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57587" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-61769" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in: Pot Pies

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        1. Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F.

        2. Place the chicken on a baking sheet and rub them with olive oil, salt and pepper. Roast for 20 to 25 minutes,
        or until cooked through. Set aside until cool enough to handle, Dice the chicken into 1/2 inch cubes.

        3. In a small saucepan, heat the chicken stock. In a large pot melt the butter and add the flour and cook over
        low heat, stirring constantly, for 2 minutes. Add the hot chicken stock to the sauce. Simmer over low heat for 1
        more minute, stirring, until thick.

        4. Add salt,pepper, and heavy cream. Add the cubed chicken, carrots, peas, mushrooms, onions and parsley. Mix
        well. cook untill veg is slightly tender. Put into hotel pans and serve immediately or store in appropriate
        cambro cool with ice wand/ice bath.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
