<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-11375" image="">

saute onions in oil until translucent
add ginger, garlic, lemongrass and cook until tender
add curry paste cook for 2 - 3 min until paste is spread throughout the ingredients
add lime leaf, lime juice, coconut milk &amp; soy - bring to a boil
simmer for 5 min,add basil &amp; cilantro
thicken with corn starch slurry, simmer for 2-3 min
adjust seasoning with salt, pepper &amp; sugar
remove from heat and hold for service

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26100" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PREP/PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

1. Put beef bones in large roasting pans, and roast till dark brown colour, in 500f oven.

2. Char whole onions and ginger in 500f oven, Char until skins turn black all over.

3. Meanwile, toast cinnamon sticks, cloves, fennel and star anise in saute pan and toast on stove top over medium flame until aromatic about 5 - 10 minutes DO NOT BURN. Recomend doing cinnamon sticks first, then the rest, for more consistant roast.

4. Add browned beef bones, charred onion, ginger and toasted spices to stock pot and cover with cold water, just until bones are crested

5. Bring to rapid simmer, then turn down heat to a slow simmer. Simmer for 8 - 10  hours, or overnight

6. Strain stock/broth through fine chinoise. Cool rapidly in blast chiller. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date, refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26308" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 375*F

2)  Place bones on roasting pan or baking sheet and place in oven to roast until golden brown, about 2 hours.  Ensure to move bones around and rotate pan to ensure bones are evenly browned.

3) Once roasted, place bones in large stock pot or steam kettle.  Cover bones with water until just a small amount of bones are sticking out of water.  Bring to a simmer.

4)  Once a simmer is achieved, skim any impurities that rise to the top.  Continue skimming and simmering for at least four hours.  

5)  Add rough chopped onion, celery, and carrot and bay leaf to stock.  Allow to simmer for another 4-8 hours (or overnight).

6)  Remove stock from heat.  Remove bones with tongs and reserve.  Using a pitcher and fine chinous, strain stock into appropriate vessel.  Bones can be covered again with water to make remoulage.   </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat up oil in large sauce pot over medium low heat.  

2. Add garlic and and gently cook for 10 minutes.  That&apos;s right, 10 minutes.  Then add ginger puree and continue gently cooking for another 5-10 minutes. Stir it alot to make sure it doesn&apos;t burn, but really cook it out. 

3. Add kecap manis and rice vinegar.  Bring to a simmer for 10-15 minutes over medium heat.  Add corn starch slurry and simmer for another 5 minutes until thick.

4. Do not strain.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28260" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Pho.jpg">1) Make sure to make preportional seasoned Pho soup recipe from broth for service.

1)  Blanch cooked rice noodles in very salty water and place in serving bowl.

2)  Place shaved beef, on noodles and then pour very hot pho broth on top.  The beef should start cooking almost immidiately.

3)  Garnish with bean sprouts, carrot, shimeji mushroom, thai basil and lime wedge.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-29391" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Kung Pao.jpg">1. Add oil to wok over medium heat.  Add thai chilis and allow to infuse the oil for about 30 seconds.  Add chicken and stir fry to 70% cooked.

2.  Crank the wok full blast and add vegetables and continue stir frying until chicken is fully cooked and vegetables are tender, about 4 minutes.  Add hunan sauce and hold warm.

3.  In the same wok, add chow mein noodles and stir fry with a small amount of sauce until hot throughout.  Hold warm.

4. When ready to serve customer, add 6 oz. chow mein noodles, and an 8 fl. oz scoop of chicken and vegetable mixture. 

5. Garnish with roasted cashews and green onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32657" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Marinate chicken in sauce in large container 1-2 hours. 3.5L per box of chicken.

2) Place marniated chicken thighs in large 2&quot; hotel pan uncovered with a 1&apos; deep pour of the marinade. Cook at 400 for roughly 20 minutes. Be sure to stir occasionally without breaking the chicken apart..

3) Once chicken is cooked, remove chicken from rondeau in to half hotel pans. Boil remaining sauce on high, until thick and syrupy, pour over chicken.

4) Hold hot for service OR

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32658" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat up oil in wok.  When hot add vegetables and garlic and stir fry for 2 minutes on high heat.  Add to Adobo sauce.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32750" image="">1)  Place appropriate amount of rice in bottom of serving bowl.  Add vegetable medley and roasted potatoes, and top with chicken adobo.  

2)  Garnish with 2 fl. oz. of reduced adobo sauce and green onion.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33530" image="">1)  Combine all very well by hand.  Store in food safe container in dry storage area.  Label and Date.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-33532" image="">RICE USES WHITE HANDLE PORTION SCOOP
CHICKEN USES 6 OZ. LADLE

1)  Toss chicken in dredge.  Be careful to not do too much at one time or else they will all stick together.  

2)  Fry in 350*F fryer for 4 - 4.5 minutes or until throughly cooked through.

3)  Toss throughly with sweet chili sauce.  

4) Garnish with 30 ML opf hot sweet chili sauce, crispy wonton, green onion, cilantro and sesame seeds.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35818" image="">1)  ENSURE TO PUT IN STOPPER FOR STEAM KETTLE!!  

2)  DOUBLE CHECK THAT YOU PUT STOPPER INTO STEAM KETTLE!!

3) Remove as much fat from the chicken carcasses as possible.

4)  Add chicken bones and water to large steam kettle.  Bring to a boil and lower to a simmer. SKIM WELL. The more scum and fat you skim off the better and cleaner the flavour of the stock will be. 

5) Add remaining ingredients and leave 5-6 hours at a very gentle simmer.

6)  Strain through china cap and fine mesh strainer combo.  

5)  Pray that you put the stopper into the steam kettle.

5)  Label and date, put in blast chiller to cool.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35819" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Dumpling.jpg">1)  Place steamed dumplings and cooked lai fen in serving bowl.  Cover with hot broth.

2)  Garnish with chopped bok choy, bean sprouts and green onion.  Add garlic chili oil in soup broth 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36075" image="">1)  Combine all well.  Allow to marinate for at least an hour, and up to 8.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Beef Vindaloo
Chickpea Vindaloo

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Over medium/ low heat in large rondeau, add oil, cinnamon and onions and cook till nearly carmalized and golden brown.

2)  Add ginger, garlic, seeded serrano peppers and cook until peppers are soft.

3) Add tomato paste and cook, stirring often until it is a deep, dark brown.

4) Add ground dry spices and vindaloo paste and cook for 10 minutes, or until spice is cooked out. Taste to ensure that the spices are cooked out. 

5)  Add water, diced tomatoes and juice, salt, lemon juice and brown sugar.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

6)  Remove from heat, remove cinnamon sticks.  Puree with immersion blender. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36078" image="">1)  Stir fry marinated vindaloo beef until well done.  Add vindaloo sauce and combine well.  Bring to a simmer.  Add fried potatoes and hold for service.

2)  When an order is placed, put appropriate amount of basmati rice in serving bowl and top with vindaloo beef and potato mixture.  

3)  Top with yogurt, cilantro and crispy papadum.  Serve immediately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37090" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients except for corn starch and water in sauce pot.  Bring to a simmer.  Blend well with immersion blender.

2)  Combine water and corn starch to make a slurry.  Add to simmering sauce and allow to simmer until thickened.  Sauce should be a light, sticky consistency.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37093" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Spaghetti.jpg">1)  Blanch cooked pasta in hot water until it is hot throughout.  Place hot pasta in serving bowl.

2)  Top with 5 meatballs and 6 fl. oz of tomato sauce.

3)  Garnish with parmesan cheese and parsley.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43680" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pot over medium low heat, add oil.  

2)  Process garlic as you normally would in food processor, but stop before a fine paste forms.  You want chunky bits of garlic.

3)  Add garlic bits for warm oil and fry, stirring frequently for 4-5 minutes until garlic is crispy.  Strain through fine mesh strainer and reserve oil.  Place cripsy garlic on papertowel to soak up excess oil.

4)  Once dry, place crispy garlic in appropriate container, lined with papertowel and lid tightly.  Garlic can be stored at room temperature for about 3 days.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43718" image="">***If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher.  You will regret life if you do not do this step.  Trust me.

1) Fill large pot or steam kettle with hot tap water at least 6x water to pasta ratio.

2) Add noodles. Stir stir to make sure noodles do not stick.Soak rice noodles checking for texture. They should be soft enough to bite through but not falling apart on their own weight.

3) When they get cooked they will absorb the sauce and get softer so it is very important you slightly UNDERCOOK the noodles.
If they are fully cooked when prepping they will fall apart when heating and become a mess.

4) Drain the water.

5) Store cooled noodles in container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45009" image="">1)  After Pho stock has been produced and chilled, scrape beef fat from the top of the cooled broth and reserve for seasoning beef pho.

2)  When heating pho broth for service add the quantities of fish sauce, palm sugar, lime juice and beef fat indicated in the recipe.  Stir well to incorporate.

IF YOU ARE PRODUCING MORE OR LESS PHO BROTH INDICATED IN THIS RECIPE, YOU WILL NEED TO MAKE ADJUSTMENTS.  PLEASE USE THE FOLLOWING RATIO PER LITRE OF PHO BROTH YOU NEED TO PRODUCE FOR SERVICE.

PER 1L OF PHO BROTH ADD:

-  5ml lime juice
-  80 ml fish sauce
-  30 g Palm sugar
-  15 g reserved beef pho fat.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45011" image="">1)  Put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher.  You will regret life if you do not do this step.  Trust me.

2)  In large kettle, bring water to a boil.  

3)  Add egg noodles and turn heat down by half.  Simmer egg noodles for 3-5 minutes or until al dente.  

4)  Drain water.  When water is completely drained, add cold water back into pot along with 3 grey lugs of ice.  Until pasta is completely covered.  mix gently.  

5)  Drain water and repeat step 4.  It&apos;s very important to stir the pasta gently to ensure that it is cooled throughout, especially when making large batches.

6)  Strain water again and add cooked pasta to appropriate vesself for storage.  Add a small amount of oil and stir into noodles to avoid having them stick.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45386" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46507" image="">1) Cut cherry tomatoes in half, toss with oil and salt and pepper mix, roast in a hot oven 450F briefly 10 min or so, just to soften up and brown lightly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50006" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Make beef stock as per recipe. Reserve for making sauce.

2) Dice pickles 1/8&quot;.

3) Make Sauteed mushroom, onions, pickles. Add wine, and reduce till most of the liquid is gone and pan is nearly dry. Remove from tilt skillet, and reserve for making sauce.

4) In large stock pot bring beef stock to a simmer, and reserve hot.

5) In tilt skillet on low, melt the butter till it&apos;s no longer frothing, gradually add warm stock to roux while stiring with whisk, until all stock is incorperated.

6) Add sauteed veg to thicken stock and season to taste. If using right away hold warm, or 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50007" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1) Season and sear beef in oil in the wok. Reserve for final dish

2) Add beef to hot stroganoff sauce.

3) Heat up egg noodles in hot water, toss with sauce and beef, garnish with teaspoon of sour cream, parsley, parm.


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:measuring cups, measuring spoon, blender
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50383" image="">1. Pre soak mung beans(overnight preferred)
2. Collect all ingredients
3. Cut tofu into meduim size.
3. Slice tomatoes
3. Heat oil on a stock pot
4. Sautee onions, add garlic
5. add tomatoes. cook until tomatoes are soft and turned into a paste like(oil comes out)
6. Deglaze it with vegetable stock( 500ml)
7. Add in drained mung beans, stir, and add the rest of the stock, Bring to boil, once it boils turn down heat, add your fish sauce, salt and pepper.
8. Check Mung beans, if its tender/cooked stir in tofu and spinach.
9. Taste and adjust seasoning.

Serving Size:180ml per serving.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50414" image="">1) Wash rice combine all ingredient and mix well.

2) Cook mix rice into the steamer for about 50 min then  check to ensure rice is fluffy and cooked.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50417" image="">1) Toast peppercorn in a DRY pan over medium low heat until fragrent. Then put cardamom and peppercorn into cheeesecloth (sachet). Toast rest of the spices DRY in the same pan over medium low heat, until fragrant; set aside.

2) In the roasting pans oil and season lamb with salt and pepper then put on roasting  pans (1 box per pan) roast at 500 in combi oven, until fully browned but not cooked through about 10 minutes.

3) While lamb is roasting in the oven, In tilt skillet at 325, add oil and when the oil is hot add, 1/4inch dice onion. Cook until dark brown then add chop garlic saute until browned and soft. Add tomatoes, chili flakes and toasted spices including sachet cooking and stirring 2-3 minutes. 

4) Add seared lamb and chopped mint and cilantro. Cover, reduce heat to a simmer; cook until lamb is tender, about 1hour. Add water if curry gets too dry.

5) Adjust seasoning w/ salt/ pepper.

6) Transfer, cool, label/date and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50422" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Lamb.jpg">Plae rice in bowl, top with lamb stew. top with chopped mint and cilantro
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50428" image="">1) wash off both

2) Complete dry with dry towel

3) Chop nicely</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50433" image="">1) Make beef stock from recipe.

2) In a tilt kettle set over medium heat, add the oil. Add the diced pancetta and cook for further 10 minutes, until the pancetta is golden and crisp.

3) Add the onion cook till translucent about 5 mintues, then add carrots and celery. Add half the salt and pepper mix and saute for 5 minutes.

4) Add the beef 1kg at a time, breaking up any lumps with a wooden spoon. Allowing the water and liquid from the meat to evaporate, and the meat to caramalize. Allow each batch to fully cook before adding more beef. Repeat until all meat is added and cooked.

5) Add the white wine in to tilt kettle to deglaze. With the wooden spoon, scrape all the brown bits from the bottom of the pan. Keep this process up until all brown is scraped up, and the wine should be mostly evaporated. Reduce heat to low.

6) Add the milk, tomatoes, beef broth and remaining salt and pepper. Turn up the heat to medium again and bring to boil, once boiling return to low heat and simmer for about 3 hours, stir every 20-30 mintues the consistency should be like oatmeal and be rich and creamy, no liquid should separate from the sauce when you push the sauce to the outside. Adjust seasoning to taste.

6) Place in containers, chill in blast chiller, label, date refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50435" image="">1) Cut pancetta log in half length-wise, then cut in to 1/4&quot; slices. Then further chop the slices in to 1/4&quot; chunks.

2) Place in container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50454" image="">1) Make garlic oil and paste ahead of time to alow to cool, place garlic oil in an insert for service, kept at room temp.

2) In cold holding have your tomatoes, shrimp, garlic paste, arugula, parsley, and lemon wedges.

3) For service, heat pasta per portion in hot water basket. Once hot, drain well, add to tossing bowl, add 15ml of garlic oil, 5 ml of garlic paste, 15g of arugula, 90g of shrimp, 5g of of salt and pepper, and 25g of roasted cherry tomatoes. Toss well with tongs to combine.

4) With tongs gather pasta and add it to serving bowl, pour rest of toppings from tossing bowl over pasta and garnish with chopped parsley and lemon wedge.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50464" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Mac &amp; cheese

Method:

1) Set milk out to warm up while doing other steps.

2) In pot melt the butter over medium heat

3) Add the flour through fine mesh chinois while whisking melted butter to insure that no lumps are formed.

4) Stir until the mixture is smooth and with out lumps, this is the time to be more careful. Cook for 1 minute so the flour becomes tastier and absorbs the fats. The roux should be a nice golden colour.

5) Add warm milk to roux in a steady stream, whisking continuously. Simmer on low heat until it starts to thicken, but insure it does not come to a boil. Whisk in the salt and pepper mix, and nutmeg, taste for seasoning and adjust if needed. Set aside for recipe.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50469" image="">1) In large pan, brown the ground beef until the pink colour is gone. Add onion and saute until translucent, about 5 mintues, Add garlic and cook until fragrant, about 1 minute.

2) Add wine to the pan and allow to simmer and reduce a bit before adding cinnamon, all spice, parsley, tomato paste, and crushed tomatoes, and sugar.

3) Allow the sauce to simmer, uncovered, for approximately 15 minutes so that exess liquid can evaporate. It should be drier, chunkier sauce. Season to taste with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50474" image="">1. Using a peeler, partially peel the eggplants, leaving strips about 1&quot; wide around the eggplant. Slice the eggplant into 1/2&quot; round slices.

2. Place the eggplant slices in a colander and salt them liberally. Cover them with an other heavy dish to weigh down the eggplant and help them purge more water. Place colander over large container or sink to drain off the water. Let sit for 1 hour.

3. If preping ahead of time you can let the purged, and rinsed eggplant dry in cooler over night.

4. Peel the potatoes, cut in to 1/4&quot; round slices, place in perferated steaming trays and steam for 7-10 mintues. They should not get too soft, just cooked enough so that they no longer crunch. 

5. Roast eggplant with oil on baking trays until cooked through. Cool and reserve for recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50481" image="">Cook chorizo

Saute onions and peppers

Heat tomato sauce

Cook Penne

Assemble by tossing chorizo, peppers and onions with tomato sauce and penne and place into ramekin. 

Top ramekin with mozza and parm

Bake unitl pasta in hot and cheese is bubbly.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50494" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto and half of the mozza cheese, then place shredded kale, zuchinni, and torn pieces of proscuitto evenly across flatbread.

2) Sprinkle remaining half of mozza cheese over top.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked, cut and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

Slice Proscuitto using #2.5 slicer.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50501" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Shrimp Pasta.jpg">1. Slice drained sundried tomatoes into long thin strips about 1/4 lenghtwise.

2. Place pasta portion in basket in hot water pot to reheat pasta.  Drain well, removing any excess water from pasta, and place in mixing bowl. 

3. Add 4oz ladle of pesto, sundried tomatoes, shrimp, arugula and salt &amp; pepper to the spaghetti and mix well with tongs to coat all pasta with sauce. You may have to add a small splash of the pasta water to loosen.

4. Place high in serving bowl placing some of the ingredients on top of pasta and top with parmesan cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50509" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50533" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto and mozzarella cheese, then place artichoke heart pieces and caramalized onion evenly across flatbread.

2) Evenly place halved grape tomatoes around flatbread, 

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 3-4 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked, cut, sprinkle arugula and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50540" image="">1. Heat oven to 350 and bake for 20-30 minutes. Till hot all the way through, and bachemel deeply browned on top.

2. Once baked and hot, cut the baked moussaka in the hotel pan, in to 16 even pieces. Scoop out with spatulas, and place on plate. Serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50541" image="">1) Put 250g of pasta in a mixing bowl and add 125ml of the bolognese sauce, mix thoroughly, place in single serving dish.

2) Top with Parm, then cover with mozza.

3) In 350F oven bake for 10-20 minutes, until hot all the way through and cheese browned.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50562" image="">1. Spread pesto across entire surface area of flatbread.

2. Add capicollo, sundried tomatoes then mozzarella.

3. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Take it off from oven and finish with balsamic glaze.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50590" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread pesto, caramelized onion.

3. Spread crumbled goat cheese, half sliced cherry tomatoes.

4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until cherry tomatoes are fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

5. Take out of oven.

7. Spread arugula and drizzle with balsamic glaze.

8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50674" image="">1. Process all veg,
2. In the wok, heat up oil, stir in onions, cook abt 2mins, add in garlic, cook for another minute. carefull not to burn garlic.
3. Add vegestables, Cooking time of veg varies so add in carrots first then peas and peppers.You can add in a bit of water. 
4. When all veg are almost done stir in bak choy.
5.Stir in red thai curry sauce. mix and season.
5. Transfer it to baine marie when done, or keep it warm until service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50681" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Stir Fry.jpg">1. In a bowl, scoop in rice.. 
2. scoop Thai curry stir-fry veg and sauce and pour it over rice.
3. Garnish with chopped cilantro and cashews</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with hot liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50686" image="">1) Removed the cabbage core and shred cabbage finely.

2) place water, vinegar, and sugar in a bowl and whisk together until the sugar is mostly dissolved, add salt  then pour over the cabbage.

3) transfer to container and keep in the fridge. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50690" image="">1. Pre heat oven 375F.
2. In a baking sheet, lay flat cashew.
3. Roast it for about 8-10minutes or until golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50691" image="">Medium heat mixed well.

Ensure that the tofu has been fried as per preceeding sub recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50694" image="">1) Heat up puttanesca sauce, place in half hotel pans, add artichoke hearts and hold for service.

2) For service, heat pasta per portion in hot water basket. Once hot, drain well, add to tossing bowl, add 50ml of puttanesca sauce, 45g of arugula. Toss well with tongs to combine.

3) With tongs gather pasta and add it to serving bowl, pour rest of toppings from tossing bowl over pasta and garnish with chopped basil and parm cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50700" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Teriyaki Tofu Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place rice in bowl and top with tofu/sauce mixture, zucchini.

2. Top with all vegetable ingredients in quadrants around the bowl. (Mushroom, cabbage, carrots, cucumber are served cold)

3. Garnish with sliced green onion.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:
sauce: 2oz ladel
rice: 1.5 white scoop
cabbage: yellow scoop
zucchini: yellow scoop
teriyaki: white scoop
mushroom: yellow scoop


Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50819" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50825" image="">1) Roast Sweet Potato in oven at 350 for 35
 minutes or until potatoes are cooked through.

2) Place in bag and put on hot plate for grab and go alforno items.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51193" image="">Put rice in a bowl, add stew.

Garnish with green onion and crispy garlic.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51194" image="">Trim pork of any excessively thick fat.

Cube and dredge in seasoned cornstarch

Deep fry to set the crust, and cook through.

Drain oil off and lay out on sheet pans to cool, or use immediatley. 

Reserve for sweet and sour pork recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51195" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Sweet and Sour Pork.jpg">1)  Make sweet and sour sauce as per recipe.

2)  Cut Pork into 1&quot; chunks , dredge in seasoned cornstarch and fry in deep fryer at 350*F for about 45 seconds - 1 minute or until crispy, reserve.  

3)  In hot wok add oil.  When oil is hot, add diced onion and saute for 3-4 minutes or until starting to soften.  Add garlic puree and saute for one minute more.

4)  Add diced red pepper and saute for another minute,  add pineapple and saute for another minute. Add pork.

5)  Add sweet and sour sauce and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for about 1 minute.  

6) Serve by placing rice in a bowl and the stirfry on top.

7) Garnish with green onions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51922" image="">1. In large rondeau, heat oil and sautee garlic until browned, then add chili flake, chopped roma tomatoes, capers, olives, oregano. Stir until fragrant.

2. Add artichoke hearts, remove from heat. Label, date, refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52544" image="">1) In a pot add garlic and olive oil. Place on burner on lowest setting.

2) Let it simmer until garlic is fully browned and soft.

3) Strain out garlic, keeping both the oiland the garlic. 

4) Place garlic in the robocoupe to puree in to paste.

5) Cool and store, garlic and oil seperately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53256" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Remove stems from chilis 

2. Create bouquet garnis with bay leaves + cheese cloth (reserve for cooking process)

3. Combine all ingredients. Blitz chilies into the sauce. 

4. Reserve sauce.

5. When ready to cook the chicken, Add chicken thighs (bone in) to hotel pan (do this in batches as needed for service) cover with reserved sauce add bay leaf, cover pan with lid and place in oven to cook (25-30 mins) Use probe thermometer to ensure temp and doneness. (74C-165F)

6. for service place chicken portion on serving vessel, ladle 1fl oz of sauce over chicken. Serve with kindness.

HOT HOLD/SERVE IMEDIATELY

* Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54644" image="">1) In 2&quot; hotel pan, spread thin layer of 240g meat sauce, then layer 960g eggplant pieces on, then 480g cooked potato slices, seasoning veg with salt and pepper mix.

2) Then add a 1920g layer of the meat filling, sprinkle parm over meat.

3) Then a 960g layer of baked eggplant, topped with the 1.36L of bechemel,

4) Heat oven to 350 and bake for 20-30 minutes. Till hot all the way through, and bachemel deeply browned on top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54667" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix cooked pasta with sauce evenly.

2. Place in full size hotel pans.

3. Cover with plastic wrap and a metal lid, steam with the thermometer in until internal temperature reachs 160F. 

4. Place in oven at 400F until cheese is golden brown. Cut in to 16 even pieces (2 x 8).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55494" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Roughly chop pineapple into small pieces and fold into cooked rice.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58343" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Sweat until fragrent but not soft.

2. Use or...

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
