<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="R-63956" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-37171" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-57583" image="">1. Place rice on one part of the plate and place deep fried pork cutlet on top.

2. Put edamame on another portion of the plate.

3. Place sauce on plate and garnish pork with green onion.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice. Use the same dicing blade for the red onions.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Egg
Milk

Method:

1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.  

2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26175" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Roughly crush cloves.  Add all ingredients in bowl and mix wel

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26056" image="">1. Cut tomatoes in half horizontally. Squeeze romano oil on tomato and season with salt &amp; pepper

2. Grill seed side down for 2-3 minutes or until grill marks are visible and tomato begins to soften.

3.  Hold for service or serve immidiately.

1 portion (ea) of grilled tomato is 2 halves

Allergens:

No known priority allergens.

Average Roma tomato = 90 g
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50795" image="">1. Thaw Corn. 
2. Saute onion. Add corn and spices. Salt if needed..</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26333" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fine chop parsley and thyme.  Combine with lemon &amp; lime juice, mayo and seasoning.  

2. Taste for seasoning and adjust if necessary.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44528" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing and portioning purposes only.

Make associated sub recipes as indicated in those particular recipes

The portion of sauce is 200ml or 6 fl. oz </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

4) Season with salt &amp; pepper. 

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26091" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26385" image="">1)  Combine olive oil, lemon juice, crushed red pepper and crushed garlic and seasoning.  Combine well with a whisk.

2)  Pour marinade over torn kale leaves.  Toss to coat and refrigerate overnight in an appropriate container.  

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1)  In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

2)  Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26328" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In appropriate sized sauce pan, combine rice vinegar, salt, sugar, and simmer until salt and sugar are dissolved.  Add thai chilis and ginger, turn off heat and allow mixture to cool to room temperature.

2)  Meanwhile, add carrot and daikon radish to 4L cambro container.  Add room temp pickling solution, and wiegh down vegetables with parchment to keep them submerged.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.  Vegetables are best if left to pickle for at least 24 hours.

Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26196" image="">1. Combine lemon juice, lime juice, vinegar, dijon, shallot, garlic, sugar, and salt and pepper mix in blender. Combine on medium speed
2. Slowly incorporate oil to create an emulsification. Add chopped parsley.  Check for seasoning
3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Dairy
Sulphites
Method:

1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26169" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat butter chicken in steamer until hot throughout.

2. Transfer to serving vessel to hold for service

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 375*F.  Pull out garlic butter to soften,  or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic wrap until it is spreadable.

2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter.  Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26047" image="">1. Add eggs to appropriate cooking vessel
2. Cover with cold water by 1 inch
3. Bring to boil slowly over medium heat. Once boil is reached, remove from heat, cover and let sit for 12 minutes
4. Run eggs under cold water until cool
5. Place in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Alternatively, eggs can be made in rationale oven by steaming on 100% steam for 13 minutes.  Ensure to ice bath to bring down temperature and to stop the eggs from overcooking.

Allergens:

Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26127" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Tie bay leaf, thyme and rosemary with butchers string.

2. Combine beef stock, garlic cloves and herb bundle. Bring to a simmer. 

3. Simmer about 20 minutes. Strain stock and keep warm.

4. Add cornstarch slurry to stock while whisking until thickened.

5. Season to taste with salt, pepper and vinegar.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26181" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Pre heat rationale oven to 250F

2) Remove excess fat from brisket, score fatty side. Rub brisket in Berbere rub.  Set aside.  Brisket can be rubbed up to two days before.

3) Place brisket and braising liquid in deep 6&quot; hotel pan, cover with parchment and then cover insert with aluminum foil.  Fold aluminum foil back about half way so you can see meat and braising liquid.  

4)  Place insert over burners or on french top and bring to a boil.  

5) Place in rationale oven and cook for 12 hours or until tender.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26063" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine half of blueberries and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the blueberries and heat until no longer frozen but still firm, about 5-8 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26527" image="">1)  Place beets in perforated tray.  Steam beets until tender enough that a paring knife can be easily inserted into beet with little resistance.  Allow to cool.  When cool enough to handle, slip off skins and cut into bite sized portions.

2)  Season with salt and pepper and store in appropriate vessel.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine soy sauce, thai chili&apos;s, sugar, cilantro, lime juice and garlic puree.  Whisk well until sugar is fully dissolved.  

2. Dice tofu into 1-1.25&quot; cubes and add to marinade.  Allow to marinate for at least 2 hours in appropriate vessel. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam rice.

2. Once rice is out of the steamer add all ingredients - oil, lime juice &amp; spice mix - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

3. When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26312" image="">1)  Peel and cut carrots on bias into medium sized angle cuts.  Put in perforated tray and steam until al dente, about 8 minutes.

2)  Combine with sweet and spicy glaze, and serve immediately, or hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 320F

2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice.

3.  Slice each butt in half, and season pork with salt and pepper.  Make sure to get in all the cracks.

4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer on french top before putting it in the oven.

5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 3.5 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart

6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks, removing large pieces of fat. Add back some of braising liquid in pork to keep moist

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine water and salt in a large pot.  Bring to a boil.

2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.  This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279



1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26073" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine mayo, sambal, lime juice, salt &amp; pepper and honey thoroughly.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26065" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 

Mustard

Method:

1. Combine mayo, ketchup, mustard, relish, pureed shallot, salt &amp; pepper in a mixing bowl. Combine well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26450" image="">1)  Make veg stock as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau, add oil.   Add onions and saute for 2-3 minutes or until starting to soften.  Add garlic and saute for 30 seconds more. Add thyme, rosemary and red wine.  Bring to a low simmer. Add veg stock and bring to a simmer.

3)  Combine soy, nutritional yeast and corn starch to form a very thick slurry.  Add to warm stock, whisking constantly.  Bring back to a simmer until stock thickens and corn starch is evenly dispersed.

5)  Allow to cool in appropriate vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate. 

Allergens:

Soy
Sulphite
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat up oil in large sauce pot over medium low heat.  

2. Add garlic and and gently cook for 10 minutes.  That&apos;s right, 10 minutes.  Then add ginger puree and continue gently cooking for another 5-10 minutes. Stir it alot to make sure it doesn&apos;t burn, but really cook it out. 

3. Add kecap manis and rice vinegar.  Bring to a simmer for 10-15 minutes over medium heat.  Add corn starch slurry and simmer for another 5 minutes until thick.

4. Do not strain.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28249" image="">1)  Season and grill beef patty until well done (71*C).  

2)  While patty is grilling,toast on grill and add thunderbird sauce to both sides of bun and lettuce to the bottom portion of bun.

3)  Place cooked beef patty on top of lettuce and close.  Top with pickle and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28250" image="">1)  Follow same procedure as classic beef burger, but add cheese to the patty when it is 90% cooked.  Top with pickle spear and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28251" image="">1)  Season and grill chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked.

2)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and garnish with guacamole and lemon herb aioli.  Top cooked chicken breast with cheese until melted.

3) Add tomato, cooked bacon and citrus arugula.

4) Close bun and top with pickle skewer.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28254" image="">1)  Spread butter on outside of sourdough and put butter side down on griddle.  While still on the griddle, put cheeses on both sides of bread.  

2) Warm oven dried tomatoes and place them over entire surface area of sandwich.

3) Close sandwich when cheese begins to melt.  Continue grilling until bread is golden brown and cheese in completely melted.

4) Cut in half from corner to corner.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28280" image="">Using a #12 scoop, portion out 1 portion of eggs, one portion of potatoes and 2 halves of grilled tomato.  lightly dress arugula with cirus oil and a pinch of S+P.  Serve Immediately.

10 grams of bacon = 2 cooked slices

breakfast comes with choice of bacon (2pc) or sausage(1pc)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28281" image="">1)  Crack egg on flat top and grill.  Meanwhile, toast bun and spread evenly with mayo.  flip egg to cook over easy and place on bottom of bun.  Top with bacon, cheddar, and citrus arugula and close bun.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28285" image="">1)  Combine pancake mix and water throughly.  Reserve for service.

Allergens:  

Gluten
Wheat
Gluten
Soy 
Dairy
Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28286" image="">1)  Grab your #12 scoop.  Grab scrambled eggs from hot holding vessel.  Put on plate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28288" image="">1)  Cook sausage in 350*F oven until probe thermometer reaches 71*C.  Hold for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28293" image="">Allergens:
Gluten, Wheat, Mustard, Soy, Egg

Icons:
N/A


1)  Fry chicken strips according to package directions.  Double check that they are fully cooked by using a probe thermometer and taking the temperature.  Chicken strip should register at least 70*C to ensure it is well done.  Hold for service in food warmer.

2)  Serve with choice of sauce.

*Recipe assumes 2.0 oz avg. weight per chicken strip.  4 per order.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28994" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients in Robocoupe.  Mix in baches if doing large amount and season to taste.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28995" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Shred cucumber in robotcoupe.  Combine all ingredients well in mixing bowl.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28301" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44379" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. scoop mash into bowl
2. top mash with portion of chicken pot pie filler
3. top with pie shell


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-30406" image="">- Pre-heat oven to 350
- bake 20-25 minutes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31111" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Add water to steam kettle, add konbu and bring to a simmer for 15 minutes. Remove konbu. 

2) Turn off heat, whisk in miso.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32192" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In large rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter.  When oil/butter is hot, add garlic and saute until golden.  Add half of corn and saute until tender, about 3-5 minutes. 

2)  Add cream and simmer 10-15 minutes more.

3)  Blend with hand blender, add remaining corn for texture.  Continue to simmer until reduced and thick.  Add S+P to taste.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57582" image="">1. Place rice on one part of the plate and place deep fried pork cutlet on top.

2. Put edamame on another portion of the plate.

3. Place sauce on plate and garnish pork with green onion.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33554" image="">1)  Combine all dry ingredients, then add in milk and egg.  Combine all well and reserve for dredging fish.

Allergens:

Egg
Milk/Dairy
Gluten
Wheat</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33557" image="">1)  Combine all well.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33556" image="">1)  Preheat fryer to 350*F

2)  Add fish to seasoned flour, then add to fried fish batter.  Add fish for preheated oil and fry until cooked through and crispy on the outside, about 4 minutes.  Serve immidiately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33866" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together and allow to marinade for 24 hours.

2. In a large rondo or tilt skillet add oil and when warm add chciken in batches ( do not overcrowd). This will allow a nice sear on the chicken.

3. Cook fully and hot hold for service.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33867" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Make veg stock as per recipe.  

2. Combine veg stock with onion, garlic, jalapeno and parsley.  Blend well. 

3. Rinse rice very well under water.  Add puree to rice and steam for 35 minutes.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service quickly steam green beans and toss with s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-34864" image="">
Combine salad greens with ranch dressing.  Plate on large square plate.

Top with sliced cherry tomato, cucumber, egg, avocado slices, cheese, bacon and turkey in seperate piles on top of greens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35313" image="">1) Toss romaine lettuce and croutons together in bowl with dressing.  Place greens on plate. 

2) Top with parmesan cheese, croutons and lemomn wedge.  Serve immidiately.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35337" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Milk
Dairy

Method:

1)  Preheat oven to 300*F

2)  In appropriate sized pot, combine water, garlic, shallot and thyme bring to a simmer, then take off heat and allow to infuse for about 20 minutes.  Strain out aromatics and add cream. Reserve warm.

3)  Combine cornmeal and salt.  Pour cornmeal mixture into stock and cream while whisking constantly

4)  Add mixture to hotel pans, and put in oven.  bake for 45 minutes, stirring every 15 minutes.

5)  Add butter and parmesan cheese.  Taste for seasoning and reserve for service, or 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35338" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor, combine half of the oil, vinegar, basil, parsely, arugula, garlic puree and seasoning.  Process until smooth.  Do not strain.  

2)  Add remianing oil and STIR with a spoon or spatula to combine. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35341" image="">1)  Place warm polenta in bottom of bowl.  Top with marinated kale and radish, then egg, and garnish with salsa verde.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47340" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35714" image="">1)  Dredge chicken breast in cajun spice and grill until 50% cooked and starting to char and blacken.  Put in oven until cooked through.  

2)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill and dress bottom of bun with mayonnaise, lettuce, red onion, and tomato.  Put chicken back on grill and top with cheese. Place under steamer lid to reheat chicken and melt cheese, about 2 minutes.

3)  Place on top of bottom bun with toppings and close bun.  Garnish with dill pickle and serve immidiately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35723" image="">1)  Remove labels from cans of condensed milk.

2)  Bring water to a boil in large rondeau.  Once a boil is reached, carfully place unopened cans of condensed milk into water and lower to a simmer.  Continue simmering for 5 hours (or more, you can&apos;t really over cook it!)

3)  ***IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THAT YOU CONTINUE TO FILL THE WATER AND MAKE SURE THE CANS ARE COMPLETELY COVERED.  THEY WILL EXPLODE IF LEFT UNATTENDED.***

4)  Allow to cool completely (overnight is best).  Peel away tops of cans and scoop into appropriate sized insert if needed right away.  Otherwise, just leave in the cans until needed.  Ensure to label.

Allergens:

Milk/Dairy
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35798" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat oil in rondeau over medium low heat.  Once oil is warm, add onions and paprika.  Saute for about 5 mintues until onions begin to soften.

2. Add garlic and saute for 1 minute more.  Add tomato &amp; oregano.  Add spinach a handful at a time, ensuring that it wilts before adding another handful.

3. Reduce heat to medium. Add drained chickpeas and alllow to simmer, stirring occassionally, for about 30 minutes.

4. Season to taste with vinegar, salt &amp; pepper.  Hold for service, or

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35823" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut potatoes in half then steam until tender, about 15 minutes.

2. On medium low heat, add oil to large rondeau.  Add cumin seeds and toast until fragrant, 30 seconds to 1 minute.  Add onion, coriander, chili powder, turmeric, jalapeno and garam masala.  Saute until onion is soft and spices are fragrant.  

3. Add garlic and ginger and saute for 1 minute more. 

4. Add tomato paste and saute for 4 minute.  Add diced tomatoes and saute 1 minute more.

5. Add fenugreek, lime juice and fresh coriander and stir well to combine.

6. Adjust seasoning.

7. NOTE: Add cooked potatoes and cauliflower during REHEATING for service for best results.

8. Stir well to combine.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35799" image="">Allergens:

Sulphites
Soy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35772" image="">1) Produce as per prep recipe.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28291" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35270" image="">1)  Place beef patty on grill.  Ensure that it is cooked well done (above 71*C)

2)    Place sauted mushrooms on burger patty, then top with cheese.  Place steamer lid on top of patty and steam until cheese is melted and mushrooms are warm.

3)  Meanwhile, garnish bun with garlic mayo on both sides and lettuce on bottom half of burger.  

4)  Top beef patty with bacon and place lettuce on bottom half of bun.  Garnish with pickle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36043" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36061" image="">1)  Put cous-cous in hotel pan.

2)  Bring water to a simmer.  Put over cous-cous and cover until cous-cous has absorbed all the water (5-10 minutes).  Fluff with a fork until tghere are no lumps and put on baking sheet to cool.

3)  When cous-cous is cool, combine with green onion, parsley, green and red pepper and viniagrette.  Taste for seasoning.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36065" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Cut potatoes in half.  Steam until 70% done in rational.  Add oil and season with salt and pepper and roast in oven at 425*F until crisp.  Add garlic chili oil and mix well.  Reserve for salad.

2)  Thaw corn by steaming 

3) Cook bacon and reserve, crumble when cooled, and keep for garnish for service.

4)  Combine potatoes, corn &amp; green onion.  Reserve for service. Top with dressing and bacon crumble (if desired) for each order.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Dairy
Milk 
Method:

1.Combine all well.

2. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36075" image="">1)  Combine all well.  Allow to marinate for at least an hour, and up to 8.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36074" image="">1)  Roast Spaghetti Squash as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onion and saute until translucent, about 2-3 minutes.  Turn heat down to medium, add chili flakes and curry powder and continue sauteing for another 5 minutes, ensuring to cook out the spices.  Add garlic puree and saute 1 minute more.

3)  Add peeled roasted spaghetti squash, coconut milk and salt and bring to a simmer.  Add spinach a handful at a time until fully incorporated.  

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Beef Vindaloo
Chickpea Vindaloo

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Over medium/ low heat in large rondeau, add oil, cinnamon and onions and cook till nearly carmalized and golden brown.

2)  Add ginger, garlic, seeded jalapenos and cook until peppers are soft.

3) Add tomato paste and cook, stirring often until it is a deep, dark brown.

4) Add ground dry spices and vindaloo paste and cook for 10 minutes, or until spice is cooked out. Taste to ensure that the spices are cooked out. 

5)  Add water, diced tomatoes and juice, salt, lemon juice and brown sugar.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

6)  Remove from heat, remove cinnamon sticks.  Puree with immersion blender. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35015" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-35014" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. cook fries crispy
2.season and toss in stainless boewl
3.place portiuon in bowl and serve
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34085" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Combine everything except chicken.  

2)  Incorporate chicken and allow to marinate for at least 24 hours.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28323" image="">Serve ingredients in the indicated proportions.

Place the butter chicken on top of the rice. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28324" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28363" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35271" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.  

2. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56884" image="">1. Reheat cooked pasta in blancher until hot.

2. Drain well and toss pasta in mixing bowl with a ladle of ratatouille.

3. Garnish with parmesan and chopped parsley.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50746" image="">1) Combine all ingredients in a pot, heat at medium until sugar dissolves. Then remove from heat.

2) Cool fully before using as marinade or if using later, store in appropriate sized vessel, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Cut lemons in quarters. Crush garlic and slice shallots.

2)  Combine all except chicken breast.  Stir well to combine.

3)  In a non-reactive container (plastic) add chicken.  Add marinade and JUST ENOUGH OIL to COAT not COVER the chicken breasts and mix well.  Allow to marinate for 8 hours or overnight.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-34129" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-37093" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Spaghetti.jpg">1)  Blanch cooked pasta in hot water until it is hot throughout.  Place hot pasta in serving bowl.

2)  Top with 5 meatballs and 6 fl. oz of tomato sauce.

3)  Garnish with parmesan cheese and parsley.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28364" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35517" image="">1)  Place all ingredients in mixing bowl and combine well.

Allergens:

Milk/Dairy
Egg
Soy
Gluten
Wheat</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-38518" image="">1)  Make cous-cous as per recipe.  Scoop appropriate amount of cous-cous and SERVE IT FORTH!

2)  Give yourself a hi-5</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28337" image="">Serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32195" image="">serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60528" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35273" image="">1) Drain liquid from pickles.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36078" image="">1)  Stir fry marinated vindaloo beef until well done.  Add vindaloo sauce and combine well.  Bring to a simmer.  Add fried potatoes and hold for service.

2)  When an order is placed, put appropriate amount of basmati rice in serving bowl and top with vindaloo beef and potato mixture.  

3)  Top with yogurt, cilantro and crispy papadum.  Serve immediately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40877" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Milk/ Dairy
Method:

1)  In large pot over medium heat, combine milk, cream, thyme, garlic, shallot &amp; bay leaf.  Bring to a light simmer, then turn off and allow to infuse about 20 minutes.

2)  Meanwhile, make caramalized onions as per recipe.  Caramalized onions can be made up to 2 days before.  Ensure to store in a perforated insert to allow any excess oil to drain out.  

3)  Run peeled yam and russet potato through 1/8&quot; slicer attachement, and reserve for recipe.

4)  Combine sliced potatoes, infused cream, caramalized onions, 2/3&apos;s of parmesan cheese and salt and pepper.  Combine well.

5)  Place in oiled 2&quot; hotel pan, a steam in rationale at 100% steam for 20 minutes until potatoes are al dente.  

6)  Top potatoes with remaining cheese and bake in 350*F oven for another 10-15 minutes, or until potatoes are cooked through and cheese is melted and looks like you wanna eat it.

7)  Hold warm for service. OR&gt;&gt;&gt;

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-40878" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-40972" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Combine portioned salmond pieces, marinade.  Allow to marinate overnight.

2)  Preheat rationale oven to 100% steam.  Steam salmon in hotel pans to 50*C (122*F).  Remove immidiately about 4 minutes.

3)  Prior to service, heat sauce to a simmer.  Keep warm for service.

4)  Use to season salmon by pouring a tbsp. over top.  Pour hot sauce over fish to finish.  Hold hot for service.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41087" image="">1)  Prepare the tofu with the exception of cutting the tofu into 150g &quot;steaks&quot;.

2) Combine portioned tofu pieces, with marinade  Allow to marinate overnight.

3) Grill tofu, baste with sauce and hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41089" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-41073" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41088" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41085" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-33558" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Gluten

Method:

1. Start by dropping 2 pieces of battered 3oz cod into the deep fryer, cook untill hot and flaky inside and golden and crisp on the outside.

2. Fry the fies until golden and crisp, season botht he fish and the fries straight out of the fryer.

3. Plating; place the hot fries on the base of the plate, place the 2 x fried cod on top of the fries to give hight, place the coleslaw on the side of the fries and 2oz of tartar sauce into a ramekin on the side of the plate, garnish with wedge of lemon and serve with kindness!

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42292" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients well until full incorporated.

2)  Reserve in appropriate container for Tandori Chicken.  Label, Date, Refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42293" image="">1)  Drain chicken legs well and put into apprpriate container.  Pour tandoori marinade over chicken legs, ensuring to get in there with your hands to disperse the marinade.  Label, date, refrigerate.

2)  Allow chicken to marinate overnight.  

3)  Be a friend to your GWH&apos;s.  Line baking pans with aluminum foil.

4)  Place perforated screens on top of baking trays in arrange chicken legs to fit.  Do not over crowd.  Discard excess marinade.

5)  Preheat oven to 180*C (350*F).  Bake for about 30 minutes, or until a probe thermomoeter inserted into the largest thigh reaches 65*C (149*F).

6)  Wheel out rack from Rationale oven and crank heat to 500*F.

7)  When oven is hot, put chicken back in.  Allow skin to blacken slightly.  Ensure that chicken legs reach internal temperature of 71*C (160*F).  

8)  Hold hot for service. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42317" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 375*F.

2)  Cut spaghetti squash in half and scoop out the seeds.

3)  Rub flesh of squash with oil and season with salt and pepper.  Place flesh side down on parchemnt lined baking tray and put in oven.  

4)  Roast for 25-30 minutes, or until squash flesh is tender and peel comes off easily.  Scoop out roasted squash and discard peel.  Reserve for recipe, or label date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42319" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter.  Once oil and butter are warm, add garlic, ginger and crushed chili.  Saute for 2-3 minutes.

2. Add all spices except salt and sugar.  Continue sauteing until spices are cooked out, about another 5 minutes.  

3. Add crushed tomato, salt and sugar.  Bring to a simmer.

4. Add water and bring back to a simmer.  Add cream and kasoori methi.  

5. Taste for seasoning.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42320" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine yogurt and spices.  Mix to combine well.  Reserve marinade.

2. Cut Paneer into 1&quot; chunks and pour marinade over top.  Combine gently to get the marinade over all the paneer chunks.  Allow to marinate at least 2 hours or overnight.

3. Preheat oven to 500*F.  Place paneer on foil lined baking sheets.  Broil for 5 minutes or until paneer turns golden brown.  Reserve for making Paneer Tika Masala

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42356" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Make Paneer gravy as per recipe.

2. Make and broil paneer as per recipe.

3. Blanch green peas in hot water, and shock in cold water.  Reserve for paneer tika masala.

4. Thin out gravy with a bit of water and bring to a simmer.  When warm, combine broiled paneer, peas and paneer sauce.  Hold warm for service.

*This recipe should make enough for one shallow hotel pan/cassrole serving vessel..

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-42358" image="">1)  Make Paneer Tika Masala as per recipe.  

2)  Upon order, place appropriate amount of paneer masala on top of rice.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29315" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In tilt skillet (225 F) or large steam kettle over medium/ low heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add garlic, ginger and cayenne.  Saute until cayenne is cooked out and garlic and ginger are no longer potent when smelled, about 5-10 minutes.

2)  Add crushed tomato, diced tomato, honey, kasoori methi and bring to a simmer. Simmer for 15-20 minutes.

3) Add milk and cream and puree with immersion blender to break up the diced tomatoes and ensure that everything is combined well.

4) Adjust seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Take off stems of jalapenos.  Remove pits of avocado and scoop flesh from skin.  Place all ingredients except oil in 20 L cambro container.  

2)  Blend well with immersion blender until a smooth puree consistency is reached.  

3)  Slowly begin adding oil, a little at a time until all oil has been added.  Taste for seasonining.


-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43680" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pot over medium low heat, add oil.  

2)  Process garlic as you normally would in food processor, but stop before a fine paste forms.  You want chunky bits of garlic.

3)  Add garlic bits for warm oil and fry, stirring frequently for 4-5 minutes until garlic is crispy.  Strain through fine mesh strainer and reserve oil.  Place cripsy garlic on papertowel to soak up excess oil.

4)  Once dry, place crispy garlic in appropriate container, lined with papertowel and lid tightly.  Garlic can be stored at room temperature for about 3 days.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57587" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-58385" image="">1. Process veg: dice cucumber 
Julienne romaine. 
Slice green onions to bias.
Half grape tomatoes.

2.slice avocado.

3. Cook eggs, allow to cool and peel and cut into quarters

4. Toss romaine with dressing.

5. Put dressed romaine on a plate. In rows top with, hardboiled eggs, blue cheese, avocado and green onions.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43729" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Combine lemon juice, orange juice, soy sauce, brown sugar, ginger and garlic puree&apos;s.  Mix very well.  Add chicken thighs and marinate for 4-6 hours.

2)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  Add chicken thighs skin side up to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up chicken thighs.  Do not cover skin.  Roast chicken thighs until biggest thigh registers 150*F on an instant read thermometer.

3)  Remove thighs and add to hot holding vessels.  Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining marinade and pour over chicken.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43730" image="">1)  Combine all well and reserve for salad.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43731" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition) 
Method:
1)  Combine brown sugar, S+P mix, soy, lime, and oil.  Mix well.  Add pineapple and allow to marinate for 30 minutes.

2)  Preheat oven to 400*F, add pineapple to parchment lined tray and roast until charred and tender, approx. 15 minutes.

3)  Reserve for salad.  Can be made the day before.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43732" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  Remove kale from stems and cut into bite sized chunks.
2.  Combine with remaining ingredients and hold cold for service.
 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29170" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Make apple cider dressing as per recipe.

2)  Shred cabbages in robot coupe food processor.

3) Pulse cleaned kale in robot coupe until broken down.

4)  Combine shredded cabbages, kale and chopped cilantro.  Mix well with dressing.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28759" image="">1) Place Turkey in 275F oven for approximately 4 hours. Internal temperature should be 165F.

2) Cool completely before slicing.

3) Slice on the meat slicer on a 2.5 setting</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-31948" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50386" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients. Store in appropriate container, lable date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26050" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine  dijon, herbs, shallots, garlic, sriracha, butter milk, salt and peppercorn in a 20L container, puree with a hand blander.

2. Combine greek yougurt &amp; sour cream . Mix thoroughly. Dressing should be thick but pourable.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-30041" image="">57 g = 2 strips of bacon. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50517" image="">1) Remove softer fronds of the dill from the harder stems. Chop well for garnish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38628" image="">PLEASE NOTE:

For portion sizes:

Because we offer 3 choices of sides on a +2 menu I have averaged them out.

These are the full sized portion weights:

Seasonal Veg x 70 g
Creamed Corn x 85 g
Potato Salad x 150 g

guest have choice of creamed corn or seasonal veg or potato salad ( request from nutrition ) </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-63018" image="">1. Dress top &amp; bottom of toasted bun with tahini dressing.

2. Place cooked burger in.

3. Top with amashed avocado, tomato &amp; citrus arugula.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Peel, core and dice the apple.
 
2)  In a big mixing bowl, add all the ingredients and whisk until all the ingredients incorporate. Reserve for service.

3) Transfer to aproppriate container, label, date and store in the fridge.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55083" image="">1. Peel and diced parsnip.
2. Combine the rest of ingredient in mixing bowl.
3. Roast.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35713" image="">1)  Dredge Chicken Breast in house rub.  

2)  Placed dredged breast on parchment lined baking sheet.

3)  Repeat until production for the day is complete.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-14675" image="">Trim any excess fat and sinew from beef

1.Combine herbs with oil and salt and pepper, blend in robocope to make a paste. Rub on trimmed roasts.

2.Cook at 325 at 60% moisture to an internal temperature of 130F.

3.Cool and slice
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60992" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In large pot/ rondo over medium heat add oil.

2. Once warm sweat onion, peppers, jalapeno &amp; garlic until fragrent.

3. Add tomatoes &amp; cream cheese and stir regularly until cheese is fully melted, ensuring you do not burn the cheese on the bottom of the pot.

4. Season with salt &amp; pepper.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-12502" image="">1. Brown chicken bones in oven at 450f for 20 minutes.

2. Add bones to stock pot, cover with cold water.

3. add veg and tomato paste to roasting pans chicken was in, cook off in oven.

4. Once stock comes to boil reduce heat to simmer and skim off fat, add roasted veg and tomato paste.

5. Simmer stock over night or at least 5 hours. Strain with fine mesh strainer.

6. Cool, lable and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35272" image="">1) Remove and discard stem, cut letuce in quarters, then shave off thin strips.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.

Average weight of a head of Iceberg is 470g with 10% yield loss for core and outer leaves. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43746" image="">1) Add dressing to greens, cucumber, carrot, tomatoes, red pepper and mix well. Use just enough dressing to coat the salad.

2) Top with sunflower seeds and radish. Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50348" image="">1) In a flat top, add oil and 4oz for each pancake.

2) Cook about 2 minutes each side.

3) Served with apple compot and coconut whip.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50349" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.In a big mixing bowl, add all the DRY ingredients and whisk until everything is combined well. Add water and continue mix until the mixture incorporate well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.




2) Storage in appropriate container, label ,date and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50350" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Put bowl of stand mixer in freezer for about 5 minutes to ensure it&apos;s cool.

2. Add whipping cream to bowl of stand mixer with whisk attachment. Once cream begins to thicken, add icing sugar, vanilla and cinnamon. Continue to whip until stiff.

3. Can be held for 24 - 36 hours or until it begins to break.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50351" image="">1) In a flat top, add oil and 4oz for each pancake.

2) Cook about 2 minutes each side.

3) Served with maple syrup and cinnamon chantilly.





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50368" image="">1) Prepare egg.

2) Slice thick end of multigrain croissant open, spread mayo on bottom.

2) Toss arugula with citrus oil and salt and pepper, place in bun, top with egg, bacon and cheese, warm on flat top till cheese is melted.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50372" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1) Split pork loin in to quarters lengthwise. Should have 4 tube like pieces. In shallow pan or bag marinate pork for 24 hours making sure it&apos;s fully covered by the marinade.

2) Remove from marinade and place on a lined baking sheet on top of a wire rack. 

3) Roast pork at 425F atop a wire racks on a tin foil lined sheet pan until an internal temp of 144F is achieved. Reserve leftover maridande to recude until proper consistency to coat the cooked meat is reached.

3) Allow the meat to rest. Coat with reduction as needed 

4) Reserve excess marinade reduce in a pot until thick and syurupy. Cube up pork in to 1/4&quot; pieces and toss with reduced marinade to add flavour and moisture back in.

Portioning: 115g

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50389" image="">1) Cut tofu into 150g  slices.

2) Place tofu in container with Shoyu Marinade, let sit for 2-3 hours.

3)  Preheat oven to 425*F.  Add marinaded tofu to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up the tofu slices. Roast tofu for 20 minutes, or until tofu temprature reads 65c on thermometer.

3)  Remove tofu and add to hot holding vessels.  Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining marinade and pour over tofu.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50428" image="">1) wash off both

2) Complete dry with dry towel

3) Chop nicely</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50504" image="">1) Place shaved beef on flat top and cook until starting to brown, add caramelized onion, and sauteed peppers.

2) On bottom piece of baguette, spread garlic mayo, place warmed up beef, onions and peppers. Break the cheddar, and provalone slices in half, and top filling with alternating halves of cheddar and provalone to cover top.

3) Place top of baguette on flat top, crust side down, until it&apos;s warm and starting to get crispy, but not hard.

4) Place place bottom piece with all fillings and cheese on parchment lined flash pan, put in deck oven for 2-3 minutes or until cheese is fully melted.

5) Combine top and bottom of sandwich, cut on a bias and serve.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50464" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Mac &amp; cheese

Method:

1) Set milk out to warm up while doing other steps.

2) In pot melt the butter over medium heat

3) Add the flour through fine mesh chinois while whisking melted butter to insure that no lumps are formed.

4) Stir until the mixture is smooth and with out lumps, this is the time to be more careful. Cook for 1 minute so the flour becomes tastier and absorbs the fats. The roux should be a nice golden colour.

5) Add warm milk to roux in a steady stream, whisking continuously. Simmer on low heat until it starts to thicken, but insure it does not come to a boil. Whisk in the salt and pepper mix, and nutmeg, taste for seasoning and adjust if needed. Set aside for recipe.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50480" image="">1) Put strainer in steam kettle, add chicken bones, and rinse with cold water. Drain.

2) Add all other ingredients to the steam kettle and cover with cold water.

3) Simmer for 4-6 hours uncovered, drain the stock and cool, lable and store.

4) Discard bones and other solids, clean and sanitize the steam kettle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50494" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto and half of the mozza cheese, then place zuchinni, and torn pieces of proscuitto evenly across flatbread.

2) Sprinkle remaining half of mozza cheese over top.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked place arugula then drizzle balsamic reduction over top.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

Slice Proscuitto using #2.5 slicer.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50501" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Shrimp Pasta.jpg">1. Slice drained sundried tomatoes into long thin strips about 1/4 lenghtwise.

2. Place pasta portion in basket in hot water pot to reheat pasta.  Drain well, removing any excess water from pasta, and place in mixing bowl. 

3. Add 4oz ladle of pesto, sundried tomatoes, shrimp, arugula and salt &amp; pepper to the spaghetti and mix well with tongs to coat all pasta with sauce. You may have to add a small splash of the pasta water to loosen.

4. Place high in serving bowl placing some of the ingredients on top of pasta and top with parmesan cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54455" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
1. Dry prawns as best you can, and lightly coat in rice flour.

2. Dip cleaned prawns into batter.

3. Deep fry until cooked through and golden brown.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50506" image="">1) Cut peppers in half, remove stem, seeds, and white rib/membrain. Slice peppers in to 1/8&quot; julien pieces.

2) In a large pan, heat oil on high, add peppers and season. Cook until tender and starting to brown.

3) Cool spread out on bakeing sheet. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50509" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50522" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) In a large bowl, toss carrots in oil, dill, maple syrup, vinegar, salt and pepper.

2) On a parchment lined baking tray, roast carrots at 425F until starting to brown, and cooked through.

3) Sprinkle parsley and toasted pumpkin seeds over carrots and put in vessel to hold hot for service.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37050" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50590" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread pesto, caramelized onion.

3. Spread crumbled goat cheese, half sliced cherry tomatoes.

4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until cherry tomatoes are fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

5. Take out of oven.

7. Spread arugula and drizzle with balsamic glaze.

8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50598" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Put bowl of stand mixer in freezer for about 5 minutes to ensure it&apos;s cool.

2. Add whipping cream to bowl of stand mixer with whisk attachment. Once cream begins to thicken, add icing sugar and lemon zest. Continue to whip until stiff. DO NOT OVERMIX.

3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

4. Can be held for 24 - 36 hours or until it begins to break.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46833" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50690" image="">1. Pre heat oven 375F.
2. In a baking sheet, lay flat cashew.
3. Roast it for about 8-10minutes or until golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50686" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Remove the cabbage core and shred cabbage finely.

2) Place water, vinegar, and sugar in a pot and warm until the sugar is dissolved, add salt, cool completely then pour over the cabbage.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50691" image="">Medium heat mixed well.

Ensure that the tofu has been fried as per preceeding sub recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50739" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine half of apples and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the apples and heat until about 8-10 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-42370" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-28318" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50894" image="">1) Add dressing to greens and mix well.

2) Top with cucumber, carrots, sunflower seeds, tomatoes, radish, red pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-49262" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-45231" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50700" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Teriyaki Tofu Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place rice in bowl and top with tofu/sauce mixture, zucchini.

2. Top with all vegetable ingredients in quadrants around the bowl. (Mushroom, cabbage, carrots, cucumber are served cold)

3. Garnish with sliced green onion.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:
sauce: 2oz ladel
rice: 1.5 white scoop
cabbage: yellow scoop
zucchini: yellow scoop
teriyaki: white scoop
mushroom: yellow scoop


Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57351" image="">1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hold for service.

3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thai basil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-41086" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45151" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-45255" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat

Icons:
N/A

Method:
 70 pcs average per case

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44601" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Toast and grind the cumin &amp; coriander.

2. Add remaining ingredients into large robot coupe with spatula attachement and puree to a smooth paste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


Prep:

- Process all ingredients into a size that will fit easily and not cause problems in the Vitamix. Also, find the PLUNGER for the Vitamix, as you will not be able to do this job without it.

- The Coconut Milk in this recipe will be used to loosen then process of Puree-ing the Green Curry Base Paste. Use Water only if necessary.

- Once processed ingredients and Coconut Milk are ready to go, Vitamix all of these ingredients into a paste. 

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

***This can be made in large batches, and frozen for future use if vac-packed. A Green Curry &quot;Base&quot; recipe only contains 4.62Kg of this base (HALF), to the rest of its ingredients.

Any questions? - Ask Chef...

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51467" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53996" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the onion with oil and salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned around the edges and hot throughout

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28758" image="">1) 

2) slice on a 2.5 setting on the meat slicer
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51828" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-52896" image="">1) On medium heat, combine all ingredients and cook until sugar is fully melted and the glaze becomes sticky and syrupy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53081" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients into food processor or blender and puree on high speed until smooth creamy texture.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53084" image="">Portion burgers to 140g.

Dress bun top and bottom with tahini dressing.

Place cooked burger on bottom bun.

Top with smashed avocado &amp; tomato.

Top with citrus arugula.

Close bun, secure with pick.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57350" image="">1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hold for service.

3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thai basil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57153" image="">1. Sauce goes on side so cutlet doesn&apos;t get soggy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54176" image="">1. Reheat cooked pasta in blancher until hot.

2. Place hot pasta on plate, top with 2 pieces of chicken and ladle of sauce.

3. Garnish with chopped parsley.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54295" image="">1) Dry jalapenos well on a large tray with paper towel.

2) Combine corn starch and spices and mix evenly.

3) Coat jalapeno evenly in corn starch mixture.

4)  Fry in batches without baskets, until crispy.

5) Remove from oil, shake to drain oil and season immediately on a paper towel lines sheet pan. If you wait to long after they come out of the fryer the salt will not stick.

6) Do not overcrowd once they are out of the fryer or they will turn soggy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55084" image="">1. Diced carrot and place in a mixing bowl with the rest of ingredients and roast.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55138" image="">1) In rondo add vegan butter, sliced onion and fresh thyme over medium/low heat and caramalize onions, stirring occasionally.

2) When onions are golden brown sprinkle in flour and stir to form a roux.

3) Slowly add the stock a little at a time whisking the whole time to avoid lumps.

4) Simmer for approximately 10 minutes to cook out flour, stirring occasionally to prevent burning.

5) Add sauce, dijon and adjust seasoning.

6) Hold for service or transfer and chill.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55141" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Ensure corn is defrosted and all excess water removed.

2. In a mixing bowl combine corn, onion, oil, chili powder and salt and pepper and mix evenly.

3. In a 450*F oven cook until corn takes on some dark colour and is slightly caramalized.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55142" image="">1) Place greens, cabbage, beans, peppers, charred corn and tomatoes in mixing bowl.

2) Add dressing and GENTLY toss to combine ensuring all ingredients are coated in dressing.

3) Plate greens leaving some of the vegetables to garnish top of salad.

4) Finish top of salad with radish slices, tortilla strips, pumpkin seeds and feta.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55515" image="">IT IS VERY IMPORTANT SPINACH IS TOTALLY DEFROSTED AND AS MUCH LIQUID HAS BEEN SQUEEZED OUT.

1) In a large pan add oil over medium heat and sweat onion until soft.

2) Add garlic and sweat 1-2 minutes until fragrant.

3) Add mushrooms and cook until most of their liquid has been released.

4) Add spinach and stir to combine ensuring most of liquid in spinach has been released.

5) Season to taste.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55516" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

1) Spread a small amount of cheese sauce on bottom of 2&quot; hotel pans.

2) Spread lasagna noodles evenly.

3) Add mushroom/ spinach mixture then ricotta.

4) Add another layer of noodles.

5) Add sauce and more vegetable mixture.

6) Add noodles/ sauce.

7) Top with mozzarella and parmesan.

8) Bake uncovered in a 300 F oven for 45 mins. Ensure noodles are cooked and internal temperature is between 160-165 F.

Build in this order:
Bottom: 3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Noodles 8
            Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
            Ricotta 500g
            Noodles 8
            3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
            Noodles 8
            3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Mozzarella 500g
            Parmesan 100g
If building ahead of time, add mozza/parm before baking.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56301" image="">1. Warm up chicken stock.

2. In seperate pan melt butter over medium heat, stir until the larger bubbles stop apearing and most of the water is cooked out. Slowly add the flour through sifter or fine mesh strainer and continously stir until flour is fully combined. Cook out roux till it is starting to brown lightly.

3. Slowly add in warm stock, whisking to combine. Once all liquid is added simmer until gravy is thickend to desired viscosity.

4. Finish with herbs and season to taste.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56337" image="">1) Spread pesto evenly over entire area of flatbread.

2) Add artichokes, olives, sundried tomatoes then goat cheese.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Take it off from oven and evenly spread arugula on top and balsamic reduction.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54296" image="">1) Fully cook the seasoned burger patty.

2) Spread chipotle mayo on top and bottom of toasted bun add smashed avocado then iceburge lettuce on bottom.

3) Place burger patty on flat top, top with cheese and let it melt so it&apos;s a bit gooey and place on lettuce. 

4) Add sliced tomato then deep fried jalapenos place top bun on, skewer with bamboo toothpick and garnish with pickle spear. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56457" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1) Puree pickled jalapenos, lime juice and cilantro.

2) Mix well with mayonnaise.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56458" image="">1. Cod takes 10 minutes to deep fry from frozen.

2. Toast bun, spread mayo on both sides. 

3. Place cooked cod piece on bun, top with slaw and pickled red onions.

4. Close and add skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56490" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Mix all marinade ingredients ensuring sugar gets dissolved.

2) Add chicken thighs and marinade 12-24 hours.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56552" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a large rondo over MEDIUM heat, add olive oil, onion, peppers, garlic, thyme and S&amp;P and sweat, stirring occasionally until fragrant.

2. Add tomatoes and simmer.

3. Add eggplant &amp; zucchini and slowly cook until slightly softened. DO NOT LET THESE 2 VEGETABLES TURN TO MUSH!

4. Turn off heat, add chopped parlsey and check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56560" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam edamame &amp; peas until tender (5 minutes).

2. Place edamame, peas, cilantro, garlic, jalapeno, lime juice &amp; fish sauce in blender.

3. Puree, adding water as needed to achieve a smooth consistency.

4. Season to taste with fish sauce..

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56712" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) SOAK LENTILS OVER NIGHT in half the water from the recipe.

2) Cook until tender (1.5 - 2 hours).

3) In a larege rondo over medium heat add oil, onion, garlic, ginger, jalapeno and spices and cook stirring often until onions get slightly brown (to sweeten).

4) Add mung beans with their water plus remaining water from recipe and kidney beans and simmer.

5) Adjust seasoning and stir in cilantro.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56740" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat up tilt skillet over medium/ high heat.

2) Season chicken with salt &amp; pepper, place skin side down in skillet and sear until skin is golden brown. Remove chicken and reserve.

3) In the tilt skillet add olive oil, onion, celery, bell peppers and garlic and sweat until fragrant (3-5 minutes). Remove and reserve.

3) Add tomatoes, capers and dry oregano to the pan. Place seared chicken into sauce and bring to a simmer.

4) Simmer for approximately 30 minutes or until chicken is fully cooked.(Internal temperature of 165F)

5) Remove chicken from the sauce and return vegetables into sauce. Check thickness of sauce and reduce if needed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56460" image="">1)  Grill beef patty to well done (70*C)

2)  Meanwhile, run bun through toaster and spread top and bottom with wasabi mayo.  When patty is nearly cooked through, brush with teriyaki sauce.

3) Place glazed burger on bottom bun, add pickled ginger and sprouts. Add top bun and skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56454" image="">1)  Grill seasoned chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked. 

2) Grill pineapple on both sides.

3) Brush chicken and pineapple on both sides with Teriyaki sauce and quickly glaze on grill. Do not leave on grill too long or sauce will burn. 

4) Place pineapple on chicken, then cheese and melt.

5)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and spread mayo on both sides.

6) Place lettuce, tomato and onion on bottom bun.

7) Place chicken and pineapple on top, close bun and skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Preheat oven to 300F (low fan)

2) Cut roma tomatoes in half LENGTHWISE.

3) Gently toss with remaining ingredients.

4) Place cut side up on a wire rack over a baking sheet, place in oven for  2 hours 30 minutes.

5) Tomatoes should be dried but have some moisture remaining.

6) Do not store more than 2 high so tomatoes do not get crushed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56500" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Cook pasta to al dente. This is very important as the pasta will soak up the sauce and get very soft/ mushy if it is over cooked.

2. Drain pasta well and mix with sauce.

3. Adjust seasoning.

4. Top with mozzarella and parmesan and bake in a 350F oven for ??? minutes ensuring top is golden brown and pasta is hot..

5. Makes 16 portions (2 x 8).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56741" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using Robot Coupe with the shredding blade, shred pear and onion, saving all juices.

2. Mix in remaining ingredients.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57051" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Place bok choy &amp; tofu on top.
4. Finish with cilantro &amp; bean sprouts.

NOTE: sunamono noodles (120g) &amp; broccoli (120g) are served on the side in small bowl

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergens:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46509" image="">Allergens:

NONE 
Icons:

n/a

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:
1. Remove any outer layers of lettuce that are soft and set aside for Shredded Lettuce Prep
2. Cut lettuce head in half Tip to Tail (from the stem to the top of the head.
3. Remove stem with a pairing knife and discard
4. Seperate lettuce into 3x ply thick sections to mimic the dimensions of a burger bun. Each bun will weight aprox. 75g top and 75g bottom for a total of 150g ea.
Most iceberg heads will provide 3 sets of 2 (top and bottom) &quot;Lettuce Buns&quot;
5. Keep all leftover lettuce for Shredded Lettuce Prep

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic and lemongrass and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.  Add yellow curry paste and saute until fragrant, about 1 minute more.
   
2. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  Strain through fine chinois. Add fish sauce and adjust seasoning. 
3. Thicken with corn starch.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56885" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-56927" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Ensure cauliflower rice is completely defrosted.

2) Heat oil over medium heat.

3) Add oil, salt &amp; pepper and shallot and sweat until fragrant.

4) Add defrosted cauliflower rice and saute until cauliflower is warmed through.

5) Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56637" image="">1. Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in eggnog mixture and put on griddle.  Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56451" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Corn Flake French Toast.jpg">1. Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg mixture then in corn flakes and put on griddle.  Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.

4. NOTE: corn flakes need to be pulsed so they are small enough to stick evenly to the bread but retain some texture</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57154" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Whisk all ingredients together ensuring sugar is dissolved. Warm ever so slightly if needed to melt sugar.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57157" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

Preheat deep fryer to 350F

1. Slice sweet potato width wise into 1/2 - 1 cm thick slices.

2. Toss evenly in flour, then liquid egg then panko and reserve on full sized sheet pans. 

3. Working in batches deep fry slices 1-2 minutes until sweet potatoes are golden brown and just cooked through.

4. Remove from fryer, shake off excess oil, place on wire rack and season immediately so the salt will stick to the sweet potatoes.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Ensure fish is fully defrosted.

2. Cook fish in hotel pans with green curry sauce and hot hold for service.

3. Garnish with drizzle of coconut milk, cilantro and Thaii basil.


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51250" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2. Cut uniform sized cubes
3.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56700" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine flour, spices and wisk together.

2. Add soy milk and stock, wisk together to create batter.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Slice eggplant 1/2 inch thick, trim the root ends
3. Place in a colander and spinkle with salt 
4. Let sit for 1 hour
5. Rinse the salt with cold water
6. Pad dry 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57384" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add oil to saute pan over medium heat. Add sliced shallots and cook until softened (1 minute) 

2. Add garlic and cook until fragrant (30-60 secs).

3. Add broth and capers and reduce by 1/2. 

4. Thicken with corn starch slurry.

5. Remove from heat, whisk in cold butter and chopped parsley.

6. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53126" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Warm bechamel over medium heat, stirring often to ensure sauce doesn&apos;t scald on the bottom of the pot.

2. Have shredded cheese ready and add off the heat while stirring to melt.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fill kettle with ROOM TEMPERATURE water. Do Not tutnr the kettle on.
2. Place the noodles into the water fully submerging the noodles. Mix the noodles around until they have loosened up and move freely and un-forzen
3. Noodles should be firm but not crispy.
4. Remove from kettle and let drain.
5. Lightly oil the noddles and store them labeled and rotated correctly.
6. Noodles are to be cook &quot;a-la-minute&quot; on the station as needed 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56540" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

THIS DISH IS SERVED COLD.

1. Working in small batches squeeze out as much water as possible and lay out on sheet pans to dry.

2. Mix dry spinach with remaning ingredients. 

3. Serve and label/ rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50803" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Char jalapenos on the grill until cooked.

3. Clean and de-seed the jalapenos.

4. Blitz jalapeno, lemon juice, salt/pepper in vitamix.

5. Mix honey, jalapeno mixture and mayo.

6. Taste and adjust as needed

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-6888" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54583" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE


Grill the chicken breast with some of the BBQ rub spice and glaze with BBQ sauce when it is nearly done.

Toast the bun and sauce the top bun, put the caramelized onions on the bottom bun. 

Place the BBQ chicken breast on the bottom bun and top it with the lettuce and tomato. 

Place the lid on the bun and serve the pickle on the side.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50543" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut tomato in half
2.Toss in all the remaning ingredients
3.Drain the excess liquid

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: Muffaleta

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out all ingredients.

2. In a Robot Coupe add all ingredents and pulse until combined and coarse/slightly chunky.

3. DO NOT PUREE UNTILL SMOOTH this should be a slightly chunky spread with evident pieces of olive and such.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50662" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-19208" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut to size
3.place in container, label and refridgerate 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44570" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
Amanda

Allergens: 
Method:

*NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp should reach 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41321" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: EGG

Method:

1. Prepare all Mise En Place items that are dry, and combine. Sift together if you have time.

2. Add Egg, and 50% of the water, and mix with a whisk. 

3. Then, add the vinegar, and continue mixing. A chemical reaction will occur at this point between the vinegar and baking soda. 

4.If necessary, add the remaining water. Otherwise, do not, and let the mixture be by itself. It should be roughly the consistency of soft serve ice cream.

NOTE: This batter should be stored in the freezable containers in the Vegetable Containers, meant for squeeze bottles and other things that stand at room temperature.

[This is where I would normally write &quot;Label/Date/Store!&quot;, but since this is made several times per day, and never stored overnight - the container NOTE was written instead.]

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53848" image="">1. Combine Romaine and dressing in mixing bowl 

2. Garnish top with croutons and parm.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Thick cut the cabbage and apples.

2. Sautee the onions and garlic first, add the cabbage, apples, vinegar, salt and pepper. Place a lid on the pot and cook out for 20 minutes.

3. Check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44527" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Clean, prepare and chop the herbs as needed. 

Use any combination (or even just a single herb) in a quanitity adding up to 8 grams total weight. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44377" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57191" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. discard unsavoury outer leaves

2.Remove core and discard

3. Cut and trim lettuce as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-15354" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54456" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Toast cut side of bun.

2. Sauce the bun with tartar sauce and layer the sandwich with fried prawns, shredded iceberg, tomato slices and pickle slices. 

Portioning:
90 g prawn

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-6989" image="">1. Heat up oil in large pot or tilt skillet, add onion and cook till soft and transparent, add garlic and oregano cook for 5 minutes, add in ground beef and break up in to small pieces as it cooks. Cook beef until almost all water is gone and meat is small brown crispy pieces.

2. Remove from and stir tomato sauce in to the cooked beef. Once combined, put in to apropriate container and cool fully.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together EXCEPT green onions.

2. Add sliced green onions last.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53995" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss mushrooms with salt and pepper and oil. 

Roast on a parchment lined sheet pan in a hot oven until the water from the mushrooms cooks away and the mushrooms are browned and flavorful</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: DAIRY
Method:

1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes. 

4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46824" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing purposes only. 

Please make all of the associated sub recipes as indicated in those recipes. 

Any blend of the listed vegetables will suffice, or just one vegetable. 

The important part is that 180g/ 6oz (by weight) of vegetables are provided. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55167" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until lightly browned and hot throughout. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53993" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss diced Zucchini with oil and salt and pepper and roast on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned and hot throughout.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46864" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Be sure to make shred from other Iceberg lettuce preps
3. evenly slice lettuce 3 mm thick
4. Cover with wet brown paper towel to stop oxidization   

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and stirring.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56631" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Use a vitamix to make this sauce. It is essential that you use a blender strong enough to puree the cashews in the sauce so it is not grainy.  If you do not have a vitamix, pre soak the cashews in hot water for a minimum of 1 hr before making the sauce. 
2. Place all ingredients in the vitamix, puree until smooth

3. Adjust consistency with water until desired consistencty is reached.

4. Adjust seasoning - acid (tamarind), heat(sambal), sweet(sugar), salt(veg fish sauce) to desired taste.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47418" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine and mix.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47422" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Saute the red peppers and onions to sweeten and soften them up

Assemble in the indicated proportions.

Cook the assembled quesdaillas.

Serve salsa and sour cream on the side.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47424" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Saute the red peppers and onions to sweeten and soften them up

Assemble in the indicated proportions.

grill or bake the assembled quesdaillas 

Serve salsa and sour cream on the side</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26628" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix, heat to a boil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51210" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-42353" image="">
Prep:

- Quarter Corn Tortillas. 2.5 Packages of Corn Tortillas will yield 2 Deep Hotel pans full of Corn Chips.

- Using Paper Towel, create a large pan or bowl for draining the excess oil off of the Tortilla Chips, after they&apos;ve come out of the Deep Fryer.

- At 350 Degrees (F) in the Deep Fryer, fry NO MORE THAN HALF OF A STACK OF CORN TORTILLAS (QUARTERED) at a time.

- Using a Spider, or Long Tongs - KEEP TORTILLAS MOVING AT ALL TIMES. 

- Depending on how dark the Deep Fryer oil is, fry the Tortilla Chips until they are brown (keeping in mind that they will cook for a little while longer once they&apos;ve been taken out of the fryer. 

- As soon as the chips are out drying, salt lightly using the Windsor coarse grain salt. The salt will only stick during this stage of production - be sure to catch it!

Label/Date/Store

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Saute the onions and pureed lemon grass until translucent, add ginger and garlic and cook out for another 5 minutes. Add sugar and cook for another 5 minutes.

3. Add Green Curry Paste and cook out for another 5 minutes to develop flavour.

4. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer, add lime leaves and season.

5. Thicken with slury, thicken so that sauce coats the back of a spoon and sticks.

6. Add lime juice just before you take it off the heat.

7. Throw in the thai basil and cilantro and blend in the sauce to give it it&apos;s green color.******

****** If you are making the sauce for the next day, DO NOT add the cilantro/thai basil as it will go brown and discolor.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48359" image="">Allergen:

egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten

Icon:

vegetarian

Method:

Cook Eggs, Hollandaise, 

Place English muffins on plate, top with sauteed spinach feta, add an egg and top with hollandaise.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut cauliflower into 1&quot; flourettes.

2. Toss in batter until completly coated.

3. Toss in 3/4 of panko. Take remaining 1/4 of the panko and bltz in robocoup until fine ( about 5 min).

4. Toss the wings in the fine blitzed panko and spread out on a sheet pan lined with parchment.

5. Bake in 350f oven for 20 min, remove from heat, stir, bake for an additional 15 min or until just golden.

6. Hold hot for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51217" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Prep all of the prep recipes in advance.

Layer all of  the ingredients in a tortilla wrap in the proportions indicated.

Wrap up tightly.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot bring the water to a boil. Add the rice, lentils, bayleaf and 1/2 the salt. Bring back to a boil, turn heat down to medium and lid, leaving lid slightly ajar.
Simmer for 30-35 minutes or until the rice and lentils are tender. Drain, reserving at least 1 1/4 C (281g) of cooking liquid (it will be used later to make the sauce). Place the rice and lentils back in their cooking pot, lid and set aside off heat.

2. *A note about the veggies. Be sure they&apos;re diced small, otherwise they&apos;ll be crunchy-ish at the end of cooking. We&apos;re looking for them to be soft.

3. In a large Rondeau add the oil and heat until shimmering.  Add the bell pepper, onion and celery. Turn the heat to low. Stir. Cook, stirring occassionally for about 12-15 minutes. The veggies are done when the they&apos;re tender/soft and brown bits (fond – the brown bits that stick to the bottom of the pan) are just starting to appear in the pan. 

4. To the pan of veggies, add the tomato paste, garlic, Cajun or Creole seasoning and remaining 1/2  salt. Stir to coa the veggies. Pour in 3/4 C (180g) of the reserved cooking liquid from the lentils and rice. Stir.

5. To the pan, add the drained kidney beans. Stir. Heat should be on medium-low to low. Lid the pan and gently cook the beans through for about 8-10 minutes. Check on the beans a few times while cooking and If needed, add just a bit more cooking liquid from the reserved liquid. Your beans should be saucy, and moist, not dry.

6. Turn the heat to low and transfer the drained rice and lentils to the bean mixture. Add Worcestershire sauce. Add the lemon juice and to taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary;  then gently fold all the ingredients together.
If needed, to loosen the mixture or if it starts to get too dry, add a splash of cooking liquid - you&apos;ll probably not use it all - thats okay. Taste for salt. Lid. Leave on low heat for 3-5 minutes just to warm though, checking to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking - the pan should be almost dry, with a moist (but not sticky) rice mixture.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano until desired texture achived (course or fine)

3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Small dice jalapenos and tomatoes. Mince cilantro.

2. In a bowl combine all ingredents. Mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. Check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41574" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. PRE-SOAK Beans overnight!
   - 2 X 20L CAMBRO Containers
   - HALF of the Beans in Each
   - Filled with 12L of Water Each

2. Drain beans from their hydration liquid. Your cooking water should be different from your soaking water.

3. Using the small steam kettle, cook beans slowly in 20 extra liters of water. They should be good to start at 250F.

4. Cook the beans until they are soft, but not decomposing. During the cooking process it is important to skim off the foamy protein that will accumulate at the surface of the cooking beans&apos; water - this, if unchecked, will lead to a poor bitter taste and a lesser shelf life for the beans themselves.

5. While the beans are cooking, saute your onions in oil, until dark brown. Caramelize them as far as they will go, and then add cumin and garlic. Saute cumin and garlic for 5 minutes, and then take off heat.

6. Turn off steam kettle when the beans are cooked, and let beans sit. Take 4L of the cooking water, and set aside.

7. Drain beans, and then transfer them into a neutral container greater than 40L in volume. Get the large Immersion Blender.

8. Add the onion mixture with the garlic and cumin, as well as half of the salt, and half of the brown sugar. The remaining halves - set aside, and use to SEASON TO TASTE. 

9. With the Immersion Blender, blend about 4L of the bean mixture into a puree - and then add back into the rest of the beans, and mix. Add reserve liquid from the cooking, until you get - not a soup - beans with a puree of more beans.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44592" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather ingredients
2. Bake on tray 190C 375F 20 minutes or till done
3. Strain fat then crumble
4. Place in container once cold, label and fridge 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Baking sheet collandier container 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Carrots on a 45 angle to ressemble a whistle
3. Steam for 4 min

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44024" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place wrap on plate and put salad inside.

2. Add hot chorizo.

3. Eggs and sauce.

4. Wrap and serve.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56449" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34892" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Scale out ingredients.

2. In a sauce pot combine water and buuter and bring to a simmer, Add powder and stir for a minute.

3. Place in container and hold for service in a WARM place.
 
Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:scale pot whisk bowl container</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55155" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
2. Build sandwich to spec.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients.
2. Put egg into a perforated pan.
3. Cook in steamer for 9-10 min.
4. Plunge eggs in a ice bath right away.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: perfforated hotel pan, ice bath

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41314" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40595" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather all Ingredients and tools.

2. Combine all ingredients in a mixing bowl.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: mixing bowl, rubber spatula, whisk, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55419" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
2. Sweat garlic, shallot, lemon grass in oil.
3. Add curry paste and cook until encorperated.
4. Add coconut milk and simmer for 15 minutes.
5. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50289" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.Gather All Ingredients and Tools

2.Toss all in a bowl and lay flat on roasting pan

3.Roast in convection @325F fro 12-15 min

*cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat well
3.Bake on sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57052" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Place bok choy &amp; tofu on top.
4. Finish with cilantro &amp; bean sprouts.

NOTE: sunamono noodles (120g) &amp; broccoli (120g) are served on the side in small bowl

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergens:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51133" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients
2. Be sure that bacon bits are cut ahead of time, and eggs are half&apos;d ahead of time
3.  

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50301" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
Slanted bowl</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.HEAT FLAT TOP AND HAVE FLAT SPATULA AND RESTING TRAY READY
2.LIGHTLY OIL FLATOP
3.CRACK EGG ONTO FLAT TOP
4.SEASON
5.COOK UNTIL WHITES FULLY CONGEALED 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:1 egg

Utensils needed:

PROCESS:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9742" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Clean  and cut leeks
2. Toss in oil and salt + pepper
3. Charr leeks on grill
4. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9767" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-6975" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash rice
3.put all ingredients into pan
4.Steam 40 minutes or till done
5. Serve or put on tray to cook. then place in container,label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50530" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using a mandoline or meat slicer make long wide ribbons of cucumber without using the middle.

2. Mix with the rest of the ingredients.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44510" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45203" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Place bok choy &amp; salmon on top.
4. Finish with cilantro &amp; bean sprouts.


Portioning:
100 g salmon

Utensils needed:

Allergens:
Fish(Salmon)
sulphites</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7420" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
SALAD BAR

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  cut brocco to uniform sized floretes
2. save stems for other recipes
3.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine everything and mix thoroughly.
2. Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50539" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Start with egg yolk and lemon, blend for 30 seconds and then start slowly adding oil.
2. Add oil faster as dressing emulsifies.
3. Thin out with water as needed.
4. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29128" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition) Sulphites
Method:
1. Sweat off ginger, garlic, shallots, lemongrass, turmeric &amp; chilies. 

2. Stir often until fragrant (3-5 minutes)

3. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer stirring occasionally.

4. Reduce slightly and adjust seasoning.

Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


ALLERGEN
SULPHITE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Spread the brocoll evenlly on perforated pans
3. Steam untill aldente (4 min)

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Steamer, perforated hotel pans 2&quot;
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50581" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50250" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Heat up oil in tilt skillet
3. Sautee carrot untill color start to appears
4. Add honey and caramelized untill golden
5. Finish with lemon juice and parsley

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 100g
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9863" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Tip/tail the leeks save the green tips for other preps
2. Soak in cold water to rinse off dirt
3. cut to desired shape
4. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55163" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Steam hot dogs in perferated hotel pan inside a non perforated hotel pan in the Rational untill fully cooked (5-7 minutes) dogs should not split (overcooked)

3. Building your dog!

-Put steamed dog on the grill to heat up (and get some awesome grill flavour) 
-In an untoasted bun spread your smashed avocado
-Top avocado with shredded lettuce
-Place grilled dog on top of lettuce base
-Garnish with crumbled bacon and crumbled blue cheese.

SERVE!


HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56856" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Place a bowl ontop of a plate, scoop mash into bowl 
2. Top mash with portion of chicken pot pie filler
3. Top with pie shell
4. serve requested side on the plate beside the bowl
Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43922" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Garnish with tofu &amp; bok choy.
4. Finish with cilantro.


Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergens:
soy, sulphites, sesame, 

Icons:
made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44753" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather all Ingredients and tools.

2. Toss the broccoli with the ginger dip.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: mixing bowl, rubber spatula
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44585" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny\

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry limes
2.Slice into 8 wedges end to end each slive weighting approc 20-25 grams
3.Place in insert lable and place in fridge for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:1 piece per order

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26019" image="">1. Combine well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53000" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU** Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cut each lemongrass stalks overly dry parts off and compost
2. using theback of a nife pound the grass to bruise it and be careful to seperate any over loose peices so they done fall into the liquid
3. Add stalk to liquid to be removed after cooking 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8202" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.mix together and label store with rest of spices

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44793" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Method:
1.Combine ingredents up to 3 days in advance.
-store, label and rotate

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim all excess and cut the cauliflower in small     florettes
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9741" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and clean ingredients.
2.Slice
3.Lable and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23151" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
ALL SALES OFF OF SALAD BAR

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. MIX ALL LARGE PREP BATCHES AND STORE IN WALK IN FOR REPLENTISHING BAR


Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43674" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Combine all ingredients and mix well

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:mixing bowl, rubber spatula, insert

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47149" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44499" image="">Allergen:

wheat, egg, gluten

Icon:

vegetarian</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56489" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Make pancakes.

2. Top w compote then chantilly.

3. Serve.


Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57405" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54875" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of crispy fries in bowl and top with cheese.

2. Pour portion of gravy over top of cheese and fries.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57461" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Place bok choy &amp; salmon on top.
4. Finish with cilantro &amp; bean sprouts.

NOTE: sunamono noodles (120g) &amp; broccoli (120g) are served on the side in small bowl
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57279" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot bring the water to a boil. Add the rice, lentils, bayleaf and 1/2 the salt. Bring back to a boil, turn heat down to medium and lid, leaving lid slightly ajar.
Simmer for 30-35 minutes or until the rice and lentils are tender. Drain, reserving at least 1 1/4 C (281g) of cooking liquid (it will be used later to make the sauce). Place the rice and lentils back in their cooking pot, lid and set aside off heat.

2. *A note about the veggies. Be sure they&apos;re diced small, otherwise they&apos;ll be crunchy-ish at the end of cooking. We&apos;re looking for them to be soft.

3. In a large Rondeau add the oil and heat until shimmering.  Add the bell pepper, onion and celery. Turn the heat to low. Stir. Cook, stirring occassionally for about 12-15 minutes. The veggies are done when the they&apos;re tender/soft and brown bits (fond – the brown bits that stick to the bottom of the pan) are just starting to appear in the pan. 

4. To the pan of veggies, add the tomato paste, garlic, Cajun or Creole seasoning and remaining 1/2  salt. Stir to coa the veggies. Pour in 3/4 C (180g) of the reserved cooking liquid from the lentils and rice. Stir.

5. To the pan, add the drained kidney beans. Stir. Heat should be on medium-low to low. Lid the pan and gently cook the beans through for about 8-10 minutes. Check on the beans a few times while cooking and If needed, add just a bit more cooking liquid from the reserved liquid. Your beans should be saucy, and moist, not dry.

6. Turn the heat to low and transfer the drained rice and lentils to the bean mixture. Add Worcestershire sauce. Add the lemon juice and to taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary;  then gently fold all the ingredients together.
If needed, to loosen the mixture or if it starts to get too dry, add a splash of cooking liquid - you&apos;ll probably not use it all - thats okay. Taste for salt. Lid. Leave on low heat for 3-5 minutes just to warm though, checking to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking - the pan should be almost dry, with a moist (but not sticky) rice mixture.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9748" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Tacos
Bowls

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.slice shallot and dredge in potato starch mix
3.Shake off excess in a strainer
4.Fry once at 310 until bubbles stop and shallot float
5. remove from and let cool on a resting rack turning the fryer up to 350 when they are out
6. whenthey are cool, re-fry at 350 until golden brown
7.place on paper towel to absorb excess oil
8.place in container on a service towel, label and use for TWO DAYS ONLY 

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44749" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Marinade the blocks of tofu in ponzu sauce, no more then 24 hours.
2. Remove marinated tofu from ponzu and cube into 24 peices.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50764" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED
STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather ingredients
2.skin salmon and portion 100g 3oz
3.Place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:100g 3oz

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20368" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. gather ingredients
2. cut Chard into strips
3. wash and dry
4. place in contain label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56866" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Plate noodle in a pile in bowl.
2. Pour broth and lime juice over noodles.
3. Place bok choy &amp; salmon on top.
4. Finish with cilantro &amp; bean sprouts.

NOTE: sunamono noodles (120g) &amp; broccoli (120g) are served on the side in small bowl


Portioning:
100g salmon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57362" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny


this product is a ratio


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients in a large pot.

2. Bring to a simmer and thicken with a corn starch slurry

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cover ribs completely in marinade in a suitable insert.

2.Adjitate the meat to ensure the liquid contcts all surfaces of the ribs while still not breaking the rib bones out of the meat.

3.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58270" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Place greens, cabbage, beans, peppers, charred corn and tomatoes in mixing bowl.

2) Add dressing and GENTLY toss to combine ensuring all ingredients are coated in dressing.

3) Plate greens leaving some of the vegetables to garnish top of salad.

4) Finish top of salad with radish slices, tortilla strips, pumpkin seeds and feta.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-47541" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED
STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.blend together and use
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32124" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:
BATCH| guacamole AR

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Serve side guacamole in a ramekin to ensure it is clearly seen by sales attendants at the till


Portioning:
45 G


Utensils needed:
BLACK ICE CREAM SCOOP
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56857" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Place a bowl ontop of a plate, scoop mash into bowl 
2. Top mash with portion of chicken pot pie filler
3. Top with pie shell
4. serve requested side on the plate beside the bowl

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58362" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Smash black peppercorns slightly.  

2)  Combine water, crushed black pepeprcorns, bay leaf, sugar, garlic cloves, onion, rosemary, thyme, salt and lemon (make sure to give the lemons a good squeeze before throwing in the mix)

3)  Bring brine to a boil and stir to ensure that salt and sugar are dissolved.  Put mixture in blast chiller to cool.

4)  When brine has cooled COMPLETELY, add turkey breast.  Ensure breasts stay in brine by weighing them down with a tray from the servery.  

5)  Allow breast to brine for 6 hours.

6)  Roast in 325*F oven until browned and probe thermometer reaches 70*C (158*F).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58368" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Simmer all ingredients in a pot for 12-15 minuites and until cranberries start to pop.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58370" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a large rondo heat olive oil over medium heat. Add onion and celery and sweat until fragrant stirring often (5-7 minutes).

2. Add chopped sage, mushrooms and salt and pepper and continue cooking until mushrooms have released most of their moisture. Transfer to a large bowl.

3. Add to bowl the diced bread, walnuts, mixed eggs and chicken stock. You may not need all the stock.

4. Cook a small piece to check for seasoning and adjust if needed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.steam beets in steamer till soft
3.peel under water once cool enough
4.cut into pieces and toss with remaining ingredients
5. spread on roasting pan
6. Roast 200C/400F 15 minute or till done
7.Hot hold in insert for service covered
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g

Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
serving dish

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46869" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Neatly dice the Shallots in Brunoise size
2.Save the trimming for stock
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, storage container

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58377" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Method:

1. Cut salmon to request portion size
2. Lightly oil and season. There is ONLY S&amp;P in the recipe: be sure to check if your salmon needs requir different seasoning
3. place in proper cooking vessel lined with parchment 
4. cook to desired doneness
5. If salmon is not for imediate use:cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:


Utensils needed:

Allergens:
Fish(Salmon)
sulphites

Icons:
oceanwise</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53794" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 425F

2. Toss all veg well with olive oil, herbs and seasoning and spread in a single layer on full sized sheet pans.

3. Roast until just cooked and slightly caramalized.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58386" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Portion mash onto plate.
2. Top with turkey.
3. Garnish with sauces.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58388" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. portion mash onto plate first
tops with turkey and gravy
2. add additional sides reuqested
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58389" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Portion mash onto plate first
2. Top with turkey and gravy
3. Add additional sides requested.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56491" image="">1. Spread mayo on both sides of baguette.

2. Place cooked chicken, cucumber, pickled veg, sliced jalepenos then cilanrto (in that order).

PLEASE ENSURE JALAPENOS ARE VERY THINLY SLICED.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58450" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Take chicken out of marinade and lay it in a single layer on parchemnt lined baking sheets.

2. Place in a 375F oven and cook until internal temperature reaches 165F

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44904" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. In Rondo or tilt skillet over medium high heat add oil, onions, garlic and red peppers. Saute to bring out flavour. 

2. Add salt, oregano, tomatoes and tomato juice and bring to a simmer for 10 mins.

3. Add zucchini and eggplant and simmer for just a coupler more minutes as you want some texture left in these vegetables (especially if you are reheating).

4. Turn off heat, add peas, parsley and adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56860" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. scoop mash portion onto bowl
2. top with ratatoulle and a puff pastry lid
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56695" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58757" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
Amanda

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp should reach 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
Amanda

Allergens: 
Method:

*NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp should reach 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57808" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
Amanda

Allergens: 
Method:

*NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp should reach 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56115" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
Amanda

Allergens: 
Method:

*NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp should reach 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Slice strawberries when they are partially frozen(rough is fine) and place in suitable sized pot.

2. Add remaining ingredients except slurry. Bring to a boil.

3. Add slurry to thicken and remove from heat.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38629" image="">PLEASE NOTE:

For portion sizes:

Because we offer 3 choices of sides on a +2 menu I have averaged them out.

These are the full sized portion weights:

Seasonal Veg x 140 g
Creamed Corn x 170 g
Potato Salad x 150 g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26471" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9738" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44506" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Halve the avocado and carefully remove the pit
3.  Slice into desired sizes
4. Toss in lemon juice to prevent oxydation

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 1 portion is 1/4 avocado

Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, bowl insert, mesuring cups
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52999" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU** Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.cut bacon into 4 cmx 2cm x 2cm strips
2. Heat pot to medium heat and add bacon
3. Stir to avoid burning while letting pieces fully render out 
4. Drain in chinoiseand cool reserving the fast
5. label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, lemongrass and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

2. Add mushrooms and rice, sautee 1 minute

3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

4. Sfter 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. 

5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48357" image="">Allergen:

egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten, fish (salmon)

Icon:

oceanwise

Method:

Cook Eggs, Hollandaise, 

Place English muffins on plate, top with smoked salmon, add an egg and top with hollandaise.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1)  Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray.  Place egg in egg poacher cup.  Steam for 8 minutes until cooked.

Allergens:

Soy, Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45153" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Start with rice

2. Sides

3. Chicken x 2 thighs

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9710" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-9712" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients
2. Chopped to desired size
3.  Store in appropriate container, label and fridge

Portioning:

Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33555" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Chop pickles and set aside pickle juice.
2.Chop parsely very fine.
3. Mix all ingredients in mixer and fully incorperate.
4. Season with lemon, L&amp;P sauce, salt and pepper to taste
5. Store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Cutting board bowl whisk scale container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60537" image="">
Combine salad greens with ranch dressing.  Plate into small side salad bowl.

Top with sliced cherry tomato, cucumber, egg, avocado slices, cheese,(no bacon or ham!) on top of greens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47361" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients EXCEPT oil in a cambro.

2. Blend with immersion blender, then slowly drizzle in oil to form an emulsion.

3. Taste for seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56796" image="">PREP RECIPE

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.

label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place beets in a food processor, pulse 2-3 times.  DO NOT puree, there needs to be texture for the patties to hold together.

2. Fine dice onion.

3. Transfer beets to a large bowl, add other ingredients and stir to combine.  If texture is too mushy, add more bread crumbs until desired consistancy. NOTE the bread crumbs and quinoa will slowly absorb excess moisture over time.

4. Scale and shape burgers and place them on a parchment lined baking sheet. 

5. Bake patties in oven for 15 min, flip over and bake for a further 15 min. Hold for service OR

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:
patty portion weight 160 grams

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. 
3. 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46545" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2. butterfly breasts if needed
3.lay out on baking sheet
4.Sprinkle cajun seasoning evenly
5.bake in oven 15 minutes or till done
6.cool and place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All ingredients
2. Chopped capers to desire size
3.  Store in container

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting Board, knife, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28373" image="">THIS IS A RATIO ONLY NOT A RECIPE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-59716" image="">PLEASE NOTE:

For portion sizes:

Because we offer 3 choices of sides on a +2 menu I have averaged them out.

These are the full sized portion weights:

Seasonal Veg x 120 g
Creamed Corn x 120 g
Potato Salad x 140 g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61501" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Puree pepperoncini.

2. Mix well with other ingredients.

 label and store it, rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61508" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Blanch corn in boiling salted water for 7 minutes. Remove and drain well.

2. On a hot grill chgar corn on all sides and season with salt &amp; pepper.

3. For service rub entire cob of corn with mayo, sprinkle with ancho chili, feta and cilantro.

4. Serve with a lime wedge (1/6th of a lime) on the side.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57710" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-57814" image="">Guac, Queso &amp; chips or grilled corn are choice for +1
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61678" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

In advance slice tofu into 8 slices and press between hotel pans with a weight to extract excess moisture.

1. In a Robot Coupe pulse peppers, tomatoes, onion, water, chipoles (with adobo sauce), garlic, red wine vinegar, ancho powder, cumin, oregano &amp; salt &amp; pepper.

2. Pulse leaving small chunks. Do NOT liquify. Taste for seasoning.

3. On flattop over medium high heat sear tofu slices until golden brown.

4. Roughly chop tofu and place in an insert with marinade. Cover and leave overnight in refrigerator.

5. For service warm marinade and tofu breaking it into small pieces adding extra water if needed.

6. Taste for seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61685" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Place coconut oil in a rondo over medium heat.
2. Once warm add curry paste and sweat until fragrant, stirring so paste does not burn (3-4 minutes). You want to draw out as much flavour as possible in this step.
3. Add coconut milk, lime leaves (no stems) and bring to a simmer.
4. Simmer until desired consistency is reached.
5. Remove from heat, add fish sauce &amp; palm sugar and adjust seasoning. Remove lime leaves.
6. Curry should be spicy/ sweet/ salty &amp; slighty sour.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61687" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61742" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto.

2) Evenly lay shrimp, tomatoes and parmesan. Sprinkle chili flakes.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Cut into 4 even pieces, garnish with arugula, squeeze fresh lemon and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61756" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. All veg should be cut in the same size (3/4&quot; dice)

2. Roast each veg seperate tossed in olive oil, caraway and s&amp;p in a 425F oven until tender and slightly caramalized.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61779" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

2) Evenly lay cooked mushrooms over pesto.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Once cooked take out from oven.

5) Lay arugula over.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62016" image="">completely thaw block of frozen spinach

in small batches, squeeze out excess water from spinach

place squeezed spinach in perforated pan or basket strainer to allow any excess water to drip away

place in appropriate container 

label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57712" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-61753" image="">Dirty rice portion is 130g

Okra portion is 120g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61754" image="">Dirty rice portion is 130g

Coleslaw portion is 120g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58400" image="">Dirty rice portion is 130g

Okra portion is 120g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58401" image="">Dirty rice portion is 130g

Coleslaw portion is 120g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41093" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-61625" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-33872" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-57811" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Fill 3 whole leaves of iceburg lettuce with Soba noodles, tofu, spinach, pickled carrots. 
2. Drizzle cashew sauce over.
3. Garnish with cilantro, mint and roasted cashews.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-63555" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Roast tomatoes in 450F oven until blistered.
2. Puree with jalapenos.
3. Add remaining ingredients and adjust seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55818" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using ES 3 1/8&quot; blade on the robot coupe thinly slice cabbage.
2. Using the R2 Robot Coupe julienne the carrots.
3. Cut green onions on a bias/ angle and mix all veg together.
4. Right before service mix with dressing.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57567" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-64640" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1. Preheat oven to 400f. Trim bottom, and slice in half, sprouts.

2. Combine oil, salt and pepper, garlic and cheese.

3. Coat the sprouts with the oil/cheese mixture. Add them to a roasting tray, don&apos;t over crowd, and make sure most are cut side down for nice even cook.

4. Roast for 20-25 minutes, until they are a nice dark golden brown. Serve.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64456" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-64478" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26713" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-64514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: Gluten, Dairy
Method:

1.Prepair muffin tray&apos;s with paper liners

2. Cut bread into cubes (1&quot; x1&quot;) set aside in a bowl

3. In a seperate bowl whisk together eggs, milk, cream, sugar and vanilla to make a custard.

4. Pour custard over bread cubes.

5. Add roasted pumpkin seeds and mix into the bread and custard. Mix to evenly incorporate.

6.  Let soak for 2 to 24 hours, ocasionally mixing to ensure bread is being evenly soaked.

7. Preheat oven to 350F. Place liners in muffin tray, and put 180g of bread pudding in each cup. Bake until pudding is set in the centre. Aprox 30-45 minutes. Serve warm. 

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64515" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Use only the thick fat from coconut milk can discard the water.
2. Add all ingredients to vitamix on medium-high until smooth.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64516" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pre-heat deep fryer to 400F.

2. Peel and cut potatoes in to 5cm pieces as even as possible.

3. Bring a large pot of water to a rappid boil, and add potatoes. Boil for 5-10 minutes, until outside is tender, but inside is still hard.

4. Once potatoes are cooked to desired consitancy, drain well. Place potatoes back in to empty pot, add the potato starch, and shake up and stir till outside becomes pasty.

5. Add potatoes to deep fryer for 10 minutes, or until dark golden brown and cooked through.

6. Dump cooked potatoes in big bowl and toss with chopped rosemary, salt and pepper. Serve.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64639" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1. Combine salt/pepper, herbs and mustard in to a paste.

2. Preheat oven to 375f. Trim extra fat from pork loin, and brush on mustard/herb paste.

3. Place pork loin in roasting pan and cook, uncovered, in oven for 45-50 minutes, until internal temperature reaches 140f in center. Might take more or less time depending on size.

4. Turn oven up to 500f  for 5-10 minutes, to brown the outside and internal temprature reaches 145f. 

5. Cover pork and let it rest for 20 minutes, Slice in to 140g pieces and keep hot for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64678" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1. Cut tofu in to 4 even square 90g slabs, then cut those in half diagionaly corner to corner. Each block should get you 8 triangles total.

2. Pat dry and coat in corn starch. Deep fry till golden brown and crispy.

3. Sprinkle with a little salt as soon as it comes out of the fryer. Hold hot for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64684" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

This sauce is served along side the prep item:
POP|Pork loin|Herb Crust

1. Gather and mesure out all ingredients while pork is in the oven. Seperate butter in to two halves.

2. Pour the fat out of the pan you cooked your roasts in, but don’t clean it. Place the pan back on the heat with half the butter and the shallots and sizzle for 2 mins to soften. Stir in the flour and cook to a sandy paste, then splash in the vinegar and simmer for a moment. Pour in the wine and stir, scraping any sticky bits off the bottom of the pan. Bring to the boil and bubble for a minute, then whisk in the mustard and then the stock.

3. Boil the sauce down to half, about 4L, in total, then taste and season. Whisk in the remaining butter and the parsley, plus any resting juices from the roast. Keep hot for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64689" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-64692" image="">1. If cooled down place in steamer for 30 seconds.

2. Server the bread pudding while still warm, in the wrapper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64718" image="">1. Serve pork loin, hot, with 2oz of sauce drapped over it. garnish with parsly.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64719" image="">1. Serve with two warm crispy tofu wedges, singled on plate, scoup cold pumpkin mouse on top, sprinkle with roasted pumpkin seeds, and a dusting of cinnoman.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64879" image="">1. Combine all ingredients, if making ahead lable and store in cooler.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61621" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. gather all ingredients, and line up all the 2&quot; hotelpans you need for the number of lasagna you&apos;re making.

2. Combine ricotta and eggs and mix well.

3. build layers in this order

Bottom layer: Meat sauce 750ml
                     Noodles 8
                     Ricotta/egg mixture 500ml
                     Noodles 8
                     Meat sauce 750ml
                     Cheese sauce 500ml
                     noodle 8
                     Meat sauce 750ml
                     Cheese sauce 500ml
Top with:        mozza 500g and parm 100g
If prepairing ahead of time, leave off mozza/parm topper till you&apos;re baking them.

4. Bake at 300f for 45 minutes. Ensure noodles are cooked and internal temperature reaches 160f
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64945" image=""/>
</Recipes>
