<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9710" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-9712" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. 
3. 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

4) Season with salt &amp; pepper. 

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26091" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26169" image="">1. Heat butter chicken in steamer until hot throughout
2. Transfer to serving vessel to hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26175" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Roughly crush cloves.  Add all ingredients in bowl and mix wel

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26181" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Pre heat rationale oven to 250F

2) Remove excess fat from brisket, score fatty side. Rub brisket in Berbere rub.  Set aside.  Brisket can be rubbed up to two days before.

3) Place brisket and braising liquid in deep 6&quot; hotel pan, cover with parchment and then cover insert with aluminum foil.  Fold aluminum foil back about half way so you can see meat and braising liquid.  

4)  Place insert over burners or on french top and bring to a boil.  

5) Place in rationale oven and cook for 12 hours or until tender.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26182" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Remove silver skin from ribs as necessary. Rub generously with house rub at least 2 hours in advance

2. Pre heat oven to 275F on combination setting. Arrange rubbed pork ribs on baking sheets without oiling. Cover with aluminum foil and roast for about 2-3 hours or until tender and cooked through

3. Finish ribs by basting generously with BBQ sauce and putting in hot oven 400f until heated through and sauce is caramalized.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26184" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Soak navy beans overnight. Ensure they are covered by at least 3&quot;. Drain beans, cook until tender, strain again and reserve water

2. Sautee diced onion, salt and house rub. Cook until onions are soft and fragrant

3. Add remaining ingredeints and bring to a simmer. Add beans and continue simmering until beans are totally cooked and flavourful. Season with more salt and pepper, mix if necessary

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26185" image="">1)  Make white sauce as per recipe.

2)  Add in shredded cheeses and season to taste.

3)  Hold for service, or mix immidiately with pasta.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26186" image="">1. Melt butter in saucepan. Combine in large mixing bowl panko, garlic, herbs de provence, and salt and pepper mix. Incorporate well with butter. 
2. Allow to cool, transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate
3. Reserve for Mac &amp; Cheese</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26187" image="">1. Cook elbow macaroni until it is tender. Cool
2. Meanwhile heat up cheese sauce if necessary so it&apos;s maleable
3. Combine cooked macaroni and cheese sauce, season with salt and pepper
4. Pour into greased medium hotel pan
5. Heat up in steamer to serve
6. Top with cheese crust  and baked until crispy </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26188" image="">1)  In large pot over high heat, bring water to a boil, add salt.

2)  Add pasta to the pot, turn water down to a simmer.  Cook pasta to al dente. Spread out on full sized sheet pans to cool.

3)  Put in approprite vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26515" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Combine all ingredients except oil.  Whisk in oil, but do not emulsify. 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26517" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Rinse and drain bean sprouts under cold running water very well.  Allow to drain  

2)  Combine slaw mixture, angle cut green onion, julienne red onion, daikon and asian slaw dressing.  Toss well to incorporate and evenly distribute dressing.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28323" image="">Serve ingredients in the indicated proportions.

Place the butter chicken on top of the rice. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28324" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28337" image="">Serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28338" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-28343" image="">serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29007" image="">1)  Combine all well.  Store in appropriate container.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29315" image="">1)  In tilt kettle or large steam kettle over medium heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add garlic, ginger and cayenne.  Saute until cayenne is cooked out and garlic and ginger are no longer potent when smelled, about 5-10 minutes.

2)  Add crushed tomato, diced tomato, cream, honey, kasoori methi and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and taste.  Adjust if necessary.  Puree with immersion blender to break up the diced tomatoes and ensure that everything is combined well.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32192" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In large rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter.  When oil/butter is hot, add garlic and saute until golden.  Add half of corn and saute until tender, about 3-5 minutes. 

2)  Add cream and simmer 10-15 minutes more.

3)  Blend with hand blender, add remaining corn for texture.  Continue to simmer until reduced and thick.  Add S+P to taste.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32195" image="">serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32691" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition):
Soy 
Wheat
Gluten

Method:

1)  Combine ingredients well.  Reserve for roast pork belly glaze, or for bao bun mushrooms.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergens:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32692" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Combine soy sauce, shallot, garlic, ginger and brown sugar.  Mix throughly and reserve.

2)  Preheat oven to 100% STEAM.

3) Place belly SKIN SIDE DOWN on wire racks on top of baking trays and steam for 1.5 hours or until very tender.

4)  Place marinade on bellies and roast at 375 F for 20-30 minutes. 

Hot hold or...

-cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32718" image="">1)  On flat-top, add oil over medium heat.  Add onion, beaten eggs, frozen veg and saute until tender.  Add chicken and saute until cooked, about 5-8 minutes.

2)  Add cooked rice and continue to saute.  Season with soy sauce.  Combine well.  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32721" image="">1)  Ini sauce pan over medium heat, add garlic and crushed red chili&apos;s and saute for 2 minutes.

2)  Add stock and bring to a simmer.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.  Season w/ S+P.  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32723" image="">1)  On flat top over medium heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, carrots and onion.  When carrots and onion are starting to become tender, add peppers, baby corn and bok choy. Saute until all vegetables are tender and add garlic sauce.  Stir well to incorporate.Season with S+P.  Hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32866" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-32868" image="">
Allergens:

Soy
Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32869" image="">
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33519" image="">1)  Combine milk, onion and bay leaf in large steam kettle.  Bring to a simmer.  Lower heat and allow onion and bay leaf to steep in liquid for 20 minutes.  

2)  Bring milk back up to a simmer and add corn starch slurry as per recipe.  

3)  Strain thickened liquid and label, date, refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34085" image="">1)  Combine everything except chicken.  

2)  Incorporate chicken and allow to marinate for at least 24 hours.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides.  Allow to cool.

2)  Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender.  Blend well until combined into a paste.  Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

3)  Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix.  Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame seeds and korean chili flakes.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35734" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Add thai chili to kecap manis, heat to a boil and remove from heat.   Reserve for mushroom mix.

2)  On grill, or working in batches in large rondeau over medium high heat, add canola oil.  Add onions when oil is hot and saute 1/4&quot; diced onions until translucent, about 5 minutes.  Add garlic and ginger and continue sauteing for another minute.  Add mushrooms and continue sauteing until mushrooms are evenly cooked.  

3)  Add kecap manis mixture and remove from heat.  Let mixture rest for 15-20 minutes and strain, reserving liquid.  
4)  Bring mushroom liquid to a boil and add hoisin sauce.  When the sauce gets sticky and reduced, add to mushrooms and reserve for service. 
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35735" image="">1)  Steam Bao for about 3 minutes, or until soft and pliable.

2)  place warm mushroom bao mixture in bao bun, top with coleslaw mix, and garnish with nori and sesame mix.

3)  SERVE IT FORTH!!!!!!

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
Soy
Sesame
Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35823" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut potatoes in half then steam until tender, about 15 minutes.

2. On medium low heat, add oil to large rondeau.  Add cumin seeds and toast until fragrant, 30 seconds to 1 minute.  Add onion, coriander, chili powder, turmeric, jalapeno and garam masala.  Saute until onion is soft and spices are fragrant.  

3. Add garlic and ginger and saute for 1 minute more. 

4. Add tomato paste and saute for 4 minute.  Add diced tomatoes and saute 1 minute more.

5. Add cooked potatoes and saute until starting to turn brown.  Add cauliflower, stir well to combine.  

6. Add fenugreek, lime juice and fresh coriander and stir well to combine.

7. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36043" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36065" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Cut potatoes in half.  Steam until 70% done in rational.  Add oil and season with salt and pepper and roast in oven at 425*F until crisp.  Add garlic chili oil and mix well.  Reserve for salad.

2)  Thaw corn by steaming 

3) Cook bacon and reserve, crumble when cooled, and keep for garnish for service.

4)  Combine potatoes, and corn, green onion.  Reserve for service.   Just prior to serving, top with dressing and bacon crumble (if desired)

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Dairy
Milk 
Method:

1.Combine all well.

2. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37050" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-37167" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Add oil to large rondo/ pan over medium heat.

2) Add aromatic mix and cook stirring constantly until fragrant.

3) Add onion and continue cooking, stirring regularly until soft.

4) Add rice and toss to combine.

5) When rice is hot and everything is combined, turn off heat and season with soy sauce &amp; chopped cilantro.

6) Reserve and keep hot. OR

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38519" image="">serve in the proportions indicated</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38628" image="">PLEASE NOTE:

For portion sizes:

Because we offer 3 choices of sides on a +2 menu I have averaged them out.

These are the full sized portion weights:

Seasonal Veg x 70 g
Creamed Corn x 85 g
Potato Salad x 150 g

guest have choice of creamed corn or seasonal veg or potato salad ( request from nutrition ) </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38629" image="">PLEASE NOTE:

For portion sizes:

Because we offer 3 choices of sides on a +2 menu I have averaged them out.

These are the full sized portion weights:

Seasonal Veg x 140 g
Creamed Corn x 170 g
Potato Salad x 150 g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-40745" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-40746" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-40749" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-40750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-40751" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-40752" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42319" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter.  Once oil and butter are warm, add garlic, ginger and crushed chili.  Saute for 2-3 minutes.

2. Add all spices except salt and sugar.  Continue sauteing until spices are cooked out, about another 5 minutes.  

3. Add crushed tomato, salt and sugar.  Bring to a simmer.

4. Add water and bring back to a simmer.  Add cream and kasoori methi.  

5. Taste for seasoning.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42320" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine yogurt and spices.  Mix to combine well.  Reserve marinade.

2. Cut Paneer into 1&quot; chunks and pour marinade over top.  Combine gently to get the marinade over all the paneer chunks.  Allow to marinate at least 2 hours or overnight.

3. Preheat oven to 500*F.  Place paneer on foil lined baking sheets.  Broil for 5 minutes or until paneer turns golden brown.  Reserve for making Paneer Tika Masala

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42356" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Make Paneer gravy as per recipe.

2. Make and broil paneer as per recipe.

3. Blanch green peas in hot water, and shock in cold water.  Reserve for paneer tika masala.

4. Thin out gravy with a bit of water and bring to a simmer.  When warm, combine broiled paneer, peas and paneer sauce.  Hold warm for service.

*This recipe should make enough for one shallow hotel pan/cassrole serving vessel..

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-42358" image="">1)  Make Paneer Tika Masala as per recipe.  

2)  Upon order, place appropriate amount of paneer masala on top of rice.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-42370" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46844" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-46845" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50418" image="">1.Shred papaya.
2.Thinly slice carrots,ginger and bell pepper(fine julienne)
3.Soak Papaya with water and 4Tbs salt for 2 days.
4. Put the Papaya in a cheesecloth in a way that is trapped in the center. Gently rotate the cheesecloth until the papaya completey releases liquid. Do this more than once for better result.
5. Make the syrup by heating the venigar in a cooking pot. Once it starts to boil, add sugar and 1 teaspoon salt. Mix well and cook for 1-3 minutes.
6. Gently pour the hot syrup in the container. Quick close the lid. This will somewhat cook the papaya and veggfies and will make it a bit softer.
7. Let it cool and refrigerate.
8. Serve it cold.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51267" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55564" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1) Rough chop ginger and shallots.

2) Put everything into a blender and blend, slowly adding oil until everything turns into a smooth paste.

3) Reserve and use within 3 days.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
</Recipes>
