<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26471" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26515" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Combine all ingredients except oil.  Whisk in oil, but do not emulsify. 

Label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26713" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35811" image="">1)  Cook Penne as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil. Once hot, add diced red onion and saute for 5 minutes or until soft add garlic and chili flakes saute for a fwe more minutes.  Add capers, kalamata olives, semidried tomatoes and saute for another minute until warm throughout.  Add confit garlic reserved from garlic chili oil.

3)  Add arugula and remove from heat.  Add cooked pasta and stir well to combine.  Season with salt and pepper.  Reserve for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35910" image="">Allergens:

Wheat
Gluten
Dairy
Milk</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Tacos
Bowls

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.slice shallot and dredge in potato starch mix
3.Shake off excess in a strainer
4.Fry once at 310 until bubbles stop and shallot float
5. remove from and let cool on a resting rack turning the fryer up to 350 when they are out
6. whenthey are cool, re-fry at 350 until golden brown
7.place on paper towel to absorb excess oil
8.place in container on a service towel, label and use for TWO DAYS ONLY 

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Spread the brocoll evenlly on perforated pans
3. Steam untill aldente (4 min)

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Steamer, perforated hotel pans 2&quot;
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44851" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tempeh, garnish with green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Method:
1.Combine ingredents up to 3 days in advance.
-store, label and rotate

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49252" image="">Heat up honey in a water water bath to make it more runny and make working with it easier.

Puree chipotles in blender, add honey.

Flush the honey bottle with 200ml of hot water and add this hot water to the blender.

Puree to a smooth sauce.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50386" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients. Store in appropriate container, lable date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50424" image="">1) Coat mushrooms in oil and seasoning. Preheat oven to 375f.

2) Place mushrooms on parchment lined baking sheets evenly, only single layer, use multiple pans if needed, place whole rosemary and thyme sprigs over mushrooms. 

3) Roast in oven about 15 mintues, carefully drain excess mushroom juices from the pan,  and respread out mushrooms if needed. Return to oven and continue roasting an other 30 minutes, or until mushrooms are brown and tender.

4) Toss with chopped parsley and move to hot holding vessel. Hold hot for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50517" image="">1) Remove softer fronds of the dill from the harder stems. Chop well for garnish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54344" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Mass to volume conversion recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54743" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Peel and dice the russet potatoes. Use in recipes.

Store in a pail of water to prevent oxidation/browning. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55280" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56300" image="">1. Cut eggplant in to thick slices aprox 100g.

2. Lightly dust eggplant slices with salt, let drain for 1-2 hours. Rinse well to remove all salt and pat dry with paper towel.

3. Once dry, dredge in flour, tap off exess flour and dip in egg wash, once fully coated put in panko and fully coat.

4. Flash eggplant in deepfryer to par cook. Cool on sheets and put in cooler until needed. You can freeze them if made a few days a head.

5. To finish for service top with tomato sauce and cheese and bake until fully cooked and cheese is browned on top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56551" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Dice potatoes, Carrots, Celery, Onion into 1/4 inch cubes. Thinly slice fennel (reserve some of the fronds for garnish) Set aside. cut cod into large dice (1/2 inch) cut salmon same size as cod. Gather and scale all ingredients.

2. In a large rondeau/Pot add a small amout of oil to sautee off the Mire poix (celery,carrot,onion),fennel No Colour just till slightly soft.

3. Add butter to pan and let melt, add in flour to make a light roux and whisk in fish stock. Allow to simmer 5-6 minutes while gently whisking to prevent lumps and allowing to slightly thicken.

4. Add thyme bundle and bay leaf


5. Add fish in and allow the cod/salmon to cook out in the broth. Reduce to a low flame and let simmer so the flovours come together (20-30 minutes)

6. Add heavy cream just before removing from heat.

7. Garnish with a few strands of fennel fronds.

Hot hold/serve imediately.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut cauliflower into 1&quot; flourettes.

2. Toss in batter until completly coated.

3. Toss in 3/4 of panko. Take remaining 1/4 of the panko and bltz in robocoup until fine ( about 5 min).

4. Toss the wings in the fine blitzed panko and spread out on a sheet pan lined with parchment.

5. Bake in 350f oven for 20 min, remove from heat, stir, bake for an additional 15 min or until just golden.

6. Hold hot for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56700" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine flour, spices and wisk together.

2. Add soy milk and stock, wisk together to create batter.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57377" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a rondo over medium/ high heat add olive oil and onion and saute until fragrant.

2. Add defrosted/ drained spinach and chopped kale and heat until wilted. Drain any excess liquid.

3. Transfer to a mixing bowl and add remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57379" image="">1. Pre-bake tart shells.

2. Warm in oven with filling.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58417" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
 

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Reserve fennel fronds for garnish 
2.
3. Garnish stuff
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
Preps used in this Product recipe:

Method:

1.Be sure that taco shells are warm and shoft

2. Place the slaw on top of the tortilla topw with prpared caluliflower, chipotle mayo, feta cheese, crispy onion, cilantro garnish in that order.

3. Lime wedge on side

3. Serve with Kindness</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60812" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dock bottom of shell with a fork.

2. Bake at 350 F for 10 minutes or until golden brown.

3. Cool and store at room temperature.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62495" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Fry tempe and place on bottom of plate.

2. Place lettuce, tomatoes, cucumber, peppers, mint &amp; cilantro in mixing bowl and toss with dressing until evenly covered.

3. Place dressed vegetables in a high mound in the centre of the plate.

4. Garnish with crushed toasted cashews &amp; crispy shallots.

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62496" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Fry tempe and place on bottom of plate.

2. Place lettuce, tomatoes, cucumber, peppers, mint &amp; cilantro in mixing bowl and toss with dressing until evenly covered.

3. Place dressed vegetables in a high mound in the centre of the plate.

4. Garnish with crushed toasted cashews &amp; crispy shallots.

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62501" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. All veg should be 1/4&quot; dice (except jalapenos which can be minced).

2. Adjust seasoning and keep cool.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62502" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Season salmon with S&amp;P.
2. Make cross hatch grill marks on the presentation side of salmon (top).
3. Finish in oven until medium well.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62517" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Puree chilies to a fine paste.

2. Add remaining ingredients and blend until smooth.

3. Adjust consistency with more water if needed.

4. Season to taste.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62598" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Remove tails from prawns and defrost completely.

2. Toss in honey chipotle glaze.

3. Cook to appropriate temperature and hold for service or...

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62622" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cook rice as per normal with the addition of cumin seeds and salt.

2. Once rice is cooked, fluff well to break up all the grains.

3. Add lime juice and cilantro and mix well.

4. Hot hold for service.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62632" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Pick leaves of herbs but DO NOT CUT.
2. Mix with lime juice in small quantities to order.
3.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62637" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim ends of mushrooms.
2. Place in ful sized sheet pans with marinade and mix well.
3.Cover with parchment and top with another sheet pan.
4. Weight down with large cans to press mushrooms for 2-3 hours.
5. Skewer.
Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
