<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="R-51504" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Cook the pancake batter on the flattop with oil. 

Use a 6 fl.oz ladle for portioning and 1 pancakes is a portion

To plate and finish, put the pancake on a plate and drizzle/zigzag with the mayo from  squeeze bottle.

Sprinkle with shredded nori and green onion



1 pancake = 220g (double check this)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10874" image="">

1 - Preheat tilt fryer to 375

2 - Saute all veg with garlic and ginger until tender

3 - Add pineapple and juice until slow simmer

4 - Add chili sauce and vinegar and continue to simmer

5 - Add both sugars and water and simmer for 30 minutes

6 - Add cornstarch slurry and whisk until thickened

7 - Let simmer for another 30 minutes

8 - Remove from heat

9 - Cool, label and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

Add  red onions. 

Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible

Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55317" image="">method:


-mix eggs and seasoning
-parchment lined baking tray, lightly oiled
-pour egg mix and cook in oven @ 350F 
-cool slightly before cutting unto julienned strips
-reserve cold for garnish</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13683" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Dice peppers

Stirfry quickly in a very hot pan with oil: onions, celery and bell peppers

Chop parsley

Squeeze liquid from crab meat and check for shell fragments

Mix all ingredients together including the eggs, mayo and breadcrumbs

Shape into 2 oz (60g) cakes

Makes approximately 40 pieces

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26684" image="">ALLERGEN: SOY, SESAME



-Toss fried tempeh in Sweet&amp; Sour sauce, until well coated
-garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33709" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Heat wok over high heat. Pour in oil, then stir in carrots and peas; cook about 30 seconds. Stir in cooked rice. Shake in soy sauce, and toss rice to coat. Drizzle with sesame oil, and toss again.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26959" image="">ALLERGEN: SESAME

-Soak rice noodles in warm water for at least 30 mins
-steam for 5 mins
-Season with the rest of ingredients</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33438" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and blend thoroughly.

You may not need the full amount of water, so test it out with less to start with and add it incrementally until the desired texture is achieved. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51214" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Combine and rub chicken.

2. Bake/Roast chicken until chicken is cooked through
internal temp should reach 160F

3. Hot hold for service or cool down according to HACCP procedures for future use.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredients

2. Chop parsley, crack eggs and whisk

3. Fold all ingredents together and ensure it is evenly mixed

4.Form into meatballs and chill thoroughly.

5. MEATBALL PORTION SIZE SHOULD BE 55g RAW- USE THE BLACK HANDLED PORTION SCOOP

6. Cook through in a hot oven and smother in warm tomato sauce.

( If prepping aheat these can be IQF&apos;d for future use)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41464" image="">ALLERGENS: GLUTEN (HOISIN)

Prep:

- Assemble: Black Cardamom, Star Anise, Coriander Seed, Cinnamon, and Nutmeg. Toast spices until fragrant, and then create a Sachet D&apos;Epices with it, using cheesecloth and cooking twine.

- Pick: Celery Leaves, and Cilantro leaves from Stems. Keep the Stems of the Cilantro and the Celery Leaves separately (together). The Celery Stalks will be used in the making of the stock; the Cilantro Leaves will be used as garnish when serving; the Cilantro Stems and Celery Leaves will be added to the final step of the stock as aromatics. 

- Peel Daikon completely and cut into 2&quot; round pieces. Do the same with the White Onions in this recipe. Grill both of these until blackened on both sides - essentially burnt. This is important to the process.

- Place these burnt Daikon and Onion pieces into a large hotel pan, and then add: Cabbage, Garlic, Ginger, and Celery Stalks. Steam for 30 minutes, allowing water to accumulate in the hotel pan throughout the process.

- Fill the Steam Kettle with the 50 L of water in this recipe. Turn on, and begin heating.

- When the steaming ingredients are done, add to the Steam Kettle. When this is done, bring the mixture to a boil, and add the Sachet D&apos;Epices. At this point, add Soy Sauce, Tamarind Paste, Brown Sugar, and Rice Vinegar.

- This stock can be done overnight, but it is not necessary. It should reach a boil for an hour - at least - and then it should reduce to a simmer, and be left for at least 2 hours. During the simmering process, salt can be added to taste. 200 grams are listed in the recipe, but this is an approximation.

- When heat is reduced to a simmer, add Cilantro Stems and Celery Leaves, and turn heat off all together. Allow these to steap for half an hour at least, and give the mixture a good stir before straining. 

Label / Date / Store Appropriately!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41551" image="">- Roast all Chilis at 400F
   - Place Each Chili on SEPARATE Oven Pan
      - Anchos will be done first...
      - Guajillos will be done around the same time...
      - Chipotle will need more time - roast until almost black...

- SEED ALL CHILIS ONCE THEY&apos;VE COOLED DOWN!
   - Break them open and shake out the seeds.
   - Keep as much of the &quot;flesh&quot; as possible.

- IN THE VITAMIX:
   - Blitz the remaining &quot;flesh&quot; into a powder.
   - Add Oil, Sugar, Salt, and Lime Juice
   - Using Hand Blender / Immersion Blender to Mix

- Date / Label  &amp; Store!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41547" image="">Prep:
- Soak Tomatillos in Warm water for half an hour
   - Brush through them with your hand to loosen &quot;jackets&quot;. The more the better...
- Take off all of the Tomatillos outer jackets

Pre-Oven:
- Ready 2 Deep Hotel Pans for Ingredients
- Half all Tomatillos to ready them for roasting
- Cut Onions
- Add Garlic Whole
- Half Jalapenos and Serranos, Remove Stems
- Set Aside All Remaining Ingredients
- Oil and Salt Ingredients in Hotel Pans

Oven:
- Roast for up to 30-40 minutes at 375For until caramelized
- add water and cook for another 60-90 minutes
   - Stir Occasionally to circulate caramelized top!
- Remove and Cool!
   - Cooling this is key to its colour. If remaining ingredients are added (namely cilantro) to a warm sauce before blending, the green will turn to brown.

Post-Cooling:
- Add 6 of the 8 Bunches of the cilantro to the mixture, and blend with the Large Hand Blender / Immersion Blender. Take 3 Cups of the mixture, and add the remaining 2 bunches of cilantro to the Vitamix. Blend in the Vitamix until it is a uniform deep green mixture. Add to the remaining mixture. 
- Continuing with the Large Hand Blender / Immersion Blender, lime juice, and salt to taste.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41574" image="">- PRE-SOAK Beans overnight!
   - 2 X 20L CAMBRO Containers
   - HALF of the Beans in Each
   - Filled with 12L of Water Each

- Drain Beans from their hydration liquid. Your cooking water should be different from your soaking water.

- Using the Small Steam Kettle, Cook Beans slowly in 20 extra liters of water. They should be good to start at 250F.


- Cook the beans until they are soft, but not decomposing. During the cooking process it is important to skim off the foamy protein that will accumulate at the surface of the cooking beans&apos; water - this, if unchecked, will lead to a poor bitter taste and a lesser shelf life for the beans themselves.

- While the beans are cooking, saute your onions in Canola Oil, until dark brown. Caramelize them as far as they will go, and then add Cumin and Garlic. Saute Cumin and Garlic for 5 minutes, and then take off heat.

- Turn off Steam Kettle when the beans are cooked, and let beans sit. Take 4L of the cooking water, and set aside.

- Drain beans, and then transfer them into a neutral container greater than 40L in volume. Get the large Hand Blender / Immersion Blender.

- Add the Onion mixture with the Garlic and Cumin, as well as half of the Salt, and half of the Brown Sugar. The remaining halves - set aside, and use to SEASON TO TASTE. 

- With the Hand Blender / Immersion Blender, blend about 4L of the bean mixture into a puree - and then add back into the rest of the beans, and mix. Add reserve liquid from the cooking, until you get - not a soup - beans with a puree of more beans.

- Cool, Label/Date, and Store. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">Prep:

- Dissolve Tomato Paste in the &quot;Water For Recipes&quot; used to cook the Rice in the Combi Oven (this will result in the Rice turning Red.)

- Once Rice is out of the oven, add all ingredients - Oil, Rice Spice - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

- When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41751" image="">Prep:

Combine in the iondicated proportions and mix

- Label / Date / Store </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45624" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Heat the oil. 

Cook the onions about 10 minutes.

Add the beef cubes, and cook, stirring frequently until the meat is no longer pink on the outside, about 10 minutes.

Stir in the vindaloo paste, tomatoes, and squash and cook for 5 minutes.

Pour in the water, and bring to a simmer.

Cover and reduce heat to medium-low; cook until the beef is tender, about 40 minutes. 

Season to taste and garnish with cilantro to serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42160" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix. 

Use a blender if you like, it is easier. A whisk will work too. 

***Please make sure to mix tahini before you use it as it settles and separates. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Open 2.8L cans of pineapple.

2. Drain Liquid - Reserve

3. In the convection oven - at 400F - roast the drained pineapple for 10 Minutes, or until darkening and caramelizing on the outside.

4. Remove from oven, and let sit until they&apos;ve reached room temperature...

*IN THE MEANTIME*

5. Set up the ROBOT COUPE

*THEN*

6. In batches (4-5), begin pulsing the lime juice,  some of the drained pineapple juice from the cans(use as needed to gain the right concistensy wont need it all) salt &amp; coriander - letting the processor do its job until the mixture is at a chunky puree! 

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42354" image="">

- Once your Pork Butts are ready to prepare, score their tops (THE FATTY PART) with cross-hashed cuts up to 1CM deep, OK?!

- At this point, rub the Pork &quot;Butts&quot; with the dry spices (Cumin, Cinnamon, Cayenne +), salt, and achiote. The Achiote paste can also be mixed into a little bit of orange juice or pineapple juice to make it easier to rub in.

- In Deep Hotel Pans, place all of the butts in there with the Onions, Garlic, and wet ingredients (Water, Pineapple Juice, Orange Juice) - THEN - pre-heat your oven to 275-300 Degrees (F). 

The level of the wet ingredients should come halfway up pork, add more water if need be. Wrap with foi

Cook for 4.5-7 hours.  At 4 hours, you can check to see how this process is going. 


Label/Date/Store!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42412" image="">

- Using the Vitamix, take 1 can of Chipotle Peppers (In Adobo) and blitz them into a fine puree with this recipe&apos;s Lime Juice.

- Fold into Sour Cream and add Salt.

Label/Date/Store!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-24091" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-42817" image="">ALLERGENS: MUSTARD

Prep: 

1. Clean and cut Potatoes into large uniform shapes and sizes. Each Potato may yield 6 pieces, if cut properly - about the same style as Homestyle Potatoes. Steam these in the combi oven until soft but not crumbling apart - use the steam setting: check after 30 minutes.

2. Cut the Cauliflower into florets, and deep fry until golden brown - then set aside. Rough Chop Onions, and set aside your Ginger and Garlic. While you&apos;re doing this, set aside your spices - to be used at the beginning of the cooking process. Also, set aside your 4 litres of Water (though, it may not be necessary).

5. In the Tilt Skillet, starting with Canola Oil - start to saute your onions (towards caramelized). Then, throw in your spices, and saute them as well - before adding your Garlic and Ginger.

6. As soon as you add your Garlic and Ginger, you&apos;re going to want to deglaze the Tilt Skillet by adding up to 3 litres of the water you set aside. At this point you can add your Turmeric, Garam Masala, Mustard, and canned Tomatoes. 

7. Let simmer for a few minutes before adding the fried Cauliflower, and Potatoes. Turn up the heat on the skillet at this point, and scrape the bottom of the skillet with the mixing paddle to accumulate caramelized sugars therein that will burn if left unincorporated. Use the remaining water in this recipe, or more, if need be - keep it moving! You&apos;re near the end here.

8. Turn the temperature down on the Tilt Skillet. Rough Chop the Cilantro and Mint. Cut the Serrano Peppers thinly on a mandoline, and then throw all of these ingredients into the mixture. 

9. Season to taste at this point - the salt in this recipe is roughly 1.2% of recipe weight. You may find that you need more.

10. Finish with lime juice before serving. This could change depending on how you&apos;re doing your batches - but the finished product should be given acidity with lime juice prior to serving regardless of how this dish interacts with the Hot Holds.

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43244" image="">ALLERGENS: SESAME, SOY

Prep:

- In a Vitamix, puree the Black Garlic, Garlic. Lime Juice and Water together until no small pieces of Black Garlic remain - until the mixture is 100% uniform.

- Add Soy and remaining ingredients, and - while the Vitamix is running on a lower setting (than necessary to puree the Black Garlic) - ease in the Xanthan Gum until the mixture thickens to a sauce-like viscousity.

Label / Date / Store Appropriately!

***Please do this once with Chef before attempting alone.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43341" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and allow the pickle juice to pickle the cabbage. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43581" image="">
zest and juice limes

chop herbs

combine everything and mix

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43587" image="">SEQUENCE!

1. Tortilla!
2. Rice
3. Beans
4. Black Chili Mayo
5. Chicken
6. Pico De Gallo
7. Serrano Peppers 
8. Cabbage Mix

Roll!

Note: SEQUENCE IS IMPORTANT!

As a general rule, it is best to put sauces on the Burrito right after the Rice &amp; Beans stage. If you put the sauces on last, or at the top (facing the customer) of the Burrito - it will be a mess when you go to roll it. It&apos;s a good technique to put Cabbage, Cheese, or Arugula at the top of the Burrito (facing the customer) before rolling it, as this will keep your hands clean, and help you save on glove waste!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43930" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Chop down shallots and galangal as required. 

Add all ingredients to a large bucket and add just enough water to get it to mix.

Use the large hand blender to puree to a smooth paste. 

Reserve for use in the curry recipe. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43931" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Saute the massaman curry paste until cooked out.

Add onions, red peppers, and brown sugar. Cook out onions.

Add coconut milk, and turn heat down. Add lime leaves.  Simmer this mixture for 20-30 minutes on low heat. Cover for best results.

Add potatoes and salt.

Let simmer now, adding water if need be, until potatoes are cooked out.

Once potatoes are cooked out, take off heat,mix in lime juice to finish and conduct final seasoning assesment and adjustment.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43932" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine in hotel pans and slow cook at 350F in the oven until beef is tender. 2-3 hours

Strain off some of the stock to make service more managable, reserving the stock for another purpose. 




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44082" image="">ALLERGENS: WHEAT, GLUTEN

Prep:

- Take the Coriander Seeds, Cumin Seeds, Ajwain Seeds, Black Pepper and Garam Masala - and toast, then grind in the Vitamix into a fine powder. The toasting, as mentioned in other recipes, is key to developing flavour and aroma.

- Amchur Powder is not a spice, but a powder made of green mango. It should not be toasted. Opinions differ on this, but - for this recipe, do not toast this ingredient.

- Normally this recipe would be made into a paste with lemon juice and a small amount of water. We use this as a more dry rub, in combination with alread-wet ingredients like potatoes that have been boiled and chickpeas that sit in &quot;aqua fava&quot; (literally: bean water).

- If this spice mix is low, talk to a Chef about it. Some of these ingredients come from a specialty provider with an indented delivery schedule - and will need to be ordered several days in advance in order to allow for proper prep time.

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43658" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Prep:

- Basically, this is a bound puree of Cilantro and Mint. All of the other ingredients in this recipe are more there for context.

- Place all ingredients (and, it&apos;s OK to use ground coriander in this recipe, even without toasting it)(don&apos;t worry, other flavours in this recipe will pick up where it otherwise would have done its thing) into a Vitamix. Keep Xanthan Gum aside.

- Start the Vitamix, and slowly raise the speed setting until you&apos;re working with a fine puree of all of the aforementioned ingredients. On &quot;High&quot; (the button to the left of the speed setting nob), remove the plunger from the pitcher base, and add the Xanthan Gum while the mixture is moving. 

- Keeping in mind while you&apos;re doing this that the base of the Vitamix will heat up, causing your greens inside this puree to become bitter and discolour. Therefore, it&apos;s best if this it done quickly - but do not sacrifice quality for haste! 

- You should know, with this recipe, and all recipes requiring a binder like Xanthan Gum, how a thickener is doing in its job. To test this mixture, turn the Vitamix off, and dip the plunger into the mixture, then raise it to see how slowly it falls off the plunger. It should fall slowly. If it doesn&apos;t, add more Xanthan Gum binder, and continue. The idea is that this will become a paste that will get things dipped into it.

- Don&apos;t worry - if you thicken it too much, you can always go backwards and let it out again, easily. This is not like over-cooking a steak. That said, know what you&apos;re looking for, and do it.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44083" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Prep:

- Basically, this is a bound gel of sweetened Tamarind Paste. 1 Jar is 300g, so the recipe is built around that.

- Fresh Tamarind, which isn&apos;t very widely available here in North America, is not very tart at all like Tamarind Paste. Citric Acid, other additives, and industrial processes force it to be this way - so it needs to be let out and sweetened. Allspice in this recipe is used to mask some of the bendinf that this ingredient must go through. 

- Place all ingredients into a Vitamix. Keep Xanthan Gum aside.

- Start the Vitamix, and slowly raise the speed setting until you&apos;re working with a fine mixture of all of the aforementioned ingredients. On &quot;High&quot; (the button to the left of the speed setting nob), remove the plunger from the pitcher base, and add the Xanthan Gum while the mixture is moving. 

- You should know, with this recipe, and all recipes requiring a binder like Xanthan Gum, how a thickener is doing in its job. To test this mixture, turn the Vitamix off, and dip the plunger into the mixture, then raise it to see how slowly it falls off the plunger. It should fall slowly. If it doesn&apos;t, add more Xanthan Gum binder, and continue. The idea is that this will become like a paste that will get things dipped into it.

- Don&apos;t worry - if you thicken it too much, you can always go backwards and let it out again, easily. This is not like over-cooking a steak. That said, know what you&apos;re looking for, and do it.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43346" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Prep:

- THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGH ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

- Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

- Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

- At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

- Any questions (especially with this recipe, as the yield is low), PLEASE ASK CHEF! 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44303" image="">SEQUENCE:

1. Tortilla
2. Rice
3. Beans
4. Sriracha Sour Cream
5. Pulled Pork
6. Pineapple &quot;Sauce&quot;
7. Cabbage Mix
8. Crispy Shallots

Roll!

Note: as a general rule, it is best to put sauces on the Burrito right after the rice &amp; beans stage. If you put the sauces on last, or at the top (facing the customer) of the burrito - it will be a mess when you go to roll it.  It&apos;s a good technuique to put the cabbage, cheese, or arugula at the top of the burrito (facing the customer) before rolling it, as this will keep your hands clean, and help you save on glove waste. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43584" image="">Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44308" image="">SEQUENCE:

1. Rice
2. Beans
3. Sriracha Sour Cream
4. Pulled Pork
5. Pineapple &quot;Sauce&quot;
6. Cabbage Mix
7. Crispy Shallots




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44310" image="">SEQUENCE

1. Rice
2. Pico De Gallo
3. Cabbage Mix
4. Chipotle Sour Cream
5. Beef
6. Chimmi Churri
7. Mozzarella

Note: THE ORDER IS IMPORTANT!


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44311" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix.

Mix again every time you use it as it is not an emulsified dressing and it will separate. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44315" image="">
SEQUENCE:

1. Rice
2. Beans
3. Black Chili Mayo
4. Chicken
5. Pico De Gallo
6. Serrano Peppers 
7. Cabbage Mix



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44316" image="">SEQUENCE:

1. Tortilla
2. Rice
3. Salsa Verde
4. Guacamole
5. Arugula
6. Feta
7. Crispy Shallots

Roll!

Note: as a general rule, it is best to put sauces on the Burrito right after the rice stage. If you put the sauces on last, or at the top (facing the customer) of the burrito - it will be a mess when you go to roll it.  It&apos;s a good technuique to put the cabbage, cheese, or arugula at the top of the burrito (facing the customer) before rolling it, as this will keep your hands clean, and help you save on glove waste. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50985" image="">Make a marinade from the ingredients and rub steak.

Grill or otherwise cook steak to complete the recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44335" image="">
- Drain Cannelini Beans. The Yield on these beans has been calculated in this recipe - roughly the loss of over a Kilogram in &quot;Aqua Fava&quot;. A quick rinse is valued, but not entirely necessary. 

- Half all Grape Tomatoes. You will notice in this recipe that 5 LBS is the measured amount require. This is because each box of Grape Tomatoes that comes in from Freshpoint is 10 LBS - meaning: use half of a box for this recipe. Easy enough?

- Small Dice Red Onions. Saute with Cumin and Cayenne, adding 1 Bag of Frozen Corn and Red Pepper to the mix along the way. Do not roast this Corn in the oven for any reason - its starches develop and it becomes tough texturally. Deglaze this mixture with Apple Cider Vinegar, and season.

- Pick Oregano. Don&apos;t bother picking the Cilantro, as some stem is fine in this recipe. Rough Chop both of these, and reserve to add into the rest of this recipe.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...


NOTE: This recipe will last if properly refrigerated for up to 5 days. This is a large batch for this item, since it&apos;s new to the menu and may not sell well depending on diner preferences. Do not make more than this until it&apos;s proven that it will move. Waste not want not!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

Pour over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44353" image="">1 PTN = 90 g

NOTES: This is a recipe where tasting is very important, as well as an understanding of what a product is or how it&apos;s supposed to taste. Each Item in this recipe has a specific process associated with it - when combined, it can be delicious.

Also, RE: ALLERGENS: it&apos;s important to know that there is no bread in this recipe. Only one item contains Wheat Fiber as an additive that makes it easier to use in a culinary setting.

Order Method:

1. Potatoes (&gt;1&quot; Cubes / Steamed)
2. Chickpeas (Pre-Cooked / Drained, Rinsed)
3. Tomatoes (Small Dice)
4. Cucumbers (Small Dice)
5. Red Onions (Fine Dice)
6. Chaat Spice (TOSS ALL AFOREMENTIONED ITEMS)
7. Salt (INCORPORATE WHEN TOSSING OTHERS)

8. Tamarind Chutney, Mint / Cilantro Chutney &amp; Yogurt 
9. Mint (Picked) &amp; Cilantro (Rough Chop w/ Mint)
10. &quot;Sev&quot; (Dried Chickpea Noodle Snack)

Prep:

- Process the Potatoes in the Combi Oven on its Steam setting. Take Chickpeas out of can(s) (in appropriate weights).

- Cut all Vegetable ingredients. This step, and the one before it with the Potatoes and Chickpeas can be done in advance. Both can be combined, but kept separate for service (Potatoes and Chickpeas, then Tomatos, Red Onions and Cucumbers). Mint and Cilantro should be processed separately, but can be combined for service.

- Chutneys and Yogurt will be processed in advance, and the bottled for service. Chat spice should be kept separate.

- Combine all, and TASTE!

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44357" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Deep fry falafel until it is crispy and hot all the way through

2. Grill pita bread lightly to warm through

3. Prepare all side dishes and accompaniments

4. The rice, pita and falafel are served warm/hot

5. The hummus, salad, and pickled cabbage are served cold

PLATING;

1. place rice on side of plate, cut pita into 4 and stack next to rice

2 Add salad to other side of plate.
add hummus and pickled cabbage next to the salad, try to keep the cold things together and the hot things together on oposite sides of same plate.

3. place the 5 pieces of crispy/hot falafel on top of the rice. Serve

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44363" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut cauliflower into florets

deep fry the cauliflower and toss in salt

***Please pay no mind to the &quot;ghost nutrition oil&quot; in the recipe- this is simply the nutrition dept. accounting for some oil absorbtion for caloric breakdown purposes***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44362" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Method
place tabouleh (90g) and pita (1pc) on plate
add fried cauliflower (1 portion, 140g)
add hummus (90 ml), pickled cabbage (50 g) and a lemon wedge (20g)  to plate
garnish with tahini drizzle

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27397" image="">ALLERGENS: MUSTARD, NON-HALAL (WINE IN THE MUSTARD).

Notes: 

This is not a traditional Vindaloo, but no one really has a good idea of what Vindaloo is - really. Many British adopters of Indian cuisine, when it hit England, didn&apos;t know that they were eating a Vindaloo made by predominantly Sri Lankan immigrants that the British just assumed were Indian. These immigrants from Sri Lanka, who ended up being lumped into British society as essentially a sub-brand of Indian people, were largely different from the majority of East Indians because they mostly Muslim. 

The dish was originally a cultural mash-up that was born out of Portuguese colonial influence in Goa. It was originally made with Pork and Wine Vinegar -but, since Sri Lankans are mostly Muslim, the dish became wine-less and pork-less (Lamb, Goat, and Beef stepped in to create what most now understand as what the dish should be), and was hence reborn under the name Vindaloo in 1950&apos;s/60&apos;s Britain as what people assume it to be today. Like many Indian dishes, it has a rich history - just lesser known, in its essential details, than others. This recipe for the base paste is somewhere between its original ethos, and its modern twists.

Prep:

- THE NIGHT BEFORE: Open up the can of Roasted Red Peppers. Add Chili Flakes, and Red Wine Vinegar. Soak overnight. You can also put together your spices the day before - this would be wise, no?

- THE DAY OF: Process Onions however you&apos;d like. This mix will be puree&apos;d once it&apos;s cooked out.

- Begin to cook out Onions. Caramelization is fine - high heat is best. Toast Spices. Add Garlic and Ginger - cook those out. Add Dijon Mustard, and cook out slightly. Then! Add Water, and let simmer. Add soaked mixture of Roasted Red Peppers, Chilis, and Vinegar, from th previous day.

- Simmer for 30-45 minutes, and then puree with an Immersion Blender until it becomes a fine paste. 

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

***This recipe can be made in advance in large batches, and then vac-packed and frozen for future use.

Any questions? - Ask Chef...
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44405" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat, sulphites

Icons
vegetarian

Method

Place 1 pc of vegetarian samosa onto side plate

serve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44413" image="">
Method:

Serve in the indicated proportions

***Note1 portion of chaat = 180g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44417" image="">Allergens:
mustard

Icons:
vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method

Place 240g portion of Aloo Gobi onto side bowl

serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44410" image="">ALLERGENS: MILK (PANEER)

Notes:

This recipe should be as green as possible - meaning: stewing the green elements of this recipe too far will kill the flavour and visual appeal of the recipe. The idea of this recipe is to have a flavourful earthy base to balance out the fats present in the Paneer (which is to be added last). 

Prep:

- Cut the root ends off of the Green Onions, and then grill them until coloured. Cool, and then chop up in pieces that are no less than 3 inches long.

- Rough Chop Onions, and begin cooking them out immediately. Throw in Spices, Garlic, and Ginger. Deglaze with water. Season and simmer for 5-10 minutes. 

- Cut Paneer into mouthful-sized cubes - nothing too big. It will cut like Tofu, but it will also flake off, as it does not have gypsum as a binder, and soy proteins are different from milk fat proteins.

- Add HALF of the Spinach in the recipe, and cover for 5 minutes. You want the Spinach to be cooked out, but not to the point of bitterness. At this point, the recipe is very close to being taken off heat.

- Add the Cilantro in this recipe. Then, using an Immersion Blender, puree the Spinach and its juices into a sauce. This does not have to be a uniform puree as it would come out of a Vitamix - a little bit of texture is OK. Check for seasoning.

- Add Chopped Green Onions (grilled), Paneer, the other half of the Spinach, and the Cilantro - season again to taste using the salt in this recipe. Turn off heat.

- Add Yogurt before moving this recipe into Hotel Pans for serving.

Any questions? - Ask Chef... </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44477" image="">Allergens:
wheat, gluten, milk

Icons:


Method:

place 1 portion of garlic bread on a plate

serve

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44606" image="">1. Assemble all the ingredients.
2. Saute the onions and pureed lemon grass until translucent, add ginger and garlic and cook out for another 5 minutes. Add sugar and cook for another 5 minutes.
3. Add Green Curry Paste and cook out for another 5 minutes to develop flavour.
4. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer, add lime leaves and season.
5. Thicken with slury, thicken so that sauce coats the back of a spoon and sticks.
6. Add lime juice just before you take it off the heat.
7. Throw in the thai basil and cilantro and blend in the sauce to give it it&apos;s green color.******

****** If you are making the sauce for the next day, DO NOT add the cilantro/thai basil as it will go brown and discolor.


Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9610" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Soak the black beans. 

Saute your onions unitl softened, add the garlic and ginger. Saute some more, and mix in the brown sugar to combine and then deglaze when you&apos;re ready with soy sauce. 

Simmer, and the add water. Strain the black beans, and then add them to the simmering mixture, and simmer further until the black beans are soft.

Prepare your potato starch into a slurry with 500ml of water, and incorporate. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44640" image="">
PREP RECIPE

- Weigh out Rice appropriately. Rinse 3 times, or until the rice become clear.

- Roughly chop all other ingredients.

- Bury those ingredients in the Rice, and add water.

- Steam for 25 minutes or more. Check along the way. Remove once done.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44641" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tofu and season with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44677" image="">

PREP RECIPE:

Cut Cucumbers in slices that are 1cm thick

Boil up sugar, vinegar, soya sauce and spices to dissolve the sugar. 

Once dissolved combine the pickling liquid with the cucumbers to pickle.

***if the liquid is poured over hot it speeds up the process.*** </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44532" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients in the proportions indicated</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44319" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Method:

Place 105g portion of Tabouleh into side bowl

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44832" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Method:

Note- 120g of tofu

Arrange the sauce, tofu, bok choy and egg roll on top of the noodles in the bowl. 

Garnish with bean sprouts and green onion. 

Be sure to portion appropriately. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44834" image="">Allergens:
soy

Icons:
vegan, vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method

120g portion of tofu
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44841" image="">
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44859" image="">Allergens:
soy, sesame, wheat, gluten, egg, sulphites (incomplete - need to confirm gyoza )

Icons:
N/A

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44860" image="">Allergens:
sesame, sulphites, soy, wheat, gluten  (incomplete - need to confirm tempeh)

Icons:


Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43261" image="">Allergens:
soy, sesame, sulphites, wheat, gluten, egg

Icons:
vegetarian

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44851" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tempeh, garnish with green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48319" image="">
Method:

Cook Eggs and Hollandaise

Assemble either a vegetarian version with sliced tomato or a traditional version with black forest ham.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Combine everything and mix thoroughly 

Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51222" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Trim ends off and peel. Discard

2. Cut and slice as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45420" image="">
Cook all sub recipes, have all product prepared and on hand. 

Place rice in the base of the bowl and top with the curry stirfry.

Top the stirfry with bean sprouts, green onion, cilantro and provide a mini lime wedge, along the inside rim of the bowl. 

A drizzle of the nuoc cham sauce can be offered to the guest and drizzled over the top to complete the dish.






Note*** a mini lime wedge is a lime cut into eight&apos;ths and then the 8ths are cut crossways to make little pyramid shapes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45422" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Rinse Rice 3 times

Combine rice in a 1:1 water ratio.

Slice up Ginger into slices, please do not use a puree. Add ginger to water and rice. Add salt to rice.

Steam the rice

While the rice is steaming Combine Mirin and Rice Wine Vinegar.

Stir the vinegar/mirin mixture into the rice to complete the seasoning.

***A portion of rice on the plate is 150g***
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45423" image="">PREP RECIPE

Combine all ingredients, and blitz together with an Immersion Blender or mix thoroughly with a whisk.  

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately




 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41309" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine everything in a blender and blend to a paste/dressing</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54277" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve either a veggie dog or an all beef hot dog. It is the guests choice. 

They are both accounted for in this recipe. They are both included for accounting purposes only. 

I order is 2 mini buns and 1 hot dog cut in half and placed into the the 2 buns. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44438" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for a 1/6 portion of baguette- that is to say a baguette cut into thirds, and then using either the top half or the bottom half as a portions. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1)  Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray.  Place egg in egg poacher cup.  Steam for 7 minutes until cooked.

Allergens:

Soy, Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50411" image="">Allergen:


Put beans in a pot. Bring to a boil. Skim the foam off the top. Cook until beans are tender. Strain and use as needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50705" image="">Method:
- heat flat top or pan over med-high heat
- add oil, ensure to coat bottom of pan
- crack egg into hot pan
- season with salt &amp; pepper
- once egg has cooked 60%, flip over gently
- cook for 20 sec until white is fully cooked
- serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51321" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe: Seafood Pancake.

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1. Thaw out seafood (apropriately) once fully thawed it is imparative to this recipe that all seafood is well drained a squeezed (gently) of exess water or soggy pancakes will happen! cheesecloth is great for this aplication. 

2. Chope tha calamari into a small dice, Chop the kimchi into a manageable size.

3. Combine veg and processed (dry) seafood together

4. Add the clams with necter to the mix (clam necter is used in place of some of the water that would normally take place in a pancake batter)

5. Add the flour and pancake mix, incorporate enough water to combine and mix untill everything is thuroughly mixed and the proper batter consistancy is achieved

6. Cook a test pancake and check for seasoning, texture and balance. Adjust seasoning as needed.

7. Use 6 fl oz ladle for portioning. 1 pancake sholud weigh 220g (double check to see that it does, adjust portioning as needed)  ladle should be a level scoop not rounded.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50988" image="">1. Saute onion in oil until translucent. Add garlic cook for 5mins.
2. Add soy sauce, mirin, korean paste. Bring to a boil. Season. add sesame oil.
3. Put in Vitamix and blend.
4. Cool it down, Label and put away.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50917" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and boil, thicken and strain.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26683" image="">Allergen: soy


-From frozen, fry pork bites until fully cooked (approx. 5 mins)
-Toss in Sweet&amp; Sour sauce, until well coated
-garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42364" image="">Combine and mix.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52630" image="">
Stirfry veggies in a wok in oil, just to sear the outside a little bit. 

Add sauce to the wok and bring to a simmer. 

Meanwhile, tray up some chicken dice and roast in the oven until cooked through. 

Add to the sauce and mix thoroughly.  


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50703" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51229" image="">
Method:

Arrange attractively in a bowl in the indicated proportions. 

Ensure rice is on the bottom and other ingredients are arranged in quadrants so that as much variety as possible is visible. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51228" image="">
Combine in the indicated proportions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53634" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Pull dough from freezer

Spread with sauce

Top with cheese

Chop peppers zucchini and saute mushromms and sprinkle them around liberally

Bake until crust is golden brown and cheese is hot and melted

Cut into 6 pieces</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53838" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Placed cooked penne in the base of a bowl and top with tomato sauce and 4 blended meatballs. 

Garnish with parmesan and herbs and stick a garlic bread in the side.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53938" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix

Taste and adjust seasoning as needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53939" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Toast the buns and stuff with the filling</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53955" image="">
PREP RECIPE

The crab cake mix rpe recipe yeilds approximately 40 crab cakes at 60g each. 

This recipe breads them. 

Set up a 3 stage breading station and run the cakes through: flour, eggwash, bread crumb.

Line up neatly on sheetpans

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53979" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Heat the large steam kettle to just below simmering

Blanch the vegetables then the noodles in hot simmering water for no longer than 30 seconds to 1 minute. (leave the vegetables in when blanching the noodles)

Strain and cool.

Mix in the seasonings.

Tray and label.

Bake to heat for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until lightly browned and hot throughout. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53995" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss mushrooms with salt and pepper and oil. 

Roast on a parchment lined sheet pan in a hot oven until the water from the mushrooms cooks away and the mushrooms are browned and flavorful</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53996" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the onion with oil and salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned around the edges and hot throughout

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46824" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing purposes only. 

Please make all of the associated sub recipes as indicated in those recipes. 

Any blend of the listed vegetables will suffice, or just one vegetable. 

The important part is that 180g/ 6oz (by weight) of vegetables are provided. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Gather All ingredients

2.Cut all veg into apropriate shape and size; Dice onions into 1/4 inch pieces dice all peppers the same, removing stems and seeds (discard)

3. Reserve for service


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54279" image="">
PREP RECIPE

*Note- the quantity for one recipe is one can of drained pineapple

Combine and mix, taste and adjust seasoning as needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54278" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Sear the crab cakes and make sure they are golden brown on both sides and hot throughout. 

Serve with pineapple salsa and ceasar salad. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54281" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Sear the chickpea patty and make sure they are golden brown on both sides and hot throughout. 

Serve with pineapple salsa and ceasar salad. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54283" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51266" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve 1 toasted pita (grilled or baked), cut into wedges with 125 ml of hummus</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54318" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Shred nori into a fine julienne with scissors</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54328" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-54329" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE
 

Serve over rice. 

Garnish with sesame seeds and green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54343" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut in half or in quarters as needed. 

Steam in an perforated hotel pan. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54344" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Mass to volume conversion recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54660" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Put all ingredients into a pot and turn to low heat, stiring occasionally so the sugar doesn&apos;t burn at the bottom.

2. Once at a simmer and sugar is dissoved, turn off, downsize, cool down, label and refrigirate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54658" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Slice the cucumbers and place into two vac bags.

2. Distribute the syrup equally between them.

3. Seal in vacum for 45 seconds.

4. Label and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54661" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Peel / slice the daikon(use the smaller ones so they match the cucumbers in size as much as possible) and place into two vac bags.

2. Distribute the syrup equally between them.

3. Seal in vacum for 45 seconds.

4. Label and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54662" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Assemble the dry ingredents in a bowl and give it a mix so it is all incorporated.

2. While on low/medium speed, add the cold butter in. (Can also blend it in with pastry cutters, ask the first cooks or chef where they are)

3. Add cold water very slowly so that it gets incorporated evenly.

4. Once the dough forms, plastic wrap it and let rest at least a few hours before use.


GHOST ITEM - This is using Earth Balance for the &quot;butter&quot; portion of the recipe - The ghost item.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54665" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Assemble all ingredients

2. Mix sugar and water and heat to 118C

3. Mix in nuts and cook untill nuts are toasted and sugar is a little caramelized (10 Min)

4. Pour onto a tray and let cool.

5. Chop into small pieces(Like a crumble)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54663" image="">1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Place all items over a double boiler and melt.

3. This has to be made after the tart shell and prelinee are complete and ready to be poured over.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54668" image="">1. Mix Raspberry Pure with Tapioca starch.

2. Place 50ML into a vac bag and spread as thing as possible.

3. Seal back without sucking any air out.

4. Steam for 25 minutes.

5. Open bag and let film tighten up/dry overnight.


Fry when ready to use!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54669" image="">1. Put all ingredients into pot.

2. Simmer for 20 min to extract the raspberry flavour from the pure into the water.

3. Strain.

4. Reboil and add agar agar.

5. Set

6. Break up and pass through the fine sieve.

7. Bottle and use as needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54674" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Put all ingredients together into a big Cambro.

3. Use the big hand blender to dissolve the sugar in the mixture.

4. Set aside, label, refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54675" image="">1. Open all the noodles into the container first.

2. Pour HOT water over them and let them cook/soak for 10 Min.

3. Drain and cool for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54677" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Cut your tofu blocks into 50g pieces. Mix soy with water/lime juice.

3. Slice ginger/chilies and mix them into soy sauce.

4. Marinate tofu in soy for 1 day.

5. Grill for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54678" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Blanch edamame beans in salted water and shock right away.

3. Put canellini beans, edamame beans, salt and lime juice into a cambro and blend with the hand blender.

4. Check seasoning.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54685" image="">1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Make batter.

3. Clean the mushroom ends.

4. Dip the whole mushroom and fry.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54686" image="">1. Steam potatoes until soft.

2. While the potatoes are steaming, place soy milk with garlic and salt on the stove on low heat to par cook the garlic.

3. Toast the nori sheets and put them through the Robo Blender to dust them.

4. Mix all the ingredients with the EARTH BALANCE in the big mixer to make mashed potatoes. Check seasoning.

Ghost Item is Earth Balance Original Butter - 1KG</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54687" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Clean the Oyster Mushrooms/Cut them in half lenghtwise.

3. Make the glaze.

4. Coat the mushrooms in glaze and lay them out on a baking tray with a sheet.

5. Bake at 375 for 10-15Min.

6. Serve 2 Pieces per plate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54688" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Follow directions for Udon/Ramen Base.

3. Thicken a little bit.

4. Check seasoning.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54689" image="">1. Mix salt with cayenne and blitz into powder.

2. Clean and slice the lotus root into skinny disks into cold water to keep.

3. Drain and dry. Deep fry between 300/325 degrees until lightly golden.

4. Season and store in a dry spot.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54691" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients

2. Mix miso paste with vinegar into a smooth paste.

3. Mix the paste into the mayo.

4. Check seasoning.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54692" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Blanch spinach in salted water.

3. Chill in ice bath and then drain/squeeze well.

4. Set aside for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54693" image="">1. Assemble ingredients

2. Blanch beans in salted water.

3. Shock and drain well.

4. Set aside for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54700" image="">1. Trip both ends off lemons.

2. Slice Lemon into 10 slices.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54769" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

This is a side beef curry, no rice or bean sprouts are included for this. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54706" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-54849" image="">Prep Recipe:

This Beef should be stewed in the curry base



note: cook the lemongrass beef in the skillet, add the curry base and simmer for 1-2 hour until beef is tender.

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55287" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Pour cold milk into a round container with extra room in it to mix.

3. Pour in the powder mixture and blend until smooth.

4. Scrape down the sides periodically. 

5. When nice and smooth, quickly transfer into cups before its fully set.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55289" image="">Allergens!

Dairy, Nuts(Almond and Hazel), Sulphites</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55370" image="">Method:

- Heat oil in wok, add onion, peppers, cabbage

- Add the noodles and sauce and combine and mix unitl noodles are cooked and everything is thoroughly mixed.

-reserve in hot table for service</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55371" image="">Method:


- Heat oil in wok, add vegetables
- add sauce and tofu, mix until tofu is well coated
- reserve for service in hottable




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem and seeds.

3. cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55776" image="">1. Aseemble all the ingredeints.

2. Shred the cucumber.

3. Rough chop the cilantro.

4. Mix all the ingredients together.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55777" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56766" image="">METHOD:

1. slice tomatoes in half

2. toss in bowl with olive oil and salt and pepper

3. on parchment lined tray place tomatoes cut side up.

4. put in oven at 400 degrees for 6-10 minutes (may need longer) 

5: check for doneness; most liquid should have evaporated and tomatoes should be slightly dried around edges but not leathery or burnt.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat a heavy pan over medium-high heat and add the canola and sesame oils.

2.  Add the beans and cook, stirring occasionally until they start to turn golden.

3.  Add the ginger, garlic, green onions, soy sauce, sugar and Sriracha and cook a few minutes more, stirring often, until the garlic is golden, the beans are deeper golden and the sauce has reduced and become sticky. The sauce should coat and cling to the beans well

4. Sprinkle with toasted sesame seeds.

Hot Hold/Serve imeediately

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53848" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a mixing bowl; add kale, romaine and dressing. ensuring to evenly coat entire salad (do not over dress)

2. Garnish with parm and croutons (idealy these items do not go into the mixing bowl to keep it dairy and gluten free)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57144" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. Cut stems off

3. Rough mince(sliceing motion not chopping; slicing will prevent brusing the delicate cilantro leaves)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50588" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove just the tips/ends of the cucumber

2. Using a sharp knife,slice/chope cuke into desired shape and size appropriate for recipe use.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57192" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Lightly trim the tougher base( bottom of stem) from mushrooms (not much needs to be discarded ast mushrooms have about a 93% yield)

.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20963" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim in edible base from veg and any unsavour pieces. Discard

2. Cut and process veg as needed for recipe use.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano until desired texture achived (course or fine)

3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-6888" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Pulse jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

*Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44312" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook and cool quinoa

Chop all other ingredients

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess oil.

use is associated recipes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46637" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.gently clean mushroom stems

2.cut down portions to approx the same size

3.Saute shallots, garlic,  in oil until translucent

4. Fold in thyme leaves and saute 1 min

5. Saute until mushrooms have expressed most of their liquid

6. Remove from heat, toss with fresh squeezed lemon juice, chopped parsley

7. Season with salt &amp; pepper

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, rondeau pot, insert, rubber spatula
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52620" image="">Each lime gets cut into 8 equal wedges!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53993" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss diced Zucchini with oil and salt and pepper and roast on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned and hot throughout.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51210" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes

2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well

3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine and mix thouroughly

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47654" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-62841" image="">each baguette makes 4 pieces for sandwiches</Recipe>
</Recipes>
