<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-43427" image="">
PREP RECIPE

heat up water to 65C. turn off and steep Konbu for 45 mins to 1hour.

Remove Konbu, cool it down and julienne. 

In steeped water, add daikon, nori sheets. Make a sachet with the umami dust and add it also. Bring to a boil.

remove Sachet and nori sheets, disgrade them in compost bin. Remove daikon and save for soup.

Add soy sauce and mirin to finish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10874" image="">

1 - Preheat tilt fryer to 375

2 - Saute all veg with garlic and ginger until tender

3 - Add pineapple and juice until slow simmer

4 - Add chili sauce and vinegar and continue to simmer

5 - Add both sugars and water and simmer for 30 minutes

6 - Add cornstarch slurry and whisk until thickened

7 - Let simmer for another 30 minutes

8 - Remove from heat

9 - Cool, label and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

Add  red onions. 

Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible

Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51221" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26610" image="">ALLERGEN: SOY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26674" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Stirfry veggies in wok. (baby corn, mushroom, ginger, garlic, peppers, chiles, onion and zucchini)

Bake chicken in the oven.

Combine sauce and baked chicken with sauce and stir thoroughly to combine. 

A portion in the product recipe is 240g of this mix. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33709" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Heat wok over high heat. Pour in oil, then stir in carrots and peas; cook about 30 seconds. Stir in cooked rice. Shake in soy sauce, and toss rice to coat. Drizzle with sesame oil, and toss again.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26959" image="">ALLERGEN: SESAME

-Soak rice noodles in warm water for at least 30 mins
-steam for 5 mins
-Season with the rest of ingredients</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26883" image="">

-Cook noodles for 5 mins in the steamer or
-Cook noodles for 3 mins in boiling water at the station</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26622" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Saute the onion and garlic in the butter unitl softened and fragrant.

2. On a low- medium heat add flour to make a roux.

3. Dilute the roux incrementally with milk stirring vigorously between additions unitl all of the milk is incorporated.

4. Season to taste. Adjust as necassary

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33559" image="">
METHOD:

Prep:

- This recipe should take 2 days - no more, no less, however, the curing process can be elongated, depending on time, to 3-4 days.

- TO CURE: Take Sesame Oil, Brown Sugar, and Salt - and rub the Pork Belly down thoroughly. Place in a Hotel Pan, SKIN SIDE DOWN, and let the sugar and salt begin drawing out moisture and breaking down the outside of the Belly. IMPORTANT: in the morning, when you come in for your shift the next day - TURN THE PORK BELLY OVER, SO THAT THE SKIN SIDE IS UP AND OPEN TO THE AIR. 

- Pre-Heat the Convection Oven to 325F/180C.

- Cover Pork Belly with remaining ingredients, and roast for 25 minutes. Then, turn the oven to 425F, and finish for and extra 10-15 minutes. 

- Once Pork Belly is cool, remove its skin layer and discard. Cut the meat, and prepare for next steps.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37870" image="">ALLERGEN
SULPHITE

Method:

- In oil, sautee onion, garlic and mushrooms
- Add Cumin and chipotle. mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41312" image="">ALLERGENS:

Prep:

- Cut all vegetables into large pieces. Do not spend more than 10 minutes cutting these vegetables, as all of them will be discarded, and no one will see your lovely cuts if you put effort into them.

- Heat a pot in the background with a small amount of oil. You can even start this process with water if you want. Start cooking out anything in the onion family first - this approach can be used with all stock making.

- Once you&apos;ve cooked out your onions (can no longer smell gas coming off of them, and you start to smell sugars coming from them), then add all remaining ingredients EXCEPT CILANTRO - as well as water - and bring to a boil. 

- When the pot is at a boil - let boil for about 20 minutes. Then, turn it down to a simmer. ADD CILANTRO (stocks and all), simmer for 40 minutes with salt, and take off heat. Once off heat, let rest for 45 minutes to an hour, and strain using the fine chinois.

- Label / date / store appropriately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42160" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix. 

Use a blender if you like, it is easier. A whisk will work too. 

***Please make sure to mix tahini before you use it as it settles and separates. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42353" image="">
Prep:

- Quarter Corn Tortillas. 2.5 Packages of Corn Tortillas will yield 2 Deep Hotel pans full of Corn Chips.

- Using Paper Towel, create a large pan or bowl for draining the excess oil off of the Tortilla Chips, after they&apos;ve come out of the Deep Fryer.

- At 350 Degrees (F) in the Deep Fryer, fry NO MORE THAN HALF OF A STACK OF CORN TORTILLAS (QUARTERED) at a time.

- Using a Spider, or Long Tongs - KEEP TORTILLAS MOVING AT ALL TIMES. 

- Depending on how dark the Deep Fryer oil is, fry the Tortilla Chips until they are brown (keeping in mind that they will cook for a little while longer once they&apos;ve been taken out of the fryer. 

- As soon as the chips are out drying, salt lightly using the Windsor coarse grain salt. The salt will only stick during this stage of production - be sure to catch it!

Label/Date/Store

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42354" image="">

- Once your Pork Butts are ready to prepare, score their tops (THE FATTY PART) with cross-hashed cuts up to 1CM deep, OK?!

- At this point, rub the Pork &quot;Butts&quot; with the dry spices (Cumin, Cinnamon, Cayenne +), salt, and achiote. The Achiote paste can also be mixed into a little bit of orange juice or pineapple juice to make it easier to rub in.

- In Deep Hotel Pans, place all of the butts in there with the Onions, Garlic, and wet ingredients (Water, Pineapple Juice, Orange Juice) - THEN - pre-heat your oven to 275-300 Degrees (F). 

The level of the wet ingredients should come halfway up pork, add more water if need be. Wrap with foi

Cook for 4.5-7 hours.  At 4 hours, you can check to see how this process is going. 


Label/Date/Store!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43212" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Gather spice and herb stems and put into a cheesecloth tied loosely with twine
 
Rough chop the daikon and reserve. 

Rough chop: shallots and garlic, Set aside.

In a pot/skillet/kettle/wok  add oil, and sweat out shallots and garlic until softened

Add coconut milk and cheesecloth spice sachet and chopped lemongrass.

Bring to a simmer for about 20 minutes to let those flavours infuse, and then add daikon.

Cook out daikon, and then remove daikon once cooked (it will be used again for the final product).

Add water, and prepare a corn starch slurry at the same time. 

Thicken just enough to give it some body, but keep it in the broth realm and not as thick as a sauce



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47263" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients in the proportions indicated. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47239" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43688" image="">
Prep:

Mince shallots and red peppers. 

Combine everyhting and mix. 

Cook and test a piece to check seasoning. 

Once you establish that seasoning is correct proceed with sauteing, stirring and breaking up the seasoned meat with a woodedn spoon in a large low sided pot.

Label / Date / Refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43929" image="">ALLERGENS: SESAME

Prep:

- Chop all Shiitake Mushrooms in the same size as the &quot;Food Service&quot; Mushroom mix from FreshPoint.

- Cut the bases off the Shimeji Mushrooms (Both: White and Brown) and pull them apart. They should be fine long as they are - cut once (half) if need be, but no more than that.

- Using the Wok, on high heat - drop all mushrooms in, and add a splash of water to get them moving. Add Salt, Pepper, and Canola Oil. Then, add Ginger, Garlic, and Mirin.

- Once cooked out, add Sesame Oil, and turn off heat. Mushrooms should be able to get a little burn on them. Taste to see if more Salt is needed.

- These items can be vac-packed and frozen for future use. This mixture should be made at least once every two weeks.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions - ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43930" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Chop down shallots and galangal as required. 

Add all ingredients to a large bucket and add just enough water to get it to mix.

Use the large hand blender to puree to a smooth paste. 

Reserve for use in the curry recipe. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43931" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Saute the massaman curry paste until cooked out.

Add onions, red peppers, and brown sugar. Cook out onions.

Add coconut milk, and turn heat down. Add lime leaves.  Simmer this mixture for 20-30 minutes on low heat. Cover for best results.

Add potatoes and salt.

Let simmer now, adding water if need be, until potatoes are cooked out.

Once potatoes are cooked out, take off heat,mix in lime juice to finish and conduct final seasoning assesment and adjustment.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43932" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine in hotel pans and slow cook at 350F in the oven until beef is tender. 2-3 hours

Strain off some of the stock to make service more managable, reserving the stock for another purpose. 




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44083" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Prep:

- Basically, this is a bound gel of sweetened Tamarind Paste. 1 Jar is 300g, so the recipe is built around that.

- Fresh Tamarind, which isn&apos;t very widely available here in North America, is not very tart at all like Tamarind Paste. Citric Acid, other additives, and industrial processes force it to be this way - so it needs to be let out and sweetened. Allspice in this recipe is used to mask some of the bendinf that this ingredient must go through. 

- Place all ingredients into a Vitamix. Keep Xanthan Gum aside.

- Start the Vitamix, and slowly raise the speed setting until you&apos;re working with a fine mixture of all of the aforementioned ingredients. On &quot;High&quot; (the button to the left of the speed setting nob), remove the plunger from the pitcher base, and add the Xanthan Gum while the mixture is moving. 

- You should know, with this recipe, and all recipes requiring a binder like Xanthan Gum, how a thickener is doing in its job. To test this mixture, turn the Vitamix off, and dip the plunger into the mixture, then raise it to see how slowly it falls off the plunger. It should fall slowly. If it doesn&apos;t, add more Xanthan Gum binder, and continue. The idea is that this will become like a paste that will get things dipped into it.

- Don&apos;t worry - if you thicken it too much, you can always go backwards and let it out again, easily. This is not like over-cooking a steak. That said, know what you&apos;re looking for, and do it.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47267" image="">
-Heat flat top to 300F
-on flatbread, spread muhamarra, pork, olives and feta on top
-place on flat top, for 3 mins or until bread is warm and crispy on the bottom
-cut into 4 pieces and serve with arugula on top </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

Pour over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44344" image="">
Prep:

- Take Roasted Red Peppers out of their can, and drain liquid - but keep the liquid (just in case).

- Salt, and then roast Pumpkin Seeds at 375F for 7-9 minutes with a small amount of Olive Oil, until brown and fragrant. Pull and cool once done.

Combine everything and blend until (mostly) smooth.


Label / Date / Refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44407" image="">Allergens:
wheat, gluten

Icons:
vegan, vegetarian

Method:

place 1 pc of Roti on side plate

serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47233" image="">Allergens:


Method:

- Combined ingredients into hotal pans
- Steam for 35 mins </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43933" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Assemble all ingredients.

1. Char onions, ginger, leek whites, daikon and cabbage in that order. 

2. While your veggies are charing, fill your kettle with 60L and pop in the Kombu and let it steep in warm water for 30 minutes. Take the Kombu out and save for Miso Soup.

3. Sautee your charred ginger and garlic. Add onions, leeks and celery.

4. Add sauteed veggies to the kettle and start filling with the rest of the water, leaving room for the Daikon and Cabbage. - Start heating up kettle to boil.

5. While the kettle is coming to temp, add Umami Dust - and any MUSHROOM ENDS that may be around. Some tomato ends are acceptable too.

6. Once the Daikon and Cabbage are done charring, cut into large chunks.

7. When Broth comes to a boil, turn it down to a very low simmer and add the daikon, cabbage and nori sheets. Season a bit at this stage too, as it helps draw out the flavour of the veggies.

8. If you are leaving the broth over night, you can add all the leek ends and any random cilantro/parsley/green onion ends to the broth while on low heat. If you are finishing it on the same day, then add the green ends at the end and let steep for 30 min before straining etc...

To finish.

1. Scoop all the veggies out.
2. Re-up with water and bring to a boil.
3. Turn down the kettle and add add 1 jug of soy sauce, taste and add more salt/pepper as needed.
4. Put through fine strainer and cool.

Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44639" image="">
PREP 

Chop the daikon into medium dice

Combine and mix all dry ingredients into hotel pans 

Add enough liquid ingredients to just cover

Braise at 350F for 2 - 3 hours or unitl beef is tender

Strain off some of the liquid after cooking to make it more manageable 

*Reserve the strained off liquid. Do NOT discard. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44640" image="">
PREP RECIPE

- Weigh out Rice appropriately. Rinse 3 times, or until the rice become clear.

- Roughly chop all other ingredients.

- Bury those ingredients in the Rice, and add water.

- Steam for 25 minutes or more. Check along the way. Remove once done.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44641" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tofu and season with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44674" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Mince the onion

Juice and zest the limes and oranges. 

Combine all ingredients iin a bowl and mix well. 

Form into 90g football shaped meatballs.

Bake to cook out. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44677" image="">

PREP RECIPE:

Cut Cucumbers in slices that are 1cm thick

Boil up sugar, vinegar, soya sauce and spices to dissolve the sugar. 

Once dissolved combine the pickling liquid with the cucumbers to pickle.

***if the liquid is poured over hot it speeds up the process.*** </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44686" image="">
Method:


- Using a rondeau, begin to saute your ginger, onions and garlic, with your oil. Once cooked out, add other ingredients and stir - lowering heat. Raise to a boil, and then let simmer. 

- Using a Corn Starch slurry, thicken the mixture slightly. 

Taste.

Use this sauce for both Dan Dan Pork and Dan Dan Tofu/Tempeh.

Either use immediatley, or hold hot for service, or chill rapidly for later use.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44826" image="">Allergens:
wheat, gluten, milk, soy, egg

Icons:
vegetarian

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44837" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

A portion size is 90g of cooked and drained weight.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51239" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Toss the steamed edamame with a little salt. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44843" image="">
Method:

Have all ingredients prepped and on hand.

Place into the bowl 150g noodles, and top with broth. arrange the tofu, and mushrooms in quadrants and garnish the top with bean sprouts, green onions, and red chili oil.


***Please note- recipe to be updated to Udon noodle once it is available in OC and reviewed by nurition team.***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44846" image="">Allergens:
sesame, soy

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41308" image="">
Method:

Arrange attractively in a bowl in the indicated proportions.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51226" image="">
Serve in the proportion indicated.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44857" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve the ingredients indicated in the appropriate proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44866" image="">
Method:

***please note the malt vinegar and chili oil components are garnishes put out for the guest to serve themselves, please do not use in recipe, they are only in here for the costing purposes.***

The bok choy is steamed.

The noodles are cooked.

The sauce, including the tofu is finished and hot.

Place noodles in the base of a bowl, top with a 4 (fluid)oz ladle of sauce. place the 100g of steamed bak choy along one edge of the bowl. 

Top with the garnishes of bean sprouts, green onion and cilantro. 

Serve with 1 fried egg roll. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41306" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44851" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tempeh, garnish with green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44933" image="">
Prep:

- Garlic and Ginger - use the Pre-Minced products that are available in the prepped items fridge.

- Cut 1/3rd of a packet of Red Thai Chilis. Each packet that we get from Freshpoint is 300g.

- Large Dice: Cabbage, Onions, and cut Gai Lan in 

- Heat the Wok. This side can be done at the station for effect or in the back, in hiding. 

Either way --&gt; THIS IS AN ITEM THAT SHOULD NEVER SIT IN OUR WARMERS, AS IT WILL LOOK HORRIBLE (WORSE THAN THE FACE THAT CHEF WILL MAKE IF HE FINDS IT IN THE WARMERS AT ANY POINT, OR BEING DONE AN HOUR BEFORE SERVICE), AND THE FLAVOURS WILL DEGRADE IMMENSELY.

- Starting with the Onions - in the hot Wok - begin to fry these ingredients. Spoiler - this is going to happen fast, and you&apos;re really just going to want to put some colour on the onions, before throwing in the Cabbage and deglazing with 2 Cups of Water. When you do this, throw in your Ginger and Garlic, and then toss your Gai Lan in. 

- Add remaining ingredients, and bring to a boil. Immediately turn off heat at this point, and while it&apos;s still at a boil, make a Corn Starch Slurry out of your remaining Cup of Water in this recipe - adding it slowly while stirring. At this point, you&apos;re pretty much done. 

- It would be best to do this infront of the students, as it will draw attention to the amazing job you&apos;re doing and the flavours that you&apos;re representing. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44934" image="">ALLERGENS: SOY, SESAME, SULPHITES 

Icons:

Vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44936" image="">
PREP RECIPE

1. Assemble ingredients

2. Sautee onions and chili flake first for a few minutes until soft.

3. Add garlic and ginger and sautee for a few more minutes until fragrant.

4. Mix in brown sugar and dissolve fully, then mix in honey and water. 

5. Bring to a boil. Turn down and add soy sauce.

6. Thicken with slurry. Check seasoning and use.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44937" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook individually then combine and mix

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44938" image="">
PREP RECIPE

cook individually and then combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Combine everything and mix thoroughly 

Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45426" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Place rice on the plate and arrange the other components around and on top. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47611" image="">
-Heat flat top to 300F
-on flatbread, spread muhamarra, eggplant stew, olives and feta on top
-place on flat top, for 3 mins or until bread is warm and crispy on the bottom
-cut into 4 pieces and serve with arugula on top </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45103" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Place rice in base of bowl

Top with chicken and broccoli and ladle the dashi into the bottom. 

drizzle the broccoli with the gomae dressing and garnish with the pickled ginger, onion and kyuri (cucumber) as well as the nori sheet triangle. 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51222" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Trim ends off and peel. Discard

2. Cut and slice as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45192" image="">Allergens:
soy, sesame, wheat, gluten, egg, sulphites

Icons:
N/A

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45379" image="">
Method:

Arrange attractively in a bowl in the indicated proportions. 

Ensure rice is on the bottom and other ingredients are arranged in quadrants so that as much variety as possible is visible. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45416" image="">
Notes:

***Portions for this recipe are 4 (fluid) oz - approximately 160g

Prep:

- Thaw ground pork if it is frozen.

- Heat oil in a large rondeau, and add pork - saute well until done, add sauce and mix thoroughly.

Use immediately, hold hot until service, or chill rapidly for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45419" image="">
Method:

***please note the malt vinegar and chili oil components are garnishes put out for the guest to serve themselves, please do not use in recipe, they are only in here for the costing purposes.***

The bok choy is steamed.

The noodles are cooked.

The sauce, including the ground pork is finished and hot.

Place noodles in the base of a bowl, top with a 4 (fluid)oz ladle of sauce. place the 100g of steamed bak choy along one edge of the bowl. 

Top with the garnishes of bean sprouts, green onion and cilantro. 

Serve with a fried Egg Roll
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45409" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A


Notes:

Sushi Rice is never made in a Combi Oven in Japan. That doesn&apos;t matter. It can be simulated well enough to a respectable standard. I would prefer to have this made in a Rondeau, with a higher water ratio than what&apos;s suggested in this recipe, however, when you use the steam function in the Combi Oven you have to use a 1:1 ratio because of the excess humidity in the oven&apos;s chamber. Timing on this will depend on how many times the oven is opened and closed during the cooking process relative to other items being prepped - a suggested number will be put forth below. 

Prep:

- Rinse Rice 3 times, or until the water from it becomes clear. In many cases, this will take more than 3 passes through COLD water.

- Once the Rice is cleaned, it should be drained effectively, and combined with its 1:1 water ratio for cooking. The steam function on our Combi Ovens, in case it isn&apos;t already going: 100% humidity w/ 212F/100C. Break up Lemongrass, and Slice up Ginger into chunks that you&apos;ll be able to take out after this process is over. DO NOT USE A GINGER PUREE for this recipe. Place the Rice in to steam.

- Combine Mirin, Rice Wine Vinegar and other ingredients into a bowl over ice. Or, place the bowl in the Freezer while the Rice cooks. THIS IS IMPORTANT, as it must help the rice cool down as much as possible, so as not to over-cook.

- Once Rice is cooked - 35+ minutes - take it out, and place in a large mixing bowl. Add the chilled liquid mixture, and mix around until evenly seasoned. BE CAREFUL NOT THE MASH IT UP. THIS IS EASY TO DO, AND WILL LEAD TO A STRANGE PRODUCT.

- Lay down on sheet trays if need be, and place in the fridge to cool down as soon as possible - stopping the cooking process.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45422" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Rinse Rice 3 times

Combine rice in a 1:1 water ratio.

Slice up Ginger into slices, please do not use a puree. Add ginger to water and rice. Add salt to rice.

Steam the rice

While the rice is steaming Combine Mirin and Rice Wine Vinegar.

Stir the vinegar/mirin mixture into the rice to complete the seasoning.

***A portion of rice on the plate is 150g***
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45423" image="">PREP RECIPE

Combine all ingredients, and blitz together with an Immersion Blender or mix thoroughly with a whisk.  

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately




 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45424" image="">ALLERGENS: SOY, SESAME


Note: 

This is a very simple recipe - combining one with the other. This will be a short write-up. 


Prep:

- Using the Wok, on high heat with the small amount of oil, mark the Beef enough to get a little taste of burning. Again, the colour here will be balanced out by the Bulgogi Sauce - go ahead and burn it a little bit.

- When you&apos;re content that you&apos;ve succeeded in giving the Beef a little burnt flavour, and that&apos;s it&apos;s cooked out, turn off the heat. As the wok is still hot though, add your Bulgogi Sauce, and let the temperature reduce until it&apos;s all ready to come out of the Wok as a mix.

- This is one of those things that you can get BONUS POINTS FROM CHEF for doing ON THE STATION during service or right at the beginning of service. It should NEVER BE DONE IN LARGE BATCHES PRIOR TO SERVICE IN A LARGE BATCH AND HELD HOT DURING SERVICE IN WASTEFUL BATCHES. 

Any Questions? - Ask Chef...</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47232" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange attractively on a plate in the indicated proportions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41309" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine everything in a blender and blend to a paste/dressing</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44438" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for a 1/6 portion of baguette- that is to say a baguette cut into thirds, and then using either the top half or the bottom half as a portions. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52088" image="">Allergen:Gluten


-Portion dough into 190 gram balls (one recipe makes 10 pc)
-in a little flour, stretch out the balls into 8inches long by 4inches wide flatbreads
-bake in pizza oven until cooked
 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47610" image="">


-Heat flat top to 300F
-on flatbread, spread muhamarra, stew, olives and feta on top
-place on flat top, for 3 mins or until bread is warm and crispy on the bottom
-cut into 4 pieces and serve with arugula on top </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47229" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Method:

- Steam carrot, potato and daikon
- Sautee leeks, garlic, ginger and onions in oil
- Add steamed vegetables and gravy.
- Season to taste

***Alternately the carrot, potato and diakon could be simmered in the gravy to cook through as well.***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47261" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Note - Mix slaw as needed during service to prevent it from turning in to a soggy mess.

Toast - Seasame seeds and cashews separately.

Slice cucumbers into matchsticks

Rough chop cilantro - Keep as whole as possible

Pick mint leaves

Mix all the veg together to form a dry slaw, keep the herbs on side as garnish.

Toss with Nuoc Cham and a dash of garlic oil as needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47165" image="">


Cook out onions, garlic and ginger in chili oil.
Add the rest of the vegetables and continue to sautee.
Deglaze with cooking wine, soy sauce.
Add corn starch slurry to thicken mix.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47259" image="">
PREP RECIPE


Make the paste first: Blitz in a Vitamix
galangal, shallots, lemongrass, thai chilies, garlic with oil and hot water to speed up the process. May need to make a few small batches.

Cut Tofu into small pieces to resemble ground meat.
Cook out the paste, add tofu and mushrooms. cook until mixture turns a light brown.

Finish with sugar, lime juice, herbs, white pepper, soy sauce and salt.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41318" image="">


in a large rondeau, toast curry powder. Add all ingredients except the slurry. Bring to a boil then add the slurry to thicken into a gravy.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50993" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients
2. Cut tomatoes in half
3. Slice mint and basil into thin slices
3. Mix everything together but do no season or dress


This recipe will create 15 portions of salad by weight!

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47200" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47599" image="">Heat up your rondeau, add oil and onions - saute untill soft. 

Add the spices - paprika, cumin and a bit of black pepper - toast for about 3 minutes and add the diced tomatoes and chickpeas.

Meanwhile, deepfry the eggplant for a few minutes to soften it up before adding it into the stew. If  you don&apos;t deepfry it before mixing it in, it will take a very long time to cook out.

Cook the stew out for about 15 minutes for the flavour to develop. Mix in the olive oil, lemon juice and salt to taste.

Prepare your herbs and only add them just prior to service and as garnish for the fresh flavour profile.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50600" image="">Save all your parsley, leek, cilantro, green onion and celery ends for stocks!!!!!

1. Gather all your ingredients first.

2. Char the ginger on the grill.

3. Sautee the onions, leek, ginger, garlic and lemon grass.

4. Add the water and bring to a boil. Turn down right away to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. After that, turn off and throw in the leek, cilantro, parsley, green onion and celery ends for 30 minutes.

5. Strain, down size and cool down.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50672" image="">
PREP RECIPE

saute the peppers and onion in oil
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50562" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Spread the pesto. 

Arrange toppings

Sprinkle cheese

Bake until bread and toppings are hot and cheese is melted. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50843" image="">Allergen: Milk, wheat


1. Assemble all the ingredients

2. Mix everything together.

3. Sprad the mixture onto 4 TRAYS evenly.

4. Intent the parm into 4 sections once spread.

5. Bake at 325* for 10-15 Minutes or until it starts to get golden on the top.

6. Let cool down and store in an airtight container.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42012" image="">1)  Roasted Serrano peppers on grill until deeply charred.  Reserve for making sour cream

2)  Combine sour cream, roasted serrano peppers, lime juice, cilantro and salt in container for vita mix.  Process on medium until well combined.

3)  Taste for seasoning and label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Milk/Dairy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50988" image="">1. Saute onion in oil until translucent. Add garlic cook for 5mins.
2. Add soy sauce, mirin, korean paste. Bring to a boil. Season. add sesame oil.
3. Put in Vitamix and blend.
4. Cool it down, Label and put away.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50858" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

On a prebaked flatbread, spread pesto and sprinkle veggies and olives

Bake until toppings and bread are hot and cheese is slightly melted. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50533" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto and mozzarella cheese, then place artichoke heart pieces and caramelized onion evenly across flatbread.

2) Evenly place halved grape tomatoes around flatbread, 

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 3-4 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked, cut, sprinkle arugula and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52027" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51245" image="">Method:

Stirfry veggies in wok. (mushroom, garlic, peppers, and onion)

Cube and lightly fry tofu.

Combine sauce and tofu into wok and stirfry briefly to combine. 

Garnish with green onion and cilantro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23310" image="">THIS RECIPE IS A RATIO ONLY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51525" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26683" image="">Allergen: soy


-From frozen, fry pork bites until fully cooked (approx. 5 mins)
-Toss in Sweet&amp; Sour sauce, until well coated
-garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52039" image="">
- Heat oil in a large Rondeau, and add Tofu. Stir to crumble 
- Add Dan Dan Sauce and continue to stir until tofu is fully coated

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51528" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE


-Boil noodles for 10 mins or until tender in stock</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47269" image="">
-Heat flat top to 300F
-on flatbread, spread muhamarra, pork, olives and feta on top
-place on flat top, for 3 mins or until bread is warm and crispy on the bottom
-cut into 4 pieces and serve with arugula on top </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50989" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51274" image="">1. Weigh dry salad mix and toss with the dressing. ****
2. Plate
3. Garnish
4. Serve


**** Taste first before you serve it to the customer for flavour.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52701" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Slice the chiles finely. 

Combine all ingredients and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50811" image="">To make the Pad Thai:

1 Pour some oil on the hot flat top and pour some egg onto it.Scramble egg.(with 2 spatulas)

2 Add the 150g portion of rice noodles on top of the egg and toss.(with 2 spatulas)

3 Add the carrot, herbs (cilantro and green onion) and bean sprouts and toss.

4 Add the 75g of fried tofu cubes and then, the 50ml of Pad Thai sauce and toss.

5 Place in bowl, arranging tofu on top.  

6 Garnish with additional bean sprouts and carrots and some more fresh cilantro and green onion.

7 Dont forget to add the toasted cashews and mini lime wedge to finish!

8 Also, serve with a spring roll and some &quot;Nuoc Cham&quot; spring roll sauce.

***Note this stirfry happens very quickly and should take no longer than a minute****
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51272" image="">
Toast one half of a baguette with garlic butter on the flattop. 

Place a 160g scoop of whole wheat penne into the bowl. 

Add 130g of cheese sauce on top.

Sprinkle with 5g of parmesan crumble.

Top this by sprinkling with 2g of chopped parsley.

Stick the toasted garlic buttered baguette into the side of the bowl. 

***note- this makes a pasta portion with sauce and garnishes 300g total, before addition of the garlic bread.***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52984" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Gently heat bechamel on medium low heat.

2. Once bechamel is hot, add scaled out cheeses, whisking vigerously to incorporate cheese. turn off flame and ensure all cheese is fully melted.

3. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48840" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange in a bowl with rice in the base, the mixed chicken, veggie, sauce on top and finish with the  garnishes of green onion and roasted cashews.

Also gets one spring roll. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51301" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26759" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toss trimmed brussel sprouts in oil salt &amp; pepper

2. Place on parchment lined sheet trays in an even layer with space between

3. Roast in Oven @ 400F for approx 12-15 minutes untill roasted and lightly charring and cooked till tender inside.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50835" image="">

Combine everything except cornstarch and water in a pot and mix.

Bring to a boil over high heat, then reduce to a simmer.

Drizzle in a cornstarch slurry whilst stirring until desired consistency is reached. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53147" image="">1. Follow the BROTH|Udon recipe to make the base for the ramen first.
2. Toast the miso paste in a rondau for a few minutes to develop flavour. Until changes color a bit.
3. Incorporate into the main broth through a sive. DO NOT BOIL THE BROTH ONCE THE MISO IS IN! IT WILL MAKE YOUR BROTH SOUR!

Cool down.

Label, date, refregirate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47211" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-47234" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange attractively on a plate in the indicated proportions.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34541" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

*** for yeilding purposes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-8357" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Stretch dough

Spread cheese(s)

Apply toppings

Bake until the bottom is a mottled golden brown and cheese is bubbly and melted. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53744" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Combine everything in a pail and blend with giant handblender </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53965" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Boil potatoes until tender and drain thoroughly

Combine milk, cream and butter in a pot and bring to a simmer

Beat potatoes whip a whip on the stand mixer until they have broken apart

Now add the liquid and season to taste

No pepper is required, salt only

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53979" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Heat the large steam kettle to just below simmering

Blanch the vegetables then the noodles in hot simmering water for no longer than 30 seconds to 1 minute. (leave the vegetables in when blanching the noodles)

Strain and cool.

Mix in the seasonings.

Tray and label.

Bake to heat for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45444" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve the ingredients listed  in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46419" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Prepare all ingredients in advance.

Parsley is to be coarsely chopped and used quite abundantly, as though it were a green and not particularly a herb. 

Quarter sundried tomatoes.

 top flatbread with both cheeses, sundried tomatoes, and chickpeas. 

Bake until the crust is crispy and mottled golden brown underneath and cheese is melted.

Top the finished flatbread with the tahini drizzle and the coarsely chopped parsley. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51302" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE


1. Assemble all ingredients and garnishes first.

2. Soba noodles should be cold for this dish, as the hot broth will warm them up.

3. Put noodles in bowl, cover with broth portion. 

4. Put all garnishes on top.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46280" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients attractively on the plate in the proportions indicated. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51235" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Prepare a sheet pan with parchment paper. 

Place rockfish fillets on the sheet pan and sprinkle with salt and pepper and give a light drizzle of oil. 

Bake for 5-7 minutes or until fish is cooked throughout and flakes easily. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51236" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Please note, the rockfish portion is 90g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54344" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Mass to volume conversion recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51291" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-54387" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE



Apply toppings in the indicated proportions

Bake until bottom of crust is mottled golden brown, cheese is melted and crust is crisping around edges. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37780" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat the oven to 450F.

2. Toss the cauliflower with the lemon oil, salt &amp; pepper until evenly coated.

3. On a parchment lined baking sheet place cauliflower in even layer with space betwee eac piece (don&apos;t crowd pan or veg will steam rather than roast) roast until golden and tender; Aprox. 20 minutes. Transfer to a hotel pan for service.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55976" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot heat up the Dan Dan sauce.

2. Crumble up the Tempeh Either on a box grater or with a chef knife (looking for the same size/texture of ground pork)

3. Add the processed tempeh to the hot sauce and allow to cook out/reduce for 10-15 minutes allowing the sauce to become homogenous with the tempeh protien.

4. Place into hotel pans and hot hold for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54692" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Blanch spinach in salted water.

3. Chill in ice bath and then drain/squeeze well.

4. Set aside for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54849" image="">Prep Recipe:

This Beef should be stewed in the curry base



note: cook the lemongrass beef in the skillet, add the curry base and simmer for 1-2 hour until beef is tender.

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55559" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Put everything into a 20L Cambro and use the large hand blender to mix everything together.

3. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim all excess and cut the cauliflower in small     florettes
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26527" image="">1)  Place beets in perforated tray.  Steam beets until tender enough that a paring knife can be easily inserted into beet with little resistance.  Allow to cool.  When cool enough to handle, slip off skins and cut into bite sized portions.

2)  Season with salt and pepper and store in appropriate vessel.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56762" image="">Method:
- drain and rinse artichoke allow all excess moisture to drain off
- toss artichokes with olive oil, oregano &amp; basil
- hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56907" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Combine ponzu and sambal together (set aside)

2.Cut tofu into 1 inch by 1 inch cubes and place into ponzu/Sambal marinade. best to marinade overnight but good to use after 1 hour.

3.Remove tofu pieces from marinade and blot off exess marinade, toss in rice flour to coat shake off any excess flour and place evenly at the bottom of deep fryer basket (do not overcrowd basket as pieces will clump together and fyer tempature will drop to low) fry until golden brown (2-3 minutes) turn out onto paper lined baking sheet to drain off exess oil season lightly with kosher salt and serve immediately.
 * Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56909" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

 1.1/4&quot; Dice the tofu 

 2. Heat coconut oil in a non-stick pan and fry the tofu on medium heat about 5 minutes. Flip tofu and cook for another 5 minutes until both sides are browned.

 3. Combine all sauce ingredients in a bowl, whisk, and set aside. 

 4. Once tofu is cooked transfer to a plate.

 5. Add the sauce to the pan and heat on medium until bubbling. 

 6. Add tofu back into the pan with sauce and cook for 1 minute.

 7. Hot hold /  Serve immediately

 *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat a heavy pan over medium-high heat and add the canola and sesame oils.

2.  Add the beans and cook, stirring occasionally until they start to turn golden.

3.  Add the ginger, garlic, green onions, soy sauce, sugar and Sriracha and cook a few minutes more, stirring often, until the garlic is golden, the beans are deeper golden and the sauce has reduced and become sticky. The sauce should coat and cling to the beans well

4. Sprinkle with toasted sesame seeds.

Hot Hold/Serve imeediately

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-8355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Stretch dough to 16&quot;

2. Spread tomato sauce evenly across dough leaving a half inch boarder for the crust.

3. top with mozza cheese evenly covering the base of the dough.

4. place slices of boccancini across the base of the dough on top of the mozza.

5. Using a lightly floured peel transfer the raw pizza into the forno to bake (aprox 3-4 minutes) crust should be baked through and golden on the edges.

6. Again using the peel remove the fully baked pizza from the forno oven. On the cutting board using the pizza knife cut into 8 equal slices, carnish with fresh basil and serve imediately.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Stretch out the dough to 16&quot;

2. Spread the pesto evenly across the base of the dough leaving a half inch border for the crust.

3. Evenly spread the mozza across the dough covering the pesto. 

4. On top of the mozza spread out the artichokes, sauteed mushrooms, and chicken, try not to overlap the ingredents too much so all aspects are visual to the guest.

5. With a lightly floured peel, scoot the raw pizza into the forno oven and bake for 3-4 minutes (longer if needed) Crust should be cooked through and golden.

6. Again using the peel remove coocked pizza from the forno placing it on the cutting board, using the pizza knife cut into 8 even slices.

&amp;. Serve imediately and with kindness.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53848" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a mixing bowl; add kale, romaine and dressing. ensuring to evenly coat entire salad (do not over dress)

2. Garnish with parm and croutons (idealy these items do not go into the mixing bowl to keep it dairy and gluten free)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57148" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Lightly trim stem at the base

3. cut into apropriate size/shape for use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57149" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Lightly trim stem at the base

3. cut into apropriate size/shape for use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50588" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove just the tips/ends of the cucumber

2. Using a sharp knife,slice/chope cuke into desired shape and size appropriate for recipe use.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57191" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. discard unsavoury outer leaves

2.Remove core and discard

3. Cut and trim lettuce as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57233" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe: Various

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. in a perferated hotel pan inside a deeper non perforated hotel pan, place the already processed and cut to size for use broccoli florets.

2. place in the steamer and allow to steam for 6-8 minutes. Broccoli should be a vibrant green and still retain a crunch in the centre as it will be cooked further when added to other dishes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51527" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place all your rice noodles in a deep mixing bowl, (trying to snap as few of them as possible as you remove them from the package). Bring a good amount of water to boil. Pour the boiling water over the rice noodles until they are completely submerged. 

2.  Stir constantly to prevent clumping/sticking. When they are completely limp, give them a taste to see if they’re cooked through. The thread-like vermicelli noodles  will cook through in just a few minutes. The flat rice noodles might take upwards of ten minutes depending on thickness. Pay attention and test the noodles frequently because they’ll become mushy if they overcook.

3. Once the noodles are tender, drain them and run them under cool water to stop the cooking. Toss them with a small bit of sesame oil to keep the noodles from sticking to each other if you’re not going to use them right away. 

4. The noodles will be used in a stir-fry dish like pad thai, you definitely want to under-cook them a little bit. They will absorb more moisture and cook the rest of the way through once in the stir fry. If your noodles are perfectly cooked to start, they will turn to mush in the stir fry. 

NOTE: Even with a bit of sesame oil, the noodles still tend to clump up after you drain them. They will loosen again once you mix the noodles into your dish

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23935" image="">THIS RECIPE IS A RATIO ONLY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-30538" image="">This Recipe is a RATIO
-
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Pulse jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

*Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31944" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Rinse rice until water becomes clear, do not skip this step it is important!

2. Add the thuroughly rinsed rice &amp; veg stock to an apopriate sized pot. Bring to a boil on high heat while whisking to make sure the rice doesn&apos;t clump or stick to the bottom of the pot

3. Turn to medium-low heat and reduce to a simmer. Cover to keep the water at a boil without spilling over.

4. Simmer for 45-50 minutes until the desired texture / concistancy is achieved.

5. stir constantly in the last 10 minutes of cooking, the rice will become very sticky and scortch to the bottom if left unattended, or heat is too high.

6. Hot hold / serve with garnishes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45879" image="">
-Combine and mix well
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-31948" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image="">Cauliflower yields about 60% once processed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34666" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. on a parchment lined sheet pan place sausage in a even layer

2. cook at 350F untill cooked through

3. Cool and reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess oil.

use is associated recipes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10873" image="">
Place chicken onto pans and bake or roast until well done. 

Some of the marinade can be drained off if it is excessively &quot;wet&quot;. Also, some of the liquid that comes out of the chicken whilst cooking can be drained off if that will make it excessively &quot;wet&quot;.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47416" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. chips on one side of plate

2. Pico, sour cream and guac served on side


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52620" image="">Each lime gets cut into 8 equal wedges!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23151" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:
ALL SALES OFF OF SALAD BAR. THIS IS A RATIO NOT A RECIPE!!

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. MIX ALL LARGE PREP BATCHES AND STORE IN WALK IN FOR REPLENTISHING BAR


Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7139" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Mix the remaining ingredients.


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43719" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.  Put in fridge overnight to allow oats to soak up liquid.  Combine with other fruits/garnishes as indicated in recipes.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53993" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss diced Zucchini with oil and salt and pepper and roast on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned and hot throughout.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service. 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes

2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well

3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7420" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
SALAD BAR

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  cut brocco to uniform sized floretes
2. save stems for other recipes
3.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine and mix thouroughly

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62841" image="">each baguette makes 4 pieces for sandwiches</Recipe>
</Recipes>
