<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 320F

2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice.

3.  Slice each butt in half, and season pork with salt and pepper.  Make sure to get in all the cracks.

4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer on french top before putting it in the oven.

5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 3.5 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart

6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks, removing large pieces of fat. Add back some of braising liquid in pork to keep moist

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26144" image="">1. In large rondeau, heat canola oil over medium high heat. Add onion, pepper and garlic and saute until soft
2. Add Basmati rice and coat completely in oil and rice is beginning to toast about 5 minutes
3. Add cumin, oregano, paprika, salt &amp; pepper and tomato paste, cook 2 minutes
4. Add veg stock and beans, bring to a boil and reduce heat to low. Cover and simmer 30-50 minutes. Remove from heat. Keep covered and let stand five minutes. Fluff with fork
5. Allow to cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28363" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans.  Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-34024" image="">1. Place warm cauliflower wedge on plate.

2. Top with mushroom/ olive mixture.

3. Garnish with olive oil drizzle and sliced green onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35227" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP,  an in house made ingredient recipe
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix to smooth consistencey 
2. Send it
3.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Tacos
Bowls

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.slice shallot and dredge in potato starch mix
3.Shake off excess in a strainer
4.Fry once at 310 until bubbles stop and shallot float
5. remove from and let cool on a resting rack turning the fryer up to 350 when they are out
6. whenthey are cool, re-fry at 350 until golden brown
7.place on paper towel to absorb excess oil
8.place in container on a service towel, label and use for TWO DAYS ONLY 

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43635" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Fish/Shellfish
Sulphites
Method:

1)  Put  chicken thighs in large cambro.

2)  Add remaining ingredients to appropriate sized sauce pan.  Simmer until sugar dissolves.  Allow to cool.

3)  Pour marinade over chicken thighs.  Allow to marinate overnight.

4)  If not using immediately, remove thighs from marinade and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43707" image="">1)  Combine well, store in appropriate container, cover with cheese cloth and leave out at room temperature for about 8-12 hours, until desired thickenss is reached.  Reserve in fridge for up to 2 weeks.

Allergens:

Dairy/Milk</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43747" image="">1)  Shuck corn and cut in half.  Preheat oven to 425*F.  In large mixing bowl, cover in oil and salt and pepper, chili powder, paprika and tajin seasoning.

2)  Put corn on parchment lined baking sheet and roast for 15-20 minutes, turning every 10 minutes until corn is nicely charred.  

3)  Combine creme fraiche, mayo and garlic puree.  Mix well.

4)  Combine roasted corn with creme fraiche and mayo mixture.  Taste for seasoning.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43928" image="">1) Tear up kale or remove from stems with a knife.  Discard stems. Rough chop kale leaves.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onion and saute for 2-3 minutes.  Add chili flakes, garlic and ginger.  Saute for 30 seconds.  

3)  Add kale leaves and coconut milk.  Bring to a simmer, and simmer for 10 minutes or until kale is tender.  

4)  Hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Saute the onions and pureed lemon grass until translucent, add ginger and garlic and cook out for another 5 minutes. Add sugar and cook for another 5 minutes.

3. Add Green Curry Paste and cook out for another 5 minutes to develop flavour.

4. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer, add lime leaves and season.

5. Thicken with slury, thicken so that sauce coats the back of a spoon and sticks.

6. Add lime juice just before you take it off the heat.

7. Throw in the thai basil and cilantro and blend in the sauce to give it it&apos;s green color.******

****** If you are making the sauce for the next day, DO NOT add the cilantro/thai basil as it will go brown and discolor.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44975" image="">Portion out 175g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45020" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45021" image="">1)  Make coconut kale as per recipe.

2)  Use a #6 scoop to portion coconut kale.  One scoop = one portion.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Method:
1.Combine ingredents up to 3 days in advance.
-store, label and rotate

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45190" image="">Salad portion is 160g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45191" image="">Salad portion is 160g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45744" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46593" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Add oil to saute pan.  Once oil is hot, add onion and saute until soft.

2)  Add corn and continue sauteing until no longer frozen.  Add refried beans and reserve for making tacos.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46864" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Be sure to make shred from other Iceberg lettuce preps
3. evenly slice lettuce 3 mm thick
4. Cover with wet brown paper towel to stop oxidization   

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-49262" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50377" image="">1. Put oil in a tilt skillet and get very hot, add the beef and saute until browned on all sides, remove beef and reserve.

2. Using the remaining oil in the skillet, add the onion, pepper and garlic and sautee for 3-4mins or until softened and garlic has browned.

3. Add the beef to the pot and tomato paste and sautee 5-10 minutes until tomato paste is cooked out, 

4. Add soya sauce, bay leaf and chilli flakes and mix thoroughly while sauteing, on meduim heat while stirring.

5. Deglaze with the beef broth, bring to a boil and then simmer until beef is tender.

6. Add the potatoes, peas and carrots to the pot and cook until potatoes are cooked through.

8. Taste and adjust seasoning as required, place in proper vessle for cooling and storing, lable, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50418" image="">1.Shred papaya.
2.Thinly slice carrots,ginger and bell pepper(fine julienne)
3.Soak Papaya with water and 4Tbs salt for 2 days.
4. Put the Papaya in a cheesecloth in a way that is trapped in the center. Gently rotate the cheesecloth until the papaya completey releases liquid. Do this more than once for better result.
5. Make the syrup by heating the venigar in a cooking pot. Once it starts to boil, add sugar and 1 teaspoon salt. Mix well and cook for 1-3 minutes.
6. Gently pour the hot syrup in the container. Quick close the lid. This will somewhat cook the papaya and veggfies and will make it a bit softer.
7. Let it cool and refrigerate.
8. Serve it cold.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50434" image="">Julinenne Chayote. shave radish, peel and cube avocado, chop cilantro. 

In a bowl, add lime juice, honey, cayenne, salt and oil. mix well. 

Add all vegetable and herb ingredients into the bowl, mix then place salad in refrigerator with label. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50439" image="">Fry, drain oil on paper towel &amp; season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50440" image="">Place Chayote salad and black beans, feta and lettuce on fried tortilla shell and serve immediatly. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50446" image="">1. Dice tofu, Coat with cornstarch and deep fry until golden brown and outside is crispy but soft inside. Set aside.
2) Peel potato cut 1/3 medium dice and blanch in hot oil  set aside.
3) In a big pot over medium heat into oil add annatto seeds and cook until the oil is infused with color and then  remove seeds with a slotted spoon.
4) Add Onion into the annatto then cook until soften and add garlic and cloves; stir well
5) Add tomatoes, simmer for 5 minutes 
6) Add all ingredients, bring to boil and reduce heat continue to simmer until vegetables are almost cooked and sauce is thickend.  Add tofu and season with salt and pepper to taste. 
7. Serve over rice and garnish with crispy shallots.

Portion Size: 4oz Laddle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50450" image="">1. In a bowl of rice. Scoop vegan menudo with the green scoop( 4oz) and put on top of rice.
2. Garnish with crispy shallots.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50509" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50560" image="">Prepare all sub recipes


Spread refried beans and put other ingredients on top of each other, First, pulled pork, lettuce iceberg, pico de gallo, cheese, sour cream and radish.

Garnish with cilantro and limes on the side.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50690" image="">1. Pre heat oven 375F.
2. In a baking sheet, lay flat cashew.
3. Roast it for about 8-10minutes or until golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51263" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51309" image="">1. Place warm cauliflower wedge on plate.

2. Top with mushroom/ olive mixture.

3. garnish with olive oil drizzle and sliced green onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51310" image="">1. Place warm cauliflower wedge on plate.

2. Top with mushroom/ olive mixture.

3. Garnish with olive oil drizzle and sliced green onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51313" image="">Layer ingredients in the proportions indicated. 

Sequence the toppings in this order

Tostada, beans, lettuce, chayote salad, crumbled feta, shaved radish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51316" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56849" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Soak papaya in cold water overnight (this will keep it crispy).

2. Bruise papaya.

3. Add carrot, green beans.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Soak papaya in cold water overnight 9this will keep it crispy).

2. Bruise papaya.

3. Add prepped papaya, carrot &amp; bean mixture with tomatoes (cut in half) to mixing bowl.

4. Add dressing and toss to combine.

5. Plate, ensuring you leave some tomato and beans to place on top of salad.

6. Garnish with toasted cashews.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57369" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. First mix in a bowl olives (cut in half), orange juice, lemon juice and chopped parsley. Set aside.

2. Heat saute pan over medium/high heat. Add olive oil and sliced mushrooms. Season with salt and pepper and saute until softened (3-5 mins).

3. Add shallots and garlic and continue cooking, stirring often. 

4. Turn off heat and add olive mixture, capers and mint stirring to combine.

5. Adjust seasoning with salt &amp; pepper and lemon for balance.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58863" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

Preheat oven to 325F

1. Remove all outer leaves and trim stem (you need some stem to keep the steaks together).Trim right and left sides. Cut in centre to form 2 thick steaks. 

2. In a large sheet pan drizzle olive oil and harissa and mix. Rub both sides of both steaks in mixture.

3. In a large roasting pan/ tilt skillet sear both sides until you get a golden brown crust.

4. Transfer to sheet pans and roast in oven (approx. 10-12 minutes) or until a pairing knife will slide easily into stem.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60816" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Soak chili&apos;s in hot tea water for 15 minutes.

2. Drain water and blend everything together.

 store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
