<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9519" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather all ingredients.

2.Blend in food processor.

3.Put in container label place in fridge.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:na

Utensils needed:food processor cutting board scale container

ALLERGENS
-NONE

Icon:

n/a- just a sauce

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9863" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Tip/tail the leeks save the green tips for other preps
2. Soak in cold water to rinse off dirt
3. cut to desired shape
4. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water from the pan runs clear

2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

4) Season with salt &amp; pepper. 

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26184" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Soak navy beans overnight. Ensure they are covered by at least 3&quot;. Drain beans, cook until tender, strain again and reserve water

2. Sautee diced onion, salt and house rub. Cook until onions are soft and fragrant

3. Add remaining ingredeints and bring to a simmer. Add beans and continue simmering until beans are totally cooked and flavourful. Season with more salt and pepper, mix if necessary

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26323" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In saute pan over medium heat, toast peppercorns and fennel until fragrant.  Allow to cool and grind in spice grinder.  Add chili flakes and reserve.  

2)  Combine parsley, cilantro, garlic cloves, canola oil, lemon juice and cumin.  Blitz into a paste with robot coupe.  Reserve.

3)  Combine herb paste with fennel, peppercorns and chili flakes and S&amp;P.  

4)  Reserve for porchetta.

* An 8 oz. recipe will make enough for 2 (two) porchetta.
.


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  With pork belly skin side down, rub belly with Porchetta Rub generously.  

2)  Roll belly into a tight log.  You may need a buddy to help you hold the belly in place.  Tie butchers knots on each end of porchetta than one good tie in the middle to secure.  Continue making butchers knots 1&quot; apart until fully tied.

3)  Combine kosher salt and baking powder.  Rub over skin of porchetta.

4)  Store in fridge, uncovered for at least 24 hours, or up to 3 days.

5)  Preheat oven to 300*F.  Place porchetta seam side down on cooling rack inside of roasting rack.  Roast until internal temperature of 60*C (140*F) is reached.

6)  Increase oven temperature to 500*F and roast for 20-30 minutes until skin is blistered and very crispy.

7)  Rest for 15 minutes and serve.  


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28340" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29172" image="">1)  Make quinoa as per recipe.

2)  Make lemon garlic dressing as per recipe.

3)  Combine remaining ingredients and serve on salad bar, or label, date, refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32665" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 450*F

2)  Spread diced pineapple on baking sheet.  Roast @ 450*F, stirring to distribute product until pineapple begins to caramalize, about 15-20 minutes.  Allow to cool.

3)  Combine roasted pineappl ewiht chopped cilantro and diced onion.  Hold cold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33738" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor, add garlic, lemon juice and S+P.  

2)  With blade of food processor running, slowly add oil to create a temporary emulsion.  Taste dressing for seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans.  Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35810" image="">1)  Rough chop kale and swiss chard.  Remove coarse stems.  Reserve for recipe.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot add onion and saute for about 5 minutes or until soft.  Add paprika, garlic puree and thyme and saute for 1 minute more.

3)  Add chopped tomatoes and habaneros and continue sauteing for 3 minutes.  Add kale and chard.  Season.  Remove from heat when kale and chard are tender.  Hold for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35815" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-35869" image="">Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37055" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-37056" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40972" image="">* This recipe makes 100 portions of salmon.  Scale up accordingly.

1)  Combine portioned salmond pieces, marinade.  Allow to marinate overnight.

2)  Preheat rationale oven to 100% steam.  Steam salmon in hotel pans to 50*C (122*F).  Remove immidiately about 4 minutes.

3)  Prior to service, heat sauce to a simmer.  Keep warm for service.

4)  Use to season salmon by pouring a tbsp. over top.  Pour hot sauce over fish to finish.  Hold hot for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41073" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41084" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41085" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-41086" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41727" image="">
Portion = 210g (6 floz ladle)

Cube and toss butternut squash &amp; yams with oil, salt &amp; pepper

Boil red lentils until soft and falling apart.

Mix together roasted veg, cooked lentils, tomato sauce and stock.
Place in insert and heat slowly to prevent burning

adjust seasoning with salt &amp; pepper, fold in fresh parsley, chard &amp; kale once hot


Garnish with chopped cilantro

Portion size: 6Oz over rice



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43680" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pot over medium low heat, add oil.  

2)  Process garlic as you normally would in food processor, but stop before a fine paste forms.  You want chunky bits of garlic.

3)  Add garlic bits for warm oil and fry, stirring frequently for 4-5 minutes until garlic is crispy.  Strain through fine mesh strainer and reserve oil.  Place cripsy garlic on papertowel to soak up excess oil.

4)  Once dry, place crispy garlic in appropriate container, lined with papertowel and lid tightly.  Garlic can be stored at room temperature for about 3 days.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Spread the brocoll evenlly on perforated pans
3. Steam untill aldente (4 min)

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Steamer, perforated hotel pans 2&quot;
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44510" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45386" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46503" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat the oven to 450F.

2. Toss the processed squash with the oil, salt &amp; pepper until evenly coated.

3. On a parchment lined baking sheet place seasoned squah in even layer with space betwee each piece (don&apos;t crowd pan or veg will steam rather than roast) roast until golden and tender; Aprox. 20 minutes. Transfer to a hotel pan for service.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49349" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 300*F.

1)  Combine dry ingredients (onion powder, black pepper, smoked paprika, garlic powder, nutritional yeast and wheat gluten) in a mixing bowl and reserve.

2)  Make veg stock as per recipe and add tomato paste and liquid smoke.  Bring to a simmer and allow to cool.

3) Add veg stock and water to dry ingredients and work into a dough.  Once everything is combined, knead the dough for about 5-8 minutes.  If making a big batch, you can use the hobart mixer with the dough hook attachement to do this.

4)  On a parchment lined baking tray, using a rolling pin, stretch the &apos;dough&apos; until it&apos;s even height ( about 1&quot;) on the baking tray. 

5)  Bake at 300*F for about 20-25 minutes.

6)  Brush with reserved BBQ sauce and continue baking for another 5 minutes or so.

7) Sear the ribs on the flat top at 350*F about 3 minutes each side.

8)  Cut &apos;ribs&apos; into 125 g portions and reserve for service.

  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-49499" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-49500" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-49501" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-49656" image="">Method:
dry portions of Rockfish
dust with Cajun Seasoning
in hot pan, heat oil
sear fish portions to set seasoning crust - do not cook through
place seared fish on sheet pan
when ready for service, cook in 450f oven for 2-3 min
remove from heat
serve

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50343" image="">1) In large pot or tilt kettle over medium heat, melt the butter, then add the diced onion, saute till translucent then add garlic and cook about 1 more minute.

2) Then add the mushroom and saute till starting to brown, add in the leek, red pepper, carrot, bite sized kale and saute, till cooked and kale starts to wither.  Add in the smoked paprika and cayenne pepper, stir well to coat the veg.

3) Add in the diced tomatoes and cook out some of the liquid. Then add the milk and cream stir well. Once the the sauce comes to a simmer, thicken with corn starch slurry until it&apos;s a heavy cream consistancy.

4) Finish with the lemon juice, season with salt and pepper to taste. Cool sauce, then label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50406" image="">Portion = 210g
Garnish with chopped cilantro</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50424" image="">1) Coat mushrooms in oil and seasoning. Preheat oven to 375f.

2) Place mushrooms on parchment lined baking sheets evenly, only single layer, use multiple pans if needed, place whole rosemary and thyme sprigs over mushrooms. 

3) Roast in oven about 15 mintues, carefully drain excess mushroom juices from the pan,  and respread out mushrooms if needed. Return to oven and continue roasting an other 30 minutes, or until mushrooms are brown and tender.

4) Toss with chopped parsley and move to hot holding vessel. Hold hot for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50473" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
-Short Rib Papperdelle
-Boneless Beef Shortrib

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Season beef with salt and pepper.  Preheat oven to 225*F.

2)  In rondo or tilt skillet over high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add beef and sear well on all sides, and place in hotel pan.

3) In same rondo or skillet sweat onion, garlic and carrot stirring often until fragrant.

4) Add tomato paste and stir 1-2 minutes.

5) Add red wine vinegar and beef stock and bring to a boil.

6)  Place warm liquid over beef until it comes about half way up side of beef.  Place parchment paper on top and cover with lid.  Place in preheated oven and braise overnight or until very tender.

7)  Remove from oven and let cool down in liquid.  Strain braising liquid and reduce until thick and almost syrupy, about 2/3&apos;s.  Reserve.  Taste for seasoning.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51279" image="">Prepare the sauce and fish as per sub recipes.

To finish and plate the dish; place a piece of roasted fish on plate, top with sauce and top that with the salad shrimp.

**the salad shrimp does not need to be heated up**</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51461" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61306" image="">1) Cut tofu in to 150g, steak style portions. (long flat rectangles)

2) Season with salt, pepper and oil. Grill to add grill marks.

3) Cool and keep for service time. Service time, heat to 74c and keep for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62501" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. All veg should be 1/4&quot; dice (except jalapenos which can be minced).

2. Adjust seasoning and keep cool.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
