<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and stirring.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine water and salt in a large pot.  Bring to a boil.

2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.  This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1)  In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

2)  Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26883" image="">

-Cook noodles for 5 mins in the steamer or
-Cook noodles for 3 mins in boiling water at the station</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35255" image="">1) Cut cucumber in quarters lenght wise, cut out seads.

2) Cut remaining pieces in to 1.5 inch lenght pieces and cut in to 1/16th inch sticks.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: soy
Method:

1)  Combine kombu, ginger, garlic, star anise and water.  Bring to a boil, then remove from heat and allow to infuse for a few hours, or preferably overnight.  

2)  Add miso and bring back up to heat, ensuring to stir often until miso is disolved and broth is hot.  Add tofu and soy sauce.  Taste for seasoning. (80*C at least)

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35319" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Miso Dumpling Soup.jpg">1. Heat the broth, bak choy, gyoza, mushrooms and the noodles.

2. Assemble all of the ingredients in the bowl.

3. Garnish with green onion, radish and chili oil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides.  Allow to cool.

2)  Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender.  Blend well until combined into a paste.  Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

3)  Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix.  Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame seeds and Korean chili flakes.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43737" image="">1)  Bring water to a rapid boil in an appropriate sized pot.  Gently lower eggs into boiling water with a slotted spoon.

2)  Cover pot with aluminum foil and turn heat off completely.  Allow eggs to sit in hot water for 8-9 minutes.  

3)  Strain eggs, and shock in ice bath to stop eggs from cooking further and to make them easier to peel.

4)  When eggs are completly cool, peel them.

5)  Egg whites should be fully cooked, and yolk should be slightly runny.

6)  Store in appropriate contianer.  Label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Egg

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43738" image="">1)  Prep soba noodles as per recipe, and portion.

2)  Prepare Dobanjiang Sauce as per recipe.

3)  Place chilled soba noodles in mixing bowl and mix well with dobanjiang sauce.  Place noodles in serving bowl and garnish with remaining vegetables. Zigzag a squirt of sauce on top of vegetables, then garnish with sesame and nori and soft boiled egg. Cut the egg in half and present the cut side. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43918" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

***This recipe does not need to be heated, put all of the ingredients in a bowl and whisk well.***

1. Combine all well. 

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in: Meatball sub 

Method:

1. Begin by sauteing onion until soft and staring to brown then add garlic and cook it out till it becomes fragrant. Reserve.

2. Cook lentils until soft and mash before adding into the mixture. DRAIN THOROUGHLY. Allow to steam out.

3. Make sure both cooked components are completely chilled down prior to adding to meat mixture.

4. Mix thoroughly, Cook a small piece and taste for seasoning, adjust as necassary.

5. Form into meatballs and chill thoroughly.

MEATBALL PORTION SIZE SHOULD BE 55g RAW- USE THE BLACK HANDLED PORTION SCOOP. CHECK WEIGHTS!

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49176" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Preheat oven to 425F
2. Toss diced sweet potato in oil &amp; seasoning.
3. Cook 10-12 minutes until tender.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.

Makes topping for 9 portions
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52096" image="">1. Assemble all the ingredients.
2. Heat your rondeau so that it&apos;s super hot.
3. Put your onions in followed by the oil - the onions cool down the skillet just enough so that the oil doesn&apos;t start burning or catches fire on you.
4. Turn down the heat to medium/low and continue cooking out the onions until golden/caramelized. Season with salt+pepper.
5. Add the brown sugar last just before you take the onins off the stove.

Cool, label, date, refrigirate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61735" image="">1) Prebake flatbread first in deck oven for 4-5 minutes until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread are golden brown before putting any toppings on.

2) After baking &amp; cooling lightly coat bottom of flatbread with cream cheese/ sour cream mixture, cooked bacon strips and thinly sliced white onion.

3) When you get an order warm flatbread in deck oven for 1 minute.

4) Take it off from oven cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61737" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with tomato sauce.

2) Evenly lay cooked meatball mix, caramalized onions then mozzarella.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Garnish with rough chopped parsley.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61743" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread cheese sauce, caramelized onions &amp; roasted sweet potatoes.

3. Spread cheese over entire surface.

4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

5. Take out of oven.

7. Garnish with chopped sage.

8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64880" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using mandoine slice cucmbers into 0.5 cm discs.
2. Toss in salt and pace over a drip pan for 2-3 hours.
3. Meanwhie simmer remaining ingredients and cool completely.
4. Transfer cucumbers to a cambro and pour enough pickling liquid to cover. Place parchment or plastic wrap on top.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64881" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Soak cashews in cold water overnight OR pour boiing water over and let sit 1 hour. Drain and rinse.
2. Cut and steam potatoes and carrots until very soft. Reserve.
3. Working in batches in large robot coupe puree mixture until smooth.
NOTE: You may have to add a bit of water to get it smooth but you don&apos;t want it to be runny.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64882" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Dessed jalapenos.

2. Combine all ingredients in a wide rondo, bring to a boil and simmer stirring occasionally until thick.

NOTE: It wil get thicker once cooled so don&apos;t reduce too much. You can put a small amount on a plate and wait a couple minutes for it too cool to check it&apos;s consistency.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64883" image="">1) Lightly season patty with salt &amp; pepper.

2) Place on oiled flattop and press down fairly hard with metal spatula. Make sure burger doesn&apos;t flatten wider than the bun. After 1 minute or so carefully flip burger and press down again.

3) Meanwhile toast bun then spread vegan mayo on both sides. Place tomato jam on bottom of bun.

4) Place seared &amp; cooked burger on top of tomato jam, top with vegan cheese sauce, 4 slices of the pickles and a leaf of iceburg lettuce.</Recipe>
</Recipes>
