<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredents
2.place in food processor, process till smooth
3.place in cambro label and date
4. refridgerate
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim all excess and cut the cauliflower in small     florettes
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9778" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry
2.process as needed
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9782" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry tomato
2.Cut by hand or if doing big amount then. Put together R2 with proper slicing and dicing blades
3.place insert and perferated pan under to catch the diced tomato and to strain excess liquid
4. once done lable and place in fridge
5. Clean R2 parts by hand and return to office.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:60g

Utensils needed:blue scoop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13881" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and wash
3.label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
serving dish

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18874" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:

Cut eggplants in half lengthwise.
Place on baking sheet face down and cook in oven on high heat.
When thoroughly cooked set aside to cool.
When still warm and able to picked up, scoop out the flesh from the eggplant and place in robocoupe.
Puree till smooth and add minced garlic and remaining ingredients.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24618" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Lightly butter one side of naan

2. place on p0archment lined sheet tray

3. Pop into 400F oven for 5-6 minutes to toast/warm and melt butter

4. Reserve for service


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26847" image="">Prep:

- Combine Butter Chicken Base sauce, and Chicken thighs in the quantities mentioned.

- Let simmer for 3 hours (if possible). This recipe should simmer for at least 3 hours - </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26885" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. mix all ingredients in a hotel pan

2. Place in steamer

3. Cook untill done (aprox 15-20 minutes)

4. VERY IMPORTANT *Fluff rice imediately and put on sheet pan to cool properly or use imediately, but do not forget to fluff the rice or the bottom half will be mush and over cooked!!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Mince mint

2. Mix all ingredents thuroughly

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-31042" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Crispy fry the samosa till golden and cooked/heated all the way through.

2. serve with chutney on the side.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32656" image="">1)  Bring water up to a boil.  Add concentrate.  Stir throughly to combine.  Use immidiately or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Over medium heat in tilt kettle or large rondeau, add oil.  Once hot, add onion and saute until beginning to soften, about 5 minutes.  Add garlic and saute 1 minute more.

2.  Add spices and continue to saute onion until spices are fragrant, about 5 minutes more.

3.  Add tomato and lentils and contine sauting until everything is combined.

4.  Add veg stock and simmer partially covered for 20-30 minutes until lentils are soft, but not mushy.  Season to taste.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

Dairy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35823" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut potatoes in half then steam until tender, about 15 minutes.

2. On medium low heat, add oil to large rondeau.  Add cumin seeds and toast until fragrant, 30 seconds to 1 minute.  Add onion, coriander, chili powder, turmeric, jalapeno and garam masala.  Saute until onion is soft and spices are fragrant.  

3. Add garlic and ginger and saute for 1 minute more. 

4. Add tomato paste and saute for 4 minute.  Add diced tomatoes and saute 1 minute more.

5. Add fenugreek, lime juice and fresh coriander and stir well to combine.

6. Adjust seasoning.

7. NOTE: Add cooked potatoes and cauliflower during REHEATING for service for best results.

8. Stir well to combine.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35848" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Zest and juice your 2 lemons.

2. Finely chop dill.

3. Process Cucumbers. These should be pulsed in the RoboCoupe. PULSED - NOT LEFT ON TO BECOME A SOUP. What you want is something about the consistency of a small dice. When this is done, transfer this mixture into a bowl with Cheese Cloth. RING OUT AS MUCH WATER AS YOU CAN. THIS WATER IS DELICIOUS. I RECOMMEND DRINKING IT FOR ITS ELECTROLYTE PROPERTIES. Unfortunately, it just doesn&apos;t belong in the Yoghurt in this recipe, as it would turn into Cacic.

4. Combine lemon juice and garlic. Let sit for 10 minutes. Salt this mixture to &quot;cook out&quot; the garlic as much as possible.

5. Fold all ingredients into one another. Taste for Salinity, Acidity, and add honey if the Sweetness needs a little kick.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



NOTES: It&apos;s important to note that this is an opportunity for using old or slightly old Cucumber! For instance: look at the recipe for Taboulleh Salad Mix - Cucumber cores should be saved, and then processed and strained in Cheese Cloth for this recipe - otherwise it will be too watery.

In Turkey, there is a dish known as Cacic - a watery version of Tzatziki. The ingredients are more or less the same. What we know as Tzatziki is actually made with Labneh, which is pressed Yoghurt. Since we use regular Yoghurt in this recipe, we have to limit the amount of water content in it, otherwise it will be an undesirable AND low-quality product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36043" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of Aloo Gobi in small serving bowl

2. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Beef Vindaloo
Chickpea Vindaloo

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Over medium/ low heat in large rondeau, add oil, cinnamon and onions and cook till nearly carmalized and golden brown.

2)  Add ginger, garlic, seeded jalapenos and cook until peppers are soft.

3) Add tomato paste and cook, stirring often until it is a deep, dark brown.

4) Add ground dry spices and vindaloo paste and cook for 10 minutes, or until spice is cooked out. Taste to ensure that the spices are cooked out. 

5)  Add water, diced tomatoes and juice, salt, lemon juice and brown sugar.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

6)  Remove from heat, remove cinnamon sticks.  Puree with immersion blender. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at base of bowl

2. Place warm portion of dahl beside rice and garnish with a piece of naan offside.

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-41669" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. crispy fry the samosa, till golden and cooked/heated through 

2. Serve with a side of chutney

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42319" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter.  Once oil and butter are warm, add garlic, ginger and crushed chili.  Saute for 2-3 minutes.

2. Add all spices except salt and sugar.  Continue sauteing until spices are cooked out, about another 5 minutes.  

3. Add crushed tomato, salt and sugar.  Bring to a simmer.

4. Add water and bring back to a simmer.  Add cream and kasoori methi.  

5. Taste for seasoning.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42320" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine yogurt and spices. Mix to combine well.  Reserve marinade.

2. Cut Paneer into 1&quot; cubes and pour marinade over top.  Combine gently to get the marinade over all the paneer chunks.  Allow to marinate at least 2 hours or overnight(best).

3. Preheat oven to 500*F.  Place paneer on foil lined baking sheets.  Broil for 5 minutes or until paneer turns golden brown.  Reserve for making Paneer Tika Masala

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42356" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Make Paneer gravy as per recipe.

2. Make and broil paneer as per recipe.

3. Blanch green peas in hot water, and shock in cold water.  Reserve for paneer tikka masala.

4. Thin out gravy with a bit of water and bring to a simmer.  When warm, combine broiled paneer, peas and paneer sauce.  Hold warm for service.

*This recipe should make enough for one shallow hotel pan/cassrole serving vessel..

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42817" image="">ALLERGENS: MUSTARD

Prep: 

1. Clean and cut Potatoes into large uniform shapes and sizes. Each Potato may yield 6 pieces, if cut properly - about the same style as Homestyle Potatoes. Steam these in the combi oven until soft but not crumbling apart - use the steam setting: check after 30 minutes.

2. Cut the Cauliflower into florets, and deep fry until golden brown - then set aside. Rough Chop Onions, and set aside your Ginger and Garlic. While you&apos;re doing this, set aside your spices - to be used at the beginning of the cooking process. Also, set aside your 4 litres of Water (though, it may not be necessary).

5. In the Tilt Skillet, starting with Canola Oil - start to saute your onions (towards caramelized). Then, throw in your spices, and saute them as well - before adding your Garlic and Ginger.

6. As soon as you add your Garlic and Ginger, you&apos;re going to want to deglaze the Tilt Skillet by adding up to 3 litres of the water you set aside. At this point you can add your Turmeric, Garam Masala, Mustard, and canned Tomatoes. 

7. Let simmer for a few minutes before adding the fried Cauliflower, and Potatoes. Turn up the heat on the skillet at this point, and scrape the bottom of the skillet with the mixing paddle to accumulate caramelized sugars therein that will burn if left unincorporated. Use the remaining water in this recipe, or more, if need be - keep it moving! You&apos;re near the end here.

8. Turn the temperature down on the Tilt Skillet. Rough Chop the Cilantro and Mint. Cut the Serrano Peppers thinly on a mandoline, and then throw all of these ingredients into the mixture. 

9. Season to taste at this point - the salt in this recipe is roughly 1.2% of recipe weight. You may find that you need more.

10. Finish with lime juice before serving. This could change depending on how you&apos;re doing your batches - but the finished product should be given acidity with lime juice prior to serving regardless of how this dish interacts with the Hot Holds.

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43656" image="">ALLERGENS: MUSTARD

Prep:

- Weigh out all ingredients.
- Set aside Sugar and Salt.

- Toast all Spices / Seeds, until fragrant. This would be done at a higher heat that the next step. 
- Toast Split Peas separately - low heat.

- Mix all ingredients together, and take to the Vitamix. Grind into a fine powder.

Label / Date / Store Appropriately.

Note: when cooking with this, it&apos;s important to fry out the Split Pea in this recipe. It cannot be used simply as a spice mix like others - Baharat (which just means Spice in Turkish and a few other Middle Eastern dialects), Ras Al Hanout, etc. - it needs to be partially cooked. This does wonders for the spice elements. But, it also takes the grainy-ness out of the Split Peas (important).

Any questions, Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44082" image="">ALLERGENS: WHEAT, GLUTEN

Prep:

- Take the Coriander Seeds, Cumin Seeds, Ajwain Seeds, Black Pepper and Garam Masala - and toast, then grind in the Vitamix into a fine powder. The toasting, as mentioned in other recipes, is key to developing flavour and aroma.

- Amchur Powder is not a spice, but a powder made of green mango. It should not be toasted. Opinions differ on this, but - for this recipe, do not toast this ingredient.

- Normally this recipe would be made into a paste with lemon juice and a small amount of water. We use this as a more dry rub, in combination with alread-wet ingredients like potatoes that have been boiled and chickpeas that sit in &quot;aqua fava&quot; (literally: bean water).

- If this spice mix is low, talk to a Chef about it. Some of these ingredients come from a specialty provider with an indented delivery schedule - and will need to be ordered several days in advance in order to allow for proper prep time.

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44367" image="">Allergens:
milk

Icons:
vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
place 150ml portion of Tzaziki into ramekin

serve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44410" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTES: 
This recipe should be as green as possible - meaning: stewing the green elements of this recipe too far will kill the flavour and visual appeal of the recipe. The idea of this recipe is to have a flavourful earthy base to balance out the fats present in the Paneer (which is to be added last). 

Prep:

1. Cut the root ends off of the Green Onions, and then grill them until coloured. Cool, and then chop up in pieces that are no less than 3 inches long.

2. Rough Chop Onions, and begin cooking them out immediately. Throw in Spices(toast spices) Garlic, and Ginger. Deglaze with veg stock. Season and simmer for 5-10 minutes. 

3. Cut Paneer into bite-sized cubes - nothing too big. It will cut like Tofu, but it will also flake off..

4.  Add HALF of the Spinach in the recipe, and cover for 5 minutes. You want the Spinach to be cooked out, but not to the point of bitterness. At this point, the recipe is very close to being taken off heat.

5.  Add the Cilantro. Then, using an Immersion Blender, puree the Spinach and its juices into a sauce. This does not have to be a uniform puree as it would come out of a Vitamix - a little bit of texture is OK. Taste &amp; check for seasoning.

6. Add Chopped Green Onions (grilled), Paneer, the other half of the Spinach, and the Cilantro - season again to taste using the salt in this recipe. Turn off heat.

7. Add Yogurt before moving this recipe intoserving pans. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44414" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: Dairy
Method:

1. Place warm portion (120g) in small bowl

2. ensure a good sauce to paneer ratio!

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44422" image="">
Prep:

- In the skillet add oil, sautee onions until caramelized, and then toast Spices in the onions 
-  add Garlic and Ginger, cook out for 10 mins
- add the Tomatoes,and water to deglaze skillet and begin simmering for 30 mins

-  Add Butter, and Cream. Simmer further for 15mins

- Check seasoning, and then take off heat 

-Reserve what is needed for serve, or COOL AS FAST AS POSSIBLE what&apos;s not needed

  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44790" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Grab can 
2.open
3.Drain and rinse
4.place in container label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45069" image="">Allergens:
sesame

Icons:
vegan, vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47957" image="">ALLERGENS: MUSTARD

Notes: This recipe is all about timing. It can easily be done on the side, without hassle, while other recipes are in development. There are key areas that require direct supervision - the rest can be managed by raising or lowering heat, and intelligently employing different equipment to serve different functions throughout the recipe. 

Prep:

- Turn on the Tilt Skillet - as high as it will go.

- Soak Yellow Split Peas overnight. Soak in a stock if possible. IF you soak in a stock, place the stock and the split peas in a couple of shallow trays and throw them in the steamer. Ideal cook time: 2 Hours.

- Have your onions ready, as well as your 5 Spice Mix, and your Ginger and Garlic - BEFORE YOU ADD OIL TO THE TILT SKILLET.  Add oil, and immediately put your onions in there. You might want to even add some water to avoid burning if you have too much going on at once. Drop the temperature of the skillet to 350F/180C, and let simmer (if you added water), until there is almost no moisture left. 

- Add your 5 Spice and Garam Masala, and saute out thoroughly. Rememeber there is blitz&apos;d up Yellow Split Peas in the 5 Spice itself, so it needs toasting. After this, add your Butternut Squash, and deglaze with your water. You may need to add more water to this recipe - 10L should be considered the minimum.

- Raise the temperature of the skillet if you need to now, to make sure that you&apos;re boiling your Butternut Squash. It will take about 30-40 minutes to cook out depending on circumstances. Add your curry leaves, and Sprouted Pulses. Reserve Green Onions, Cilantro, and Kale until last for your Coconut Milk finish.

- At this point, check your Yellow Split Peas. They need to be done. They will likely be &quot;al dente&quot;, but that&apos;s OK. Add them to the mixture, and cook them with the Squash. They are now your indicator as to how you&apos;re doing - the Squash may finish before the Split Peas. 

- Season to taste. Add Coconut Milk VERY LAST, along with Cilantro and Green Onions. Check Seasoning. 

Any questions? Ask Chef...</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54705" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Remove the skin form the chicken and slash the chicken meat down to the bone in a couple places per leg. 

Combine and mix chicken with the other ingredients in order to marinate. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of dahl on plate, place naan bread besid dahl. place chicken on top of naan, garnish with fresh cilantro

2. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55420" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Cut off top. Scoop out seeds. Peel off exterior skin.

3. Cut into apropriate shape / Size for recipe uses.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem and seeds.

3. cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with seran wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56424" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Grate cucumber on a box grater and squeeze out excess moisture, discarde the cucumber water.

3. in a large bowl incorporate all ingredients till well combined, ensure there are no &quot;spice clumps&quot;

4. Taste for seasoning, adjust if needed

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56768" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Heat a large pot over medium heat. Once hot, add oil, onion, cumin, and one-third of the salt.(Adjust if altering batch size).

2. Add garlic, ginger, cilantro, and green chilies to Robot coupe to pulse into a paste. Then, add to the pan with the onions.

3. Next add ground coriander, chili powder, and turmeric and stir to coat. Add a little more oil at this point if the pan is looking dry.

4. Next add pureed tomatoes and chickpeas and remaining salt. If the mixture looks a little too thick, add up to 1 cup (250 ml) water. You’re looking for a semi-thick soup consistency at this point, as it will cook down into more of a stew.

5. Increase heat to medium high until it reaches a rolling simmer, then reduce heat to low or medium-low and maintain a simmer (uncovered) for 15-20 minutes, or until thick and stew-like. Stir occasionally.

6. When the chana masala is thickened and bubbly, taste and adjust seasonings as needed, add more salt if needed.

7. Remove from heat and add lemon juice and garam masala. Stir to mix.

Hot hold/serve immediately

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56827" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm basmati rice in the middle of serving bowl.

2. Place warm portion of vegetables with sauce on top 

3. Garnish with yogurt, diced tomatoes, fresh cilantro and papadom.

4. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57144" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. Cut stems off

3. Rough mince(sliceing motion not chopping; slicing will prevent brusing the delicate cilantro leaves)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62405" image="">This is a yielded prep, not a recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62422" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm Portion of rice at base of bowl

2. Place Portion of Butter chicken on top of rice

3. Garnish with dolop of minted yogurt on top of butter chicken

4. Place piece of naan bread off side in bowl

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62424" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm Portion of rice at base of bowl

2. Place Portion of Chana Masala on top of rice

3. Garnish with dolop of minted yogurt on top of Chana Masal (omit if vegan)

4. Place piece of naan bread off side in bowl (omit if vegan)

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67830" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1.Rinse the lentils in cold water until the water runs clear.

2.Heat a large Rondeau or tilt skillet over medium-high heat and add the oil. Once the oil is shimmering, add the garlic, ginger, and Serrano pepper and cook for 2 minutes, stirring frequently to prevent garlic from burning.

3. Add the cumin, coriander, chili powder, curry powder, garam masala, salt, and black pepper to taste, and cook for 30 to 60 seconds until fragrant, tossing frequently to prevent burning. Add the ground turmeric now, along the the rest of the spices.

4. Pour in the vegetable broth, and use a wooden spoon or spatula to scrape up any browned bits on the bottom of the pot. Add in the lentils and the crushed tomatoes and mix well. 

5. Reduce the heat to low and cover the pan with a lid. Simmer for 20 to 25 minutes, or until the lentils are cooked through and have mostly softened. If you find that the lentils are not quite soft after 25 minutes, add a bit more veg stock and cook for another 5 minutes.

6. Remove the lid and stir in the coconut milk. 

7. Continue cooking on low heat, uncovered for 5 to 8 minutes, until the curry has thickened and is creamy.

8. Finally, stir in the lemon juice and cilantro, and turn off the heat. 

9. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67831" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at base of bowl, place warm portion of lentil curry beside rice in bowl

2. Place naan portion off side of bowl

3. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

4. Seve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67833" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Heat 1/2 of the oil in a large rondeau. Fry potatoes in hot oil until brown. Remove to a paper towel-lined tray to drain and reserve.

2. Add remaining oil to the rondeau and fry onions, garlic, and fresh ginger until onion is soft and golden. Add chili, pepper, turmeric, cumin, salt, and tomatoes. Fry, stirring constantly, for 5 minutes. Stir in yogurt, mint, ground cardamom, and cinnamon stick. Cover and cook over low heat, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are cooked to a pulp. It may be necessary to add a little hot water if the mixture becomes too dry and starts to stick to the pan.

3. When mixture is thick and smooth, add chicken and stir well to coat. Cover and cook over very low heat until chicken is tender, 30 to 35 minutes. There should only be a little very thick sauce left when the chicken is finished cooking. If necessary cook uncovered for a few minutes to reduce the sauce.

RICE:

1. Wash rice well and drain well for at least 30 minutes.

2. Heat remaining oil in a large rondeau. Fry onion in hot oil until golden. Add saffron, cardamom pods, cloves, cinnamon stick, ground ginger, and rice. Stir continuously until rice is coated with spices.

3. Heat stock and salt in a pot. When the mixture is hot, pour it over the rice and stir well. Add the chicken mixture and quartered potatoes; gently mix them into the rice. Bring to boil. Cover the saucepan tightly, turn heat to very low, and steam for 20 minutes. Do not lift lid or stir while cooking!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67834" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of Biryani in bottom of bowl

2. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

3. Place warm piece of naan bread off side in bowl

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67835" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place 3 warm Pakoras in a small bowl

2. Serve with small side of chutney


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67836" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. In a large bowl, combine yogurt, lemon juice, cumin, cinnamon, cayenne, black pepper, ginger, and salt. Stir in chicken, cover, and refrigerate for 1 hour.

2. In a 400F oven place chicken on parchment lined sheet trays and roast just untill cooked (10-12 minutes apporox) Reserve.

3. Melt butter in a large rondeau over medium heat. Saute garlic and finely minced serrano pepper for 1 minute. Season with cumin, paprika, and salt. Stir in crushed tomatoes and cream. Simmer on low heat until sauce thickens, about 20 minutes.

4. Add roasted chicken, and simmer for 10 minutes. Remove from heat and stir in  fresh cilantro. 

5. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67837" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

MARINATE THE CHICKEN

1. Put the chicken in a large bowl with the yogurt, turmeric and pinch of salt. Mix well. Chill for 2 hours, or preferably overnight. 

CASHEW PASTE

2. Put 80g of cashews into a Vitamix, along with 110ml of hot water, ginger, and serrano peppers. Blitz to a smooth paste and reserve. 

COOK THE CHICKEN

3. Heat the oil in a large rondeau over a medium heat, and sizzle the cinnamon and clove for 1 minute. 

4. Add the onion and fry, stirring for 10-12 minutes until softened and turning golden brown. Add the chicken and left-over marinade and fry for 8 minutes, turning the chicken to seal as you go. Reduce the heat.

5. Add 100ml of water, cover and cook for 25 minutes, stirring halfway through. 

6. Add the cashew paste, remove the lid and simmer for 5-7 minutes, or until the gravy has thickened slightly and just coats the chicken. Add the cardamom powder, stir into sauce and chicken. Cover and turn off the heat. let sit 5 minutes.

7. Heat the oil in a small pan. Fry the remaining cashews for 2-3 minutes or until starting to brown (DO NOT WALK AWAY DURING THIS PROCESS) Scoop into a bowl with a slotted spoon. Set aside. Add the mustard seeds and curry leaves to the pan. As soon as they begin to splutter, pour everything over the chicken, along with the cashew nuts. Ready to serve!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at bottom of bowl

2. Place warm portion of curry on top of rice, garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

3. Place warm portion of naan bread off side on bowl

4. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67839" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Cook the cumin seeds, cloves, cardamom pods, ground almonds, coconut and sesame seeds in a small pan for 2-3 minutes or until lightly toasted. Cool, then use a spice grinder to grind to a powder.

2. Put the ginger, garlic, serrano chillies and 60ml water into a food processor and blend to a purée. Stir into the spice powder.

3. Heat the oil in a large rondeau and fry the potatoes for 10 minutes until really golden all over. Add the onions and fry for 5 minutes until soft and golden.

4. Add in the purée along salt &amp; pepper, the ground turmeric, yogurt and 300ml of water. Mix well, put on a lid and simmer for 20 minutes or until the potatoes are just tender. Remove the lid and simmer for another 10-15 minutes or until the sauce has thickened. 

5. Taste for seasoning, adjust as needed. Add Chopped cilantro and fold in.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67840" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. At the base of serving bowl place warm portion of basmati rice

2. Place warm portion of Dum Aloo on top of rice, garnish with fresh cilantro

3. Place piece of naan bread off side of bowl

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68226" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of basmati rice at bottom of serving bowl

2. Place warm portion of tikka masala on side/top of rice

3. Place portion of warm naan bread off side of bowl

4. garnish with fresh chopped cilantro and serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68227" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 1. Place cauliflower florets &amp; chickpeas in wok and warm through.

2. Add Zucchini and heat through making sure not to overcook zucchini so it still has some texture. 

3. Add roasted potatoes and sauce, fold in cilantro.

3. Place in warmer &amp; reserve for service. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68228" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large bowl, combine yogurt, lemon juice, cumin, cinnamon, cayenne, black pepper, ginger, and salt. Stir in Tofu, cover, and refrigerate for 1 hour.

3. Heat oil in a large rondeau / tilt skillet over medium heat. Saute garlic and finely minced serrano pepper for 1 minute. Season with cumin, paprika, and salt. Stir in crushed tomatoes and coconut millk. Simmer on low heat until sauce thickens, about 20 minutes.

4. Add marinated tofu cubes, and simmer for 10 minutes. Remove from heat and stir in  fresh cilantro. 

5. Reserve for service.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68229" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at bottom of bowl

2. Top rice with warm portion of tikka masala

3. place portion of naan bread off side in the bowl and garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68230" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm Portion of rice in bottom of bowl

2. Place warm portion of paneer tikka on top of rice

3. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

4. Place portion of Naan bread off side of the bowl

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68231" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice on one side of plate

2. serv portion of salad (cold on other side of plate

3. Place naan portion between rice and salad

4. garnish with fresh cilantro

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68232" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Drain and rinse chickepeas

3. Small dice cucumbers, red peppers, tomato. Julienne carrot, finely mince thai chili pepper (do not leave large pieces this will be very spicy)

4. Finely mince cilantro and mint leaves

5. In a large bowl toss together with dressing and ensure everything is evenly coated!

6. Reserve for service.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68233" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Blend together and taste for seasoning. Asjust if needed.

3. Reserve


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68236" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Heat 1/2 of the oil in a large rondeau. Fry potatoes in hot oil until brown. Remove to a paper towel-lined tray to drain and reserve.

2. Add remaining oil to the rondeau and fry onions, garlic, and fresh ginger until onion is soft and golden. Add chili, pepper, turmeric, cumin, salt, and tomatoes. Fry, stirring constantly, for 5 minutes. Stir in yogurt, mint, ground cardamom, and cinnamon stick. Cover and cook over low heat, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are cooked to a pulp. It may be necessary to add a little hot water if the mixture becomes too dry and starts to stick to the pan.

3. When mixture is thick and smooth, add Tofu and stir well to coat. Cover and cook over very low heat, 20 to 30 minutes. There should only be a little very thick sauce left when the biryani is finished cooking. If necessary cook uncovered for a few minutes to reduce the sauce.

RICE:

1. Wash rice well and drain well for at least 30 minutes.

2. Heat remaining oil in a large rondeau. Fry onion in hot oil until golden. Add saffron, cardamom pods, cloves, cinnamon stick, ground ginger, and rice. Stir continuously until rice is coated with spices.

3. Heat stock and salt in a pot. When the mixture is hot, pour it over the rice and stir well. Add the chicken mixture and quartered potatoes; gently mix them into the rice. Bring to boil. Cover the saucepan tightly, turn heat to very low, and steam for 20 minutes. Do not lift lid or stir while cooking!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68237" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of Biryani in bottom of bowl

2. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

3. Place warm piece of naan bread off side in bowl

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
</Recipes>
