<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-6888" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: DAIRY
Method:

1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes. 

4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9710" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-9712" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim all excess and cut the cauliflower in small     florettes
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9741" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and clean ingredients.
2.Slice
3.Lable and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. 
3. 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-15353" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Add soda water from fountain into mixing bowl.

2. Slowly pour in dry ingredients while mixing with wooden spoon or gloved hand to avoid lumping but being careful to not develop gluten too much- LESS MIXING=MORE FLUFFY BATTER

It may appear a little too thick at first, a small amount of fizzy water helps, but after a 30 minute proofing period/letting it sit in the fridge it will bubble up to perfection
3. Lable &amp; rest in fridge for 1/2 hour beore use to proof

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: beer and fizzy water arn&apos;t reflected in the recipe.

Utensils needed: 



- </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Thinly slice up green onion.

2.  Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26019" image="">1. Combine well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand. Add water, 1:1 with rice.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir to fluff and loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26169" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat butter chicken in steamer until hot throughout.

2. Transfer to serving vessel to hold for service

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26196" image="">1. Combine lemon juice, lime juice, vinegar, dijon, shallot, garlic, sugar, and salt and pepper mix in blender. Combine on medium speed
2. Slowly incorporate oil to create an emulsification. Add chopped parsley.  Check for seasoning
3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Dairy
Sulphites
Method:

1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 375*F.  Pull out garlic butter to soften,  or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic wrap until it is spreadable.

2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter.  Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26450" image="">1)  Make veg stock as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau, add oil.   Add onions and saute for 2-3 minutes or until starting to soften.  Add garlic and saute for 30 seconds more. Add thyme, rosemary and red wine.  Bring to a low simmer. Add veg stock and bring to a simmer.

3)  Combine soy, nutritional yeast and corn starch to form a very thick slurry.  Add to warm stock, whisking constantly.  Bring back to a simmer until stock thickens and corn starch is evenly dispersed.

5)  Allow to cool in appropriate vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate. 

Allergens:

Soy
Sulphite
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1)  In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

2)  Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26461" image="">1)  In a saute pan over medium high heat, add canola oil.  Once hot, saute onion until soft, about 5 minutes. Add mushrooms and continue sauteing until a dark color develops and mushrooms are soft.   Add garlic, celery and montreal steak spice and saute until tender.  Reserve.

2)  In large bowl, combine cooked lentils, cooked rice, oats, tomato paste, walnuts, herbs and reserved mushroom and onion mixture.  Combine well with S+P.

3)  Working in batches, add mixture to bowl of food processor.  Alternate pulsing and scraping bowl until blended, but still chunky.  Repeat until all mixture is done.

4)  Line loaf pan w/ parchment and add blitzed mushroom + lentil mixture.  Spread out evenly.  Cover with aluminum foil.

5)  Preheat oven to 350*F.  Place lentil loaf in oven and bake for 40 minutes.  Remove foil and continue baking for another 15-20 minutes until browned and edges are crispy.

6)  Slice and serve in appropriate dish, or hold for service.

Allergens:

Nuts/Tree Nuts
Gluten
Wheat
Mustard (montreal seasoning)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28313" image="">1)  Steam or simmer perogies according to package directions until soft.  Add to grill and sear until golden brown and slightly crunchy on the exterior, and hot throughout.  

2) Combine with grilled onions and hold for service.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28314" image="">1)  In tilt kettle over medium high heat, add oil.  Once oil is hot add onions and saute until beginning to soften and  caramalize.  Add seasoning and hold for service, or put in shallow hotel pan and chill in cooler.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28323" image="">Serve ingredients in the indicated proportions.

Place the butter chicken on top of the rice. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29315" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In tilt skillet (225 F) or large steam kettle over medium/ low heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add garlic, ginger and cayenne.  Saute until cayenne is cooked out and garlic and ginger are no longer potent when smelled, about 5-10 minutes.

2)  Add crushed tomato, diced tomato, honey, kasoori methi and bring to a simmer. Simmer for 15-20 minutes.

3) Add milk and cream and puree with immersion blender to break up the diced tomatoes and ensure that everything is combined well.

4) Adjust seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33555" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Chop pickles and set aside pickle juice.
2.Chop parsely very fine.
3. Mix all ingredients in mixer and fully incorperate.
4. Season with lemon, L&amp;P sauce, salt and pepper to taste
5. Store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Cutting board bowl whisk scale container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33557" image="">1)  Combine all well.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service quickly steam green beans and toss with s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34085" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Combine everything except chicken.  

2)  Incorporate chicken and allow to marinate for at least 24 hours.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36061" image="">1)  Put cous-cous in hotel pan.

2)  Bring water to a simmer.  Put over cous-cous and cover until cous-cous has absorbed all the water (5-10 minutes).  Fluff with a fork until tghere are no lumps and put on baking sheet to cool.

3)  When cous-cous is cool, combine with green onion, parsley, green and red pepper and viniagrette.  Taste for seasoning.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Beef Vindaloo
Chickpea Vindaloo

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Over medium/ low heat in large rondeau, add oil, cinnamon and onions and cook till nearly carmalized and golden brown.

2)  Add ginger, garlic, seeded jalapenos and cook until peppers are soft.

3) Add tomato paste and cook, stirring often until it is a deep, dark brown.

4) Add ground dry spices and vindaloo paste and cook for 10 minutes, or until spice is cooked out. Taste to ensure that the spices are cooked out. 

5)  Add water, diced tomatoes and juice, salt, lemon juice and brown sugar.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

6)  Remove from heat, remove cinnamon sticks.  Puree with immersion blender. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38518" image="">1)  Make cous-cous as per recipe.  Scoop appropriate amount of cous-cous and SERVE IT FORTH!

2)  Give yourself a hi-5</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42504" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44527" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Clean, prepare and chop the herbs as needed. 

Use any combination (or even just a single herb) in a quanitity adding up to 8 grams total weight. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44528" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing and portioning purposes only.

Make associated sub recipes as indicated in those particular recipes

The portion of sauce is 200ml or 6 fl. oz </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45231" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46869" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Neatly dice the Shallots in Brunoise size
2.Save the trimming for stock
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, storage container

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50428" image="">1) wash off both

2) Complete dry with dry towel

3) Chop nicely</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All ingredients
2. Chopped capers to desire size
3.  Store in container

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting Board, knife, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients
2. Chopped to desired size
3.  Store in appropriate container, label and fridge

Portioning:

Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Slice cucumber lenghtwise on a mandolin, do not use the core, as it is too soft and the cucumbers will break.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51210" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano until desired texture achived (course or fine)

3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53079" image="">1. Wash and core apples.
2. Using mandoline. shred apple
3.Soak it wit water and salt and drain.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54204" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Whisk all ingredients together to combine.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55143" image="">1) Warm peas and stock and simmer for 10 minutes.

2) Transfer to a blender, add mint, salt &amp; pepper and butter and puree until smooth.

3) Hold for service or chill and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55167" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-55280" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice all veg to 1/4&quot; and combine all but avocado in bowl.

2. Gently fold in diced avocado in to mix.

3. Portion size should be 120g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55818" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using ES 3 1/8&quot; blade on the robot coupe thinly slice cabbage.
2. Using the R2 Robot Coupe julienne the carrots.
3. Cut green onions on a bias/ angle and mix all veg together.
4. Right before service mix with dressing.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56540" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

THIS DISH IS SERVED COLD.

1. Working in small batches squeeze out as much water as possible and lay out on sheet pans to dry.

2. Heat up oil and sautee off garlic, and remove from heat

3. Mix dry spinach with remaning ingredients and combine well.

4. Serve, or cool and label/ rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56741" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using Robot Coupe with the shredding blade, shred pear and onion, saving all juices.

2. Mix in remaining ingredients.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56827" image="">1. Place cauliflower florets &amp; chickpeas in wok and warm.

2. Add Zucchini and heat through making sure not to overcook zucchini so it still has somne texture. 

3. Place in warmer for service. 

4. Place warm brown rice in the middle of serving bowl.

5. Place ladle of vegetables with sauce on top and put roasted potatoes around outside of bowl.

6. Garnish with yoghurt, diced tomatoes, cilantro and papadom.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cover ribs completely in marinade in a suitable insert.

2.Adjitate the meat to ensure the liquid contcts all surfaces of the ribs while still not breaking the rib bones out of the meat.

3.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58417" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
 

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Reserve fennel fronds for garnish 
2.
3. Garnish stuff
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60528" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-60548" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP,  an in house made ingredient recipe
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. pat fish dry
2. fully coat fish in batter letting excess batter fall off before deep frying
3.slowly drop into deep fryer using a slow &apos;wave&apos; motion to cook one side and make that side float before dropping it gently in
4. ensure that fish isnt sticking to fryer basket 
5. Let fish cook to a golden brown colour and pull basket up to drain for at least 90 seconds before seasoning
6. Transfer fully cooked fish to a bowl and season with salt and 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60807" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes until tender.
2. Using large mixer with the paddle attachment, whip hot potatoes while drizzling in warm stock and olive oil as well as seasoning.
3. Adjust seasoning to taste.
4. Hot hold for service OR....

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61625" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-62632" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Pick leaves of herbs but DO NOT CUT.
2. Mix with lime juice in small quantities to order.
3.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67984" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

1. Bloom your saffron in some warm water, and set aside. In batches deep fry potato until browned and cooked, but not mushy.

2. In the tilt kettle  sauté the onion, bell pepper, and garlic, ginger and chili until soft and translucent. Once most of the moisture is cooked out of vegies add spices, and toast in oil until fragrent, about 5 minutes.

3. Add in the uncooked rice, and mix well with toasted spices, covering rice in the oil and flavour. 

4. Once the rice is fully coated in oil and toasted slightly add in veg stock, tomatoes and salt and pepper. Close the lid and bring to a simmer and cook 20-25 minutes, until rice is almost fully cooked but still a little firm in center. Stir every 5 minutes or so. Do not over cook the rice as this will need to be reheated and the rice will turn to mush.

5. Stir in bloomed saffron with rice. Steam the carrot, beans and cauliflower until just tender. Then fold in veg, potato, fresh mint, with the rice.

-Serve, or cool, label and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67986" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE
Final product handed to the customer

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE***
Preps used in this Product recipe:
Method:
1. Scoop rice &amp; vegetables into bowl.
2. Tuck Naan into side of bowl.
3. Top with mint &amp; cilantro &amp; toasted cashews.

Portioning:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68125" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well ensuring there are no lumps of spices.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68131" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:
1. Line pullman loaf pan with parchment.

2. Whisk eggs, apple, scallions, garlic, ginger, chili flakes, sugar, soy, salt &amp; sesame oil to combine.

3. Add panko and let sit for 5-10 minutes to hydrate.

4. Working in batches add the ground beef to panko mixture until evenly mixed.

5. Add to loaf pans and tamp down to ensure there are no air pockets.

6. Bake in 325 F oven for 75-90 minutes and internal temperature reaches 160F

7. Let cool for a minimum of 20 minutes in pan before removing. Slice when cold.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68133" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE
Final product handed to the customer

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE***
Preps used in this Product recipe:
Method:
1. Sear one side of meatloaf on flattop until golden brown.
2. Brush w/ Gochujang.
3. Hold for service.
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
