<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

        2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

        3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

        4. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
        2.wash and drain
        3.add water or veg stock
        4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
        5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Products related to this Prep recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

        2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

        3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice.
        Mix well.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26112" image="">1. Preheat grill to high. Pre heat oven to 350F

        2. Brush sausage with oil. Put sausage on grill to sear. Once crisp and has grill lines, remove from grill and
        put in oven until hot throughout, about 10 - 15 minutes

        2. Cut to appropriate serving size and put in serving vessel.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Preheat oven to 320F

        2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice.

        3. Slice each butt in half, and season pork with salt and pepper. Make sure to get in all the cracks.

        4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it
        comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer on french top before putting it in the oven.

        5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 3.5 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart

        6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks, removing large pieces of fat. Add back some of braising
        liquid in pork to keep moist

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26144" image="">1. In large rondeau, heat canola oil over medium high heat. Add onion, pepper and
        garlic and saute until soft
        2. Add Basmati rice and coat completely in oil and rice is beginning to toast about 5 minutes
        3. Add cumin, oregano, paprika, salt &amp; pepper and tomato paste, cook 2 minutes
        4. Add veg stock and beans, bring to a boil and reduce heat to low. Cover and simmer 30-50 minutes. Remove from
        heat. Keep covered and let stand five minutes. Fluff with fork
        5. Allow to cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1) Preheat oven to 400*F.

        2) In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots. Add seasoning. Distribute among
        baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

        3) Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper. Put on seperate baking sheet and
        cover in tinfoil.

        4) When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan. Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until
        vegetables are caramalized and tender.

        5) Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

        Allergens:

        No known priority allergens

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

        2) Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes. Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and
        store in appropriate vessel.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26323" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In saute pan over medium heat, toast peppercorns and fennel until fragrant. Allow to cool and grind in spice
        grinder. Add chili flakes and reserve.

        2) Combine parsley, cilantro, garlic cloves, canola oil, lemon juice and cumin. Blitz into a paste with robot
        coupe. Reserve.

        3) Combine herb paste with fennel, peppercorns and chili flakes and S&amp;P.

        4) Reserve for porchetta.

        * An 8 oz. recipe will make enough for 2 (two) porchetta.
        .


        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) With pork belly skin side down, rub belly with Porchetta Rub generously.

        2) Roll belly into a tight log. You may need a buddy to help you hold the belly in place. Tie butchers knots on
        each end of porchetta than one good tie in the middle to secure. Continue making butchers knots 1&quot; apart
        until fully tied.

        3) Combine kosher salt and baking powder. Rub over skin of porchetta.

        4) Store in fridge, uncovered for at least 24 hours, or up to 3 days.

        5) Preheat oven to 300*F. Place porchetta seam side down on cooling rack inside of roasting rack. Roast until
        internal temperature of 60*C (140*F) is reached.

        6) Increase oven temperature to 500*F and roast for 20-30 minutes until skin is blistered and very crispy.

        7) Rest for 15 minutes and serve.


        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
        3.sprinkle with other ingredients
        4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
        5. put in serving dish for service
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:130g

        Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
        ALLERGEN
        -NONE
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-28995" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Shred cucumber in robotcoupe. Combine all ingredients well in mixing bowl.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-32659" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Steam yukon gold nugget potato&apos;s for 8 minutes. If steaming ahead of time cool properly and store for
        later.

        2) Combine oregano with oil, lemon juice, garlic and salt and pepper. Pour marinade over potatoes.

        3) Pour potatoes onto parchment lined baking trays and roast @ 450*F for 15 minutes or until potatoes are crispy
        and brown. Serve immidiately or hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1) Bring water to a boil in large stock pot. Add veg stock concentrate and stir well
        to combine. Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-32752" image="">1) Preheat oven to 400*F.

        2) Place skewers on baking trays and cook until well done (at least 71*C). Hold hot for service.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-32757" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1) Prepare and Ice bath

        2) Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes. Immidiately put into ice
        bath. Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

        3) Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans. Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p
        mix. Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-35815" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-37055" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-37056" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-38664" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-38665" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43707" image="">1) Combine well, store in appropriate container, cover with cheese cloth and leave out
        at room temperature for about 8-12 hours, until desired thickenss is reached. Reserve in fridge for up to 2
        weeks.

        Allergens:

        Dairy/Milk
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43747" image="">1) Shuck corn and cut in half. Preheat oven to 425*F. In large mixing bowl, cover in
        oil and salt and pepper, chili powder, paprika and tajin seasoning.

        2) Put corn on parchment lined baking sheet and roast for 15-20 minutes, turning every 10 minutes until corn is
        nicely charred.

        3) Combine creme fraiche, mayo and garlic puree. Mix well.

        4) Combine roasted corn with creme fraiche and mayo mixture. Taste for seasoning.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1) Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment. If you don&apos;t know
        how, ask chef or a 1st cook.

        2) Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

        Allergens:

        No known prioirity allergens.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingedients
        2.pick leaves
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-44975" image="">Portion out 175g</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-45744" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Drain the cheese
        2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46593" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Add oil to saute pan. Once oil is hot, add onion and saute until soft.

        2) Add corn and continue sauteing until no longer frozen. Add refried beans and reserve for making tacos.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46864" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Be sure to make shred from other Iceberg lettuce preps
        3. evenly slice lettuce 3 mm thick
        4. Cover with wet brown paper towel to stop oxidization

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-47361" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Add all ingredients EXCEPT oil in a cambro.

        2. Blend with immersion blender, then slowly drizzle in oil to form an emulsion.

        3. Taste for seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50434" image="">Julinenne Chayote. shave radish, peel and cube avocado, chop cilantro.

        In a bowl, add lime juice, honey, cayenne, salt and oil. mix well.

        Add all vegetable and herb ingredients into the bowl, mix then place salad in refrigerator with label.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50439" image="">Fry, drain oil on paper towel &amp; season.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50440" image="">Place Chayote salad and black beans, feta and lettuce on fried tortilla shell and
        serve immediatly.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50560" image="">Prepare all sub recipes


        Spread refried beans and put other ingredients on top of each other, First, pulled pork, lettuce iceberg, pico
        de gallo, cheese, sour cream and radish.

        Garnish with cilantro and limes on the side.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

        2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme
        is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
        3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-51313" image="">Layer ingredients in the proportions indicated.

        Sequence the toppings in this order

        Tostada, beans, lettuce, chayote salad, crumbled feta, shaved radish.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1.

        2.

        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55138" image="">1) In rondo add vegan butter, sliced onion and fresh thyme over medium/low heat and
        caramalize onions, stirring occasionally.

        2) When onions are golden brown sprinkle in flour and stir to form a roux.

        3) Slowly add the stock a little at a time whisking the whole time to avoid lumps.

        4) Simmer for approximately 10 minutes to cook out flour, stirring occasionally to prevent burning.

        5) Add sauce, dijon and adjust seasoning.

        6) Hold for service or transfer and chill.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55143" image="">1) Warm peas and stock and simmer for 10 minutes.

        2) Transfer to a blender, add mint, salt &amp; pepper and butter and puree until smooth.

        3) Hold for service or chill and store.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56808" image="">1) Place chicken in large storage container and add remaining ingredients.

        2) Ensure chicken is evenly mixed.

        3) Refrgerate overnight.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56836" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        Preheat oven to 350F

        1. Place marinaded chicken SKIN SIDE UP in hotel pans in an even layer.

        2. Pour all of marinade plus white wine into pans evenly.

        3. Remove any food from the top of the chicken and sprinkle the brown sugar over the top of the chicken skin.

        4. Cook for 40-50 minutes (or until internal temperature of chciken reaches 165F).

        5. Baste the chicken 2-3 times during cooking with the liquid.

        6. Hold for service.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56837" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-57082" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut Tempe into appropriate sized pieces.

        2. Place into storage container, add remaining ingredients and store in refridgerator for 24 hours.


        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57083" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        Preheat oven to 350F

        1. Place marinaded tempe in hotel pans in an even layer.

        2. Pour all of marinade plus white wine into pans evenly.

        3. Remove any food from the top of the tempe and sprinkle the brown sugar over the top.

        4. Cook for 10-15 minutes.

        5. Baste 2-3 times during cooking with the liquid.

        6. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57338" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. portion mash scoop out first
        2. top with sausage
        3. nape&apos; sauce over the stack of delicious potato and sausage


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57340" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. portion mash scoop out first
        2. scoop peas off the side of the poatos leaving a solid space for the sausage
        3. top mash and peas with sausage
        4.nape&apos; sauce over the stack of delicious potato and sausage


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57630" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Mix well.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57631" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Season all sides of the chicken skewer.

        2. Cook to an internal temperature of 165F

        3. Hold for service.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57632" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cube both the cucumber and melon into 2-3 cm cubes.

        2. Add remaining ingredients and toss dressing well.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-60807" image=""/>
</Recipes>
