<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7139" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Mix the remaining ingredients.


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7635" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny Bravo

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Open can
2.Drain in strainer and wash throughly
3.Place drained beans in insert label and place in fridge
4. Heat in steam required amount

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:90G Blue scoop

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: DAIRY
Method:

1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes. 

4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9767" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Thinly slice up green onion.

2.  Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water from the pan runs clear

2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

NOTE: this is 2 boxes of tomatoes.

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice. Use the same dicing blade for the red onions.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and salt, and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil.

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes. In a cycle of letting them brown, and scraping and stirring with a wooden spoon, until onions are a dark golden brown. Add a splash of water cold if the bottom browning is sticking too much.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand. Add water, 1:1 with rice.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir to fluff and loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix.  Blend well.  

2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26384" image="">1)  Soak navy beans in cold water overnight in fridge, ensuring to cover beans by at least 2-3 inches of water.

2)  The next day, drain soaked beans and add to large pot.  Add water, rough chopped carrot, celery and onion.  DO NOT SEASON!

3)  Bring to a gentle simmer, skimming any impurities that comes to the top.  Simmer until beans are cooked through, about 15-20 minutes.  

4)  Carefully drain, trying not to squish beans.  Pick out vegetables and bay leaf and discard.

5)  Cool on baking tray.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26385" image="">1)  Combine olive oil, lemon juice, crushed red pepper and crushed garlic and seasoning.  Combine well with a whisk.

2)  Pour marinade over torn kale leaves.  Toss to coat and refrigerate overnight in an appropriate container.  

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26387" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition): Allergens:
Sulphite
Mustard   

Method:
1)  Preheat oven to 400*F

2)  In mixing bowl, combine shallot, 2T canola oil, 1 tsp S&amp;P and thyme sprigs.  Combine well.  Lay out on large piece of aluminum foil and fold.  Put on baking sheet and roast in oven until soft and caramalized, about 40 minutes.  Open package carefully and discard thyme.  Allow to cool.

3)  Combine roasted shallots, garlic, dijon mustard, lemon juice, white wine vinegar and remaining S&amp;P in jug of vitamix or bowl of robot coupe.  Blitz.  Slowly add remaining oil to create and emulsification.  Strain through fine mesh strainer.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed: </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1)  Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

2)  Remove baskets from deep fryer.  Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

3)  Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil.  Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

4)  Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil.  Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

5)  Place in appropriate container once cooled.  Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
soy (from tortilla)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26450" image="">1)  Make veg stock as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau, add oil.   Add onions and saute for 2-3 minutes or until starting to soften.  Add garlic and saute for 30 seconds more. Add thyme, rosemary and red wine.  Bring to a low simmer. Add veg stock and bring to a simmer.

3)  Combine soy, nutritional yeast and corn starch to form a very thick slurry.  Add to warm stock, whisking constantly.  Bring back to a simmer until stock thickens and corn starch is evenly dispersed.

5)  Allow to cool in appropriate vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate. 

Allergens:

Soy
Sulphite
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279



1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27272" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Tuscan.jpg">1)  Combine Quinoa with half of shallot vineagrette.  Place in bowl.

2)  Add oil to saute pan over medium high heat.  Once hot, add beans and remaining dressing.  Once beans are warm, add seasoning, tomato and spinach.  Place on top of quinoa.

3)  Drop poached egg in warm water.  Top bean mixture with marinated kale and pickled red onions.  When egg with warm, remove with a slotted spoon and put on side of bowl, so as to not cover garnishes.  Serve immediately.

Allergens:

Egg
Mustard</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35337" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Milk
Dairy

Method:

1)  Preheat oven to 300*F

2)  In appropriate sized pot, combine water, garlic, shallot and thyme bring to a simmer, then take off heat and allow to infuse for about 20 minutes.  Strain out aromatics and add cream. Reserve warm.

3)  Combine cornmeal and salt.  Pour cornmeal mixture into stock and cream while whisking constantly

4)  Add mixture to hotel pans, and put in oven.  bake for 45 minutes, stirring every 15 minutes.

5)  Add butter and parmesan cheese.  Taste for seasoning and reserve for service, or 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35338" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor, combine half of the oil, vinegar, basil, parsely, arugula, garlic puree and seasoning.  Process until smooth.  Do not strain.  

2)  Add remianing oil and STIR with a spoon or spatula to combine. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35341" image="">1)  Place warm polenta in bottom of bowl.  Top with marinated kale and radish, then egg, and garnish with salsa verde.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36666" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\5 Alarm Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Start building this bowl with the beans and rice hot in the bottom of the serving vessel.

2. Add remaining ingredients topping with poached egg and avocado fan.

3. Drizzle with cumin lime dressing and habanero sauce..

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37780" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat the oven to 450F.

2. Toss the cauliflower with the lemon oil, salt &amp; pepper until evenly coated.

3. On a parchment lined baking sheet place cauliflower in even layer with space betwee eac piece (don&apos;t crowd pan or veg will steam rather than roast) roast until golden and tender; Aprox. 20 minutes. Transfer to a hotel pan for service.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44392" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.in non reactive pot place everything except eggs
3.bring to a simmer
4. Crack egg into simmering water and cook soft
5. pull from water and put in ice bath to cool rappedly
6. place in container place enough cold water in container to keep eggs loose so they do not break
7. Label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Pot slotted spoon containers</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44506" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Halve the avocado and carefully remove the pit
3.  Slice into desired sizes
4. Toss in lemon juice to prevent oxydation

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 1 portion is 1/4 avocado

Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, bowl insert, mesuring cups
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather ingredients.
2. Put frozen corn in mixing bowl.
3. Add other ingredients and mix.
4. Spead out on roasting pan and bake 190C 375F for 15 minutes or till roasted (lightly coloured).
5. Place in insert label, cover and place in warmer for service.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:30G

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46507" image="">1) Cut cherry tomatoes in half, toss with oil and salt and pepper mix, roast in a hot oven 450F briefly 10 min or so, just to soften up and brown lightly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46870" image="">Allergens:

none
Icons:

n/a

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.zest the most outer layer of the lemon using a fine microplane
2. Set aside zested lemon to be used first/ juiced 
3. Use zest as close to recipe execution as possible but any excess is to be Stored, labeled and rotated correctly with any older product diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48487" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tomatoes, chile de arbol, garlic cloves.  Add water until vegetables are just covered.  

2)  Bring to boil, turn down to a simmer and continue simmering until tomatoes are soft, about 10-15 minutes.

3)  Remove vegetables by straining into a large bowl.  ENSURE TO RESERVE WATER!

4)    Add vegetables to a vita mix, or puree with hand blender in an appropriatly sized vessle.  Puree until smooth, but do not strain.  Add some reserved water if you are having difficulties pureeing, or if puree is too thick.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48488" image="">
1)  Warm tortilla shell on the flat-top grill with a small amount of oil.  Grill until warm and slightly crispy.

2)  Meawhile add more oil to the grill and fry the egg.

3)  Spread refried beans on tortilla shell and place fried egg on top of beans.

4)  Top with warm Rancheros Salsa, and add feta cheese, and top with chopped cilantro.  Serve immediately.







</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49176" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:
1. Preheat oven to 425F

2. Dice to 3/4&quot; and toss diced sweet potato in oil &amp; seasoning.

3. Cook 10-12 minutes until tender.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50464" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Mac &amp; cheese

Method:

1) Set milk out to warm up while doing other steps.

2) In pot melt the butter over medium heat

3) Add the flour through fine mesh chinois while whisking melted butter to insure that no lumps are formed.

4) Stir until the mixture is smooth and with out lumps, this is the time to be more careful. Cook for 1 minute so the flour becomes tastier and absorbs the fats. The roux should be a nice golden colour.

5) Add warm milk to roux in a steady stream, whisking continuously. Simmer on low heat until it starts to thicken, but insure it does not come to a boil. Whisk in the salt and pepper mix, and nutmeg, taste for seasoning and adjust if needed. Set aside for recipe.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50469" image="">1) In large pan, brown the ground beef until the pink colour is gone. Add onion and saute until translucent, about 5 mintues, Add garlic and cook until fragrant, about 1 minute.

2) Add wine to the pan and allow to simmer and reduce a bit before adding cinnamon, all spice, parsley, tomato paste, and crushed tomatoes, and sugar.

3) Allow the sauce to simmer, uncovered, for approximately 15 minutes so that exess liquid can evaporate. It should be drier, chunkier sauce. Season to taste with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50474" image="">1. Using a peeler, partially peel the eggplants, leaving strips about 1&quot; wide around the eggplant. Slice the eggplant into 1/2&quot; round slices.

2. Place the eggplant slices in a colander and salt them liberally. Cover them with an other heavy dish to weigh down the eggplant and help them purge more water. Place colander over large container or sink to drain off the water. Let sit for 1 hour.

3. If preping ahead of time you can let the purged, and rinsed eggplant dry in cooler over night.

4. Peel the potatoes, cut in to 1/4&quot; round slices, place in perferated steaming trays and steam for 7-10 mintues. They should not get too soft, just cooked enough so that they no longer crunch. 

5. Roast eggplant with oil on baking trays until cooked through. Cool and reserve for recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50489" image="">1. Preheat oven to 275F
2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice into a thick spreadable paste.
3.  Season pork with salt and pepper.  Make sure to get in all the cracks.
4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer.
5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 7-8 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart
6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks. Reduce remaining braising liquid and add half if necessary. Add back in pork to keep moist
7. Allow to cool. Store in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50540" image="">1. Heat oven to 350 and bake for 20-30 minutes. Till hot all the way through, and bachemel deeply browned on top.

2. Once baked and hot, cut the baked moussaka in the hotel pan, in to 16 even pieces. Scoop out with spatulas, and place on plate. Serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50562" image="">1. Spread pesto across entire surface area of flatbread.

2. Add capicollo, sundried tomatoes then mozzarella.

3. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes in a 325F oven until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread are golden brown.

4) Take it off from oven and finish with balsamic glaze.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces, top w arugula and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50590" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 325F or grill

2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread pesto, caramelized onion.

3. Spread crumbled goat cheese, half sliced cherry tomatoes.

4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until cherry tomatoes are fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

5. Take out of oven.

7. Spread arugula and drizzle with balsamic glaze.

8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50725" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut bread into 4 x 4 rectagles using pastry cutter as marker- each peice s=will weight approx. 130 grams 
2.Cut each portion horizontally
3. wrap tightly, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50788" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

2) Evenly lay sliced Bocconcinni over pesto.

3) Add sliced tomatoes.

4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

5) Once cooked take out from oven.

6) Spread out whole basil and drizzle balsamic glaze.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50789" image="">1.Drain and slice boconccinni.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50803" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Char jalapenos on the grill until cooked.

3. Clean and de-seed the jalapenos.

4. Blitz jalapeno, lemon juice, salt/pepper in vitamix.

5. Mix honey, jalapeno mixture and mayo.

6. Taste and adjust as needed

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50824" image="">1. Pre-heat oven to 325F 
2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, 
3. Spread half of the cheese, pulled pork, corn, julienne peppers and lastly sprinkle the rest of the cheese
4. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.
5. Take off fom oven and add pico de gallo.
7. Drizzle the sour cream.
8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50858" image="">1.Sautee peppers &amp; onions until slightly soft and fragrent.

2. Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with mashed confit garlic. 

3. Evenly spread spinach then sauteed peppers &amp; onions.

4. Lay down sliced tomatoes.

5. Sprinkle feta cheese and olives.

6. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50859" image="">1) Spread pesto on the bottom of the flatbread, drain excess liquid off bruschetta mix and place evenly over the top of the flatbread.

2) Add mozzarella cheese.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

3) Take it off from oven and drizzle with balsamic reduction.

4) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50860" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Dice tomatoes.

2) Combine all ingredients, and place in a container, pour over liquid to coat tomatoes. Let marinate at least 24 hours. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50896" image="">1) Prebake flatbread first in deck oven for 4-5 minutes until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread are golden brown before putting any toppings on.

2) After baking &amp; cooling lightly coat bottom of flatbread with cream cheese, smoked salmon, capers and sliced white onion.

3) When you get an order warm flatbread in deck oven for 1 minute.

4) Take it off from oven and garnish with fresh dill.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51303" image="">Method:
ladel 90 ml portion of sauce onto plate
top with portion of baked pasta
garnish with fresh parsley sprig and sprinkle of shredded parm
serve

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52096" image="">1. Assemble all the ingredients.
2. Heat your rondeau so that it&apos;s super hot.
3. Put your onions in followed by the oil - the onions cool down the skillet just enough so that the oil doesn&apos;t start burning or catches fire on you.
4. Turn down the heat to medium/low and continue cooking out the onions until golden/caramelized. Season with salt+pepper.
5. Add the brown sugar last just before you take the onins off the stove.

Cool, label, date, refrigirate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53126" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Warm bechamel over medium heat, stirring often to ensure sauce doesn&apos;t scald on the bottom of the pot.

2. Have shredded cheese ready and add off the heat while stirring to melt.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54644" image="">1) In 2&quot; hotel pan, spread thin layer of 240g meat sauce, then layer 960g eggplant pieces on, then 480g cooked potato slices, seasoning veg with salt and pepper mix.

2) Then add a 1920g layer of the meat filling, sprinkle parm over meat.

3) Then a 960g layer of baked eggplant, topped with the 1.36L of bechemel,

4) Heat oven to 350 and bake for 20-30 minutes. Till hot all the way through, and bachemel deeply browned on top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54664" image="C:\Users\okbrianb\Pictures\Pasta 16 pieces.bmp">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cook off, and break up chorizo, sautee until fully cooked and browned. Remove cooked meat with slotted spoon and set asidet.

2. In the fat left by the chorizo, saute onions and peppers until fragrant. Add mushrooms until soft and most of the moisture has been cooked off.

3. Combine evenly with penne and tomato sauce.

4.  Place into 2&quot; hotel pan and top with the cheeses.

5. Cover with plastic wrap and a metal lid, steam with the thermometer in until internal temperature reachs 160F. 

6. Place in oven at 400F until cheese is golden brown. Cut in to 16 even pieces (2 x 8).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54666" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Warm up sauce.
 
2. Blanch broccoli.

3. Cook chicken.

4. Toss cooked pasta with sauce, broccoli, chicken and portion into a hotel pans. 

5. Cover with plastic wrap and a metal lid, steam with the thermometer in until internal temperature reachs 160F. 

6. Place in oven at 400F until cheese is golden brown. Cut in to 16 even pieces (2 x 8).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55515" image="">IT IS VERY IMPORTANT SPINACH IS TOTALLY DEFROSTED AND AS MUCH LIQUID HAS BEEN SQUEEZED OUT.

1) In a large pan add oil over medium heat and sweat onion until soft.

2) Add garlic and sweat 1-2 minutes until fragrant.

3) Add mushrooms and cook until most of their liquid has been released.

4) Add spinach and stir to combine ensuring most of liquid in spinach has been released.

5) Season to taste.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55516" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

1) Spread a small amount of cheese sauce on bottom of 2&quot; hotel pans.

2) Spread lasagna noodles evenly.

3) Add mushroom/ spinach mixture then ricotta.

4) Add another layer of noodles.

5) Add sauce and more vegetable mixture.

6) Add noodles/ sauce.

7) Top with mozzarella and parmesan.

8) Bake uncovered in a 300 F oven for 45 mins. Ensure noodles are cooked and internal temperature is between 160-165 F.

Build in this order:
Bottom: 3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Noodles 8
            Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
            Ricotta 500g
            Noodles 8
            3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
            Noodles 8
            3-cheese sauce 750ml
            Mozzarella 500g
            Parmesan 100g
If building ahead of time, add mozza/parm before baking.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56337" image="">1) Spread pesto evenly over entire area of flatbread.

2) Add artichokes, olives, sundried tomatoes then goat cheese.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Take it off from oven and evenly spread arugula on top and balsamic reduction.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56500" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Cook pasta to al dente. This is very important as the pasta will soak up the sauce and get very soft/ mushy if it is over cooked.

2. Drain pasta well and mix with sauce.

3. Adjust seasoning.

4. Top with mozzarella and parmesan and bake in a 350F oven for ??? minutes ensuring top is golden brown and pasta is hot..

5. Makes 16 portions (2 x 8).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56509" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Breakfast Quesadilla.jpg">1. Place tortilla on flattop, spread cheese evenly on both sides (this will be the glue to hold the whole thing together).

2. Add remaining ingredients evenly over the entire surface so each bite gives you all the ingredients..

3. Fold in half and cook on both sides until golden brown and crispy.

4. Cut into 4 even pieces. Place crispy tortilla strips on plate and place quesadilla on top to prevent bottom from getting soggy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56687" image="">1) Puree pear tomatoes and half of the roasted peppers in a blender until smooth.

2) In a saute pan heat olive oil over medium heat. Add garlic and cook until fragrant but not brown.

3) Add spices &amp; tomato paste and cook 1-2 minutes.

4) Add pureed tomato mix, kale and remaining roasted red peppers (cut into strips).

5) Simmer for 10-15 minutes.

6) Adjust seasoning.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56688" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Shakshuka.jpg">1) Pre poach eggs to 70% done.

2) grill pita on both sides to warm, cut into 6 even pieces. 

3) Warm sauce in saurte pan and finsih cooking egg in sauce.

4) Garnish with diced avocado, feta cheese &amp; Italian parsley.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58715" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a saute pan/ rondo over medium/ high heat add butter, garlic and salt/ pepper.

2. When garlic is soft and fragrant (1 minute) add chopped mushrooms and cook until they are soft strirring occasionally.

3. When 90% cooked add whipping cream and reduce until mushrooms bind together slightly.

4. Turn off heat, add lemon zest, parsley and chopped thyme. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61308" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients, place in to pot and simmer, until the veg is cooked and soft.

2. Puree and season

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61498" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with tomato sauce.

2) Evenly lay ham, then mozzarella and diced mango.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61658" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Ensure roasted cauliflower is broken down into small pieces.

2. Mix all ingredients (including some of the mozzarella) together in a large mixing bowl reserving a bit of mozza for the top. Check for seasoning.

3. Top with mozza and parmesan. 

Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61663" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Rinse black beans well, lay evenly on a baking tray and dry in medium oven.

2. Saute onion, garlic in olive oil until fragrant (about 5 minutes).

3. Working in batches in a food processor, pulse all ingredients ensuring you leave a little texture in the mix.

4. Check for seasoning, form into 160g patties.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61664" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix ground flax meal with water, stir and let stand for 5 minutes. 

2. This is the equivalent to one egg.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61665" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Deforst mango &amp; puree in a blender.
2. Mix with remaining ingredients ensuring there are some chunks of avocado.
3. Check for seasoning.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-12347" image="">1. Warm black bean burger in oven until hot.

2. Toast bun, spread mango avocado sauce on both sides of bun.

3. Top with tomato, lettuce and pickled red onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61742" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto.

2) Evenly lay shrimp, tomatoes and parmesan. Sprinkle chili flakes.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Cut into 4 even pieces, garnish with arugula, squeeze fresh lemon and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61749" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in bbq sauce.

2) Evenly lay chicken, peppers then cheese.

3) Top with corn..

4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

5) Once cooked take out from oven.

6) Add pickled onions.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61778" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in olive oil.

2) Mix all cheeses together.

3) Spread cheese evenly over flatbread.

4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

5) Once cooked take out from oven.

6) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61779" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

2) Evenly lay cooked mushrooms over pesto.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Once cooked take out from oven.

5) Lay arugula over.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
