<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26022" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place apples, cinnamon, and brown sugar together in a pot.

2. Add water if needed (the frozen apples will purge some liquid, but be prepared to add some if it seems to not be enough) Bring to a boil and reduce to a simmer for  about 5-10 minutes

3. Make a cornstarch slurry and pour it in incrementally, while stirring the pot. Be careful to add a bit at a time, and check the consistency between additions, because once the sauce consistency has been acheived, no more slurry should be added. 

4. Spread out on baking tray to cool.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26044" image="">1)  In a sauce pot, combine half of berry mix, lemon juice, vanilla extract, sugar and water.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow water to reduce slightly and sugar to dissolve.

2)  Combine corn starch and cold water to make a slurry.  Add to simmering compote to thicken.

3)  Add remaining berries and allow to heat through until no longer frozen.  Add more water if necessary if mixture is too stiff.

4)  Store in appropriate vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, havarti and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add  red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Dairy
Sulphite
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 375*F.  Pull out garlic butter to soften,  or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic wrap until it is spreadable.

2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter.  Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26378" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. With 1/4 inch dice attachment on the robocope dice shallots and then tomatoes (so the shallots don&apos;t get stuck/lost make sure they are processed first), place in perferated hotel pan and let drain excess liquid out for 10-15 minutes.

2. Add diced tomato and shallot and mix with puree garlic, chiffonade basil, olive oil, balsamic vinegar and S&amp;P in mixing bowl and mix throughly.  Taste for seasoning.

3.  Check quality after 24 hours.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Egg
milk

Method:

1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.  

2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279



1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26497" image="">Preheat oven to 325*F


Spread walnuts out over baking tray and toast in oven until toasted and fragrant, about 15-20 minutes.  Ensure to stir the nuts and rotate pan about half way though cooking to ensure even toasting.  Allow to cool.

Store in airtight container.  Label, date and store in a cool, dry place.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27273" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Avocado Taost.jpg">1)  Grill or toast ciabatta until crisp and warm.

2)  Spread evenly with guacamole, than top with bruscetta mix, arugula then pickled onions.

3)  Garnish with hemp hearts.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28354" image="">1. Preheat oven to 400F
2. Rub  chicken with house rub
3. Place chicken on raised rack in roasting pan. Place in 400F oven for 15 - 25 minutes.
4. Continue roasting chicken until probe reaches 70C. Take chicken out of oven and allow to rest. Reserve juices.
5. Allow to cool, transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28355" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-28398" image="">
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32742" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Apple overnight oats.jpg">1)  Scoop appropriate amount of oats into serving bowl.

2)  Garnish with roasted apples, toasted walnuts, coconut whipped cream and a drizzle of maple syrup.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35801" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  In large mixing bowl, combine oil, yams, and salt and pepper.  Mix well.

2)  Put seasoned yams on parchment lined roasting pan, and roast yams until well caramalized and tender, about 15 minutes.  Make sure to rotate pan and mix product half way through cooking to ensure even roasting.

3)  Make sure to not smash up yams.  We need them to be nice and unsmashed.

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35811" image="">1)  Cook Penne as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil. Once hot, add diced red onion and saute for 5 minutes or until soft add garlic and chili flakes saute for a fwe more minutes.  Add capers, kalamata olives, semidried tomatoes and saute for another minute until warm throughout.  Add confit garlic reserved from garlic chili oil.

3)  Add arugula and remove from heat.  Add cooked pasta and stir well to combine.  Season with salt and pepper.  Reserve for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35910" image="">Allergens:

Wheat
Gluten
Dairy
Milk</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37081" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38586" image="">1)  Poach eggs as per recipe.

2)  Make cheese sauce as per recipe.  Heat up for service and hold warm.

3)  Saute mushrooms as per recipe. When mushrooms are almost done, add in baby kale and continue sauteing for 30 seconds - 1 minute or until kale has wilted. Hold warm for service.

4)  When customer orders, place 1 english muffin cut in half on the grill, and a portion of grapefruit.  Grill until muffins are toasted and grapefruit has grill lines on it, about 2 minutes.  

5)  While english muffins and grapefruit is grilling, drop poached eggs into hot water and bring up to temperture.  

6)  Place grilled english muffins on plate, top with warm mushroom and kale mixture, then the warm poached eggs, and top with cheese sauce.  Garnish with grilled grapefruit and arugula dressing in citrus oil.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38587" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-41042" image="">1)  Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2)  When an order is placed, put oil on grill to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg wash, and put on grill.  Allow toast to grill for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3)  Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with warm fruit compote, maple syrup, toasted walnuts and icing sugar.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In large mixing bowl, combine oats, almond milk, maple syrup, cinnamon, salt, grated apple and chia seeds.  Combine throughly.  Season to taste with allspice and ginger.

2)  Cover mixture and refrigerate at least 2 hours, or overnight.  Product will hold for 2 days.
3)
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43680" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pot over medium low heat, add oil.  

2)  Process garlic as you normally would in food processor, but stop before a fine paste forms.  You want chunky bits of garlic.

3)  Add garlic bits for warm oil and fry, stirring frequently for 4-5 minutes until garlic is crispy.  Strain through fine mesh strainer and reserve oil.  Place cripsy garlic on papertowel to soak up excess oil.

4)  Once dry, place crispy garlic in appropriate container, lined with papertowel and lid tightly.  Garlic can be stored at room temperature for about 3 days.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43733" image="">1)  Soak steel cut oats overnight by covering them in cold water.

2)  Strain oats well.  Make vegetable stock as per recipe.

3)  In large sauce pot, or rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onion and saute 3-4 minutes.  Add garlic and soaked oats and saute for about 5-6 minutes to toast the oats.  Season with salt and pepper.

4)  Add vegetable stock and simmer oats until tender, about 5-8 minutes.  Taste for seasoning.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43734" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48487" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tomatoes, chile de arbol, garlic cloves.  Add water until vegetables are just covered.  

2)  Bring to boil, turn down to a simmer and continue simmering until tomatoes are soft, about 10-15 minutes.

3)  Remove vegetables by straining into a large bowl.  ENSURE TO RESERVE WATER!

4)    Add vegetables to a vita mix, or puree with hand blender in an appropriatly sized vessle.  Puree until smooth, but do not strain.  Add some reserved water if you are having difficulties pureeing, or if puree is too thick.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48488" image="">
1)  Warm tortilla shell on the flat-top grill with a small amount of oil.  Grill until warm and slightly crispy.

2)  Meawhile add more oil to the grill and fry the egg.

3)  Spread refried beans on tortilla shell and place fried egg on top of beans.

4)  Top with warm Rancheros Salsa, and add mozzarella cheese, and top with chopped cilantro.  Serve immediately.







</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50387" image="">1)  Season pork loin with Italian seasoning, and salt and pepper.

2) Place fat side up in the center of the pan then spread dijon mustard over the top and sprinkle brown sugar over the dijon mustard to create crust. Let sit open to air in cooler over night.

3) Roast oven to 375F for 40-45min, check the pork&apos;s temperature in the middle of the roast with a thermometer to read 65C. 



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50388" image="">Add all ingredient well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50393" image="">1) Apples need to be peeled, cored and 1/3 medium dice

2) Place apple, lemon juice and 1/4 cup of water in a saucepan over medium-high heat bring to the boil then reduce heat to low and then stiring occasionaly until apples are very soft

3) Cool slightly then add sugar

4) blend all ingredient until smooth

5) Transfer to a shallow hotel pan and cover surface with plastic wrap. Cool completely and rabley. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50416" image="">1) Split breast lengthwise. Preheat oven to 375F. Coat Turkey with oil. 

4) Rub cajun spice on the turkey breast pieces, and coat thoroughly.

5) Place rubbed turkey on parchment lined baking sheets and roast in oven until internal temp reaches 74c, let rest for 10 minutes then transfer to hot holding to hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50420" image="">1) Carve a 125g Piece of the cajun turkey breast and place on plate, serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50734" image="">1. Cut butternut squash to meduim dice.
2. Fine dice sage.
3. Mix all ingredients.
4. Roast in 375F oven until soft for about 20minutes.
5. Put in baine marie until service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50800" image="">1. Toast bread
2. Spread ricotta 
3. Place butternut squash dice on
4. Sprinkle pumpkin seeds
5. Serve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51018" image="">Place all dry ingredients into a bowl and whisk to combine, remove whisk and set aside.

Pour in cream and stir the dough to combine.

Turn out onto a floured table and knead 3-4 times, with floured hands just until it comes together.

Press into a rectangular shape and cut triange shaped wedges (approx 130g wedges)

Brush the tops with additonal cream.

Bake at 375F for 25 minutes. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51294" image="">Rub tofu with oil and then roll arounbd in cajun spice to coat thoroughly.

Roast in a hot oven.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55651" image="">1) Bring butter to room temperature.

2) Chop herbs and add everything into mixer with paddle attachment.

3) Combine well so herbs are evenly mixed. You may have to scrape down the sides of the bowl 1-2 times between mixes.

4) Roll in plastic wrap in a cylinder shape.

5) Date and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56733" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Dijon Roasted Pork Loin

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

PUT ALL SPICES IN A SACHET/ CHEESECLOTH.

PREHEAT OVEN TO 325F

1) In a large rondo over MEDIUM heat add oil and onions and sweat until slightly soft. They should not get too much colour on them.

2) Add garlic and cook 1-2 minutes until fragrant.

3) Add cabbage, wine and vinegar. Bring to a simmer, stir well and cover with a lid or foil (tight) and place in warmed oven.

4) After 45 minutes, take out, stir well and put back in oven for 15 more minutes.

5) Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.</Recipe>
</Recipes>
