<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients and tools
        2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15
        minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

        2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil. Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4
        minutes.

        2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar. Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is
        dissolved and well incorporated.

        2. Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink.
        Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs
        clear

        2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice
        and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

        3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-27492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Heat up oil in large sauce pot over medium low heat.

        2. Add garlic and and gently cook for 10 minutes. That&apos;s right, 10 minutes. Then add ginger puree and
        continue gently cooking for another 5-10 minutes. Stir it alot to make sure it doesn&apos;t burn, but really
        cook it out.

        3. Add kecap manis and rice vinegar. Bring to a simmer for 10-15 minutes over medium heat. Add corn starch
        slurry and simmer for another 5 minutes until thick.

        4. Do not strain.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-28258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Fill kettle with ROOM TEMPERATURE water. Do Not tutnr the kettle on.
        2. Place the noodles into the water fully submerging the noodles. Mix the noodles around until they have
        loosened up and move freely and un-forzen
        3. Noodles should be firm but not crispy.
        4. Remove from kettle and let drain.
        5. Lightly oil the noddles and store them labeled and rotated correctly.
        6. Noodles are to be cook &quot;a-la-minute&quot; on the station as needed

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-28301" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-30552" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine hot water and beef base and bring to a boil to incorporate. Set aside.

        2. Combine sesame oil and canola oil in large pot over medium low heat. When oil is warm (not hot!) add garlic,
        black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, korean red pepper flakes and korean chili paste. Infuse in oil until
        garlic is soft and spices are aromatic, about 5 minutes.

        3. Add warm beef stock, soy sauce and sugar and bring to a simmer. Allow to simmer for 15-20 minutes until
        flavours are well incorporated.

        *It may be necessary to thicken sauce with corn starch to bring to desired consistency. General rule of thumb is
        about 4 oz of corn starch slurry per litre of sauce.


        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergens:

        Sesame
        Soy
        Wheat
        Gluten

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-31128" image="">1) Combine all well with whisk. Taste for seasoning.

        Allergens:

        Sesame
        Soy
        Mustard
        Shellfish
        Wheat
        Gluten
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1) In large stock pot, bring water to a boil. Add concentrate and stir throughly. Use
        immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar. Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken).

        cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1) Blend the hell out of it.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-36599" image="">1) In a pot, mix tamarind paste and water and palm sugar. Heat until sugar has
        dissolved. Add korean chili paste.

        2) In a seperate pot, heat oil and cook garlic puree for about 10 minutes until it is no longer bitter to smell.

        3) In 20 L cambro, combine fish sauce, vinegar, and tamrind paste mixture and garlic. Blend with immersion
        blender, thicken with corn starch slurry. Label, Date, Refrigerate.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-37171" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

        2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

        3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour
        or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

        4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44601" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1.

        2.

        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


        Prep:

        - Process all ingredients into a size that will fit easily and not cause problems in the Vitamix. Also, find the
        PLUNGER for the Vitamix, as you will not be able to do this job without it.

        - The Coconut Milk in this recipe will be used to loosen then process of Puree-ing the Green Curry Base Paste.
        Use Water only if necessary.

        - Once processed ingredients and Coconut Milk are ready to go, Vitamix all of these ingredients into a paste.

        - Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

        ***This can be made in large batches, and frozen for future use if vac-packed. A Green Curry &quot;Base&quot;
        recipe only contains 4.62Kg of this base (HALF), to the rest of its ingredients.

        Any questions? - Ask Chef...

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-45371" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-47541" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED
        STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.blend together and use
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50372" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1) Split pork loin in to quarters lengthwise. Should have 4 tube like pieces. In shallow pan or bag marinate
        pork for 24 hours making sure it&apos;s fully covered by the marinade.

        2) Remove from marinade and place on a lined baking sheet on top of a wire rack.

        3) Roast pork at 425F atop a wire racks on a tin foil lined sheet pan until an internal temp of 144F is
        achieved. Reserve leftover maridande to recude until proper consistency to coat the cooked meat is reached.

        3) Allow the meat to rest. Coat with reduction as needed

        4) Reserve excess marinade reduce in a pot until thick and syurupy. Cube up pork in to 1/4&quot; pieces and toss
        with reduced marinade to add flavour and moisture back in.

        Portioning: 115g

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50746" image="">1) Combine all ingredients in a pot, heat at medium until sugar dissolves. Then remove
        from heat.

        2) Cool fully before using as marinade or if using later, store in appropriate sized vessel, label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-51828" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-52459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Mix all ingredients together EXCEPT green onions.

        2. Add sliced green onions last.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55419" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
        2. Sweat garlic, shallot, lemon grass in oil.
        3. Add curry paste and cook until encorperated.
        4. Add coconut milk and simmer for 15 minutes.
        5. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55484" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Warm oil over medium heat in pot.

        2) Sweat garlic, stirring constantly.

        3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer.

        4) Thicken w/ corn starch slurry.

        5) Taste for seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56631" image="">Method:

        - use a vitamix to make this sauce. It is essential that you use a blender strong enough to puree the cashews in
        the sauce so it is not grainy. If you do not have a vitamix, pre soak the cashews in hot water for a minimum of
        1 hr before making the sauce.
        - place all ingredients in the vitamix, puree until smooth
        - adjust consistency with water until desired consistencty is reached
        - adjust seasoning - acid (tamarind), heat(sambal), sweet(sugar), salt(veg fish sauce) to desired taste
        - label, date, hold for service
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic and lemongrass and saute until fragrant,
        about 2-3 minutes. Add yellow curry paste and saute until fragrant, about 1 minute more.

        2. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer. Allow to simmer for 10 minutes. Strain through
        fine chinois. Add fish sauce and adjust seasoning.
        3. Thicken with corn starch.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place all ingredients in a large pot.

        2. Bring to a simmer and thicken with a corn starch slurry

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57959" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place all ingredients in a large pot.

        2. Warm until sugar dissolves.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-61685" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep is used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Place coconut oil in a rondo over medium heat.
        2. Once warm add curry paste and sweat until fragrant, stirring so paste does not burn (3-4 minutes). You want
        to draw out as much flavour as possible in this step.
        3. Add coconut milk, lime leaves (no stems) and bring to a simmer.
        4. Simmer until desired consistency is reached.
        5. Remove from heat, add fish sauce &amp; palm sugar and adjust seasoning. Remove lime leaves.
        6. Curry should be spicy/ sweet/ salty &amp; slighty sour.
        Cool, label and store.
        Rotate this item with older product.
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
