<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

        PREP RECIPE

        1. Over medium heat, heat oil

        2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

        3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions
        begin to soften

        4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and
        distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

        5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in
        bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
        2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

        Allergens:

        No known priority allergens
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26169" image="">1. Heat butter chicken in steamer until hot throughout
        2. Transfer to serving vessel to hold for service
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
        2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and
        serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26231" image="">1) Chop thyme and rosemary finely. Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon
        juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Dairy
        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Preheat oven to 375*F. Pull out garlic butter to soften, or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic
        wrap until it is spreadable.

        2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

        3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter. Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet
        for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

        4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-28323" image="">Serve ingredients in the indicated proportions.

        Place the butter chicken on top of the rice.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-28324" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-29315" image="">1) In tilt kettle or large steam kettle over medium heat, add oil. When oil is hot,
        add garlic, ginger and cayenne. Saute until cayenne is cooked out and garlic and ginger are no longer potent
        when smelled, about 5-10 minutes.

        2) Add crushed tomato, diced tomato, cream, honey, kasoori methi and bring to a simmer. Add seasoning and taste.
        Adjust if necessary. Puree with immersion blender to break up the diced tomatoes and ensure that everything is
        combined well.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1) Prepare and Ice bath

        2) Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes. Immidiately put into ice
        bath. Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

        3) Just prior to service, add oil to flat top, and once oil is hot, add green beans. Saute for 1 minute and s&amp;p
        mix. Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34085" image="">1) Combine everything except chicken.

        2) Incorporate chicken and allow to marinate for at least 24 hours.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1) Blend the hell out of it.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35823" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut potatoes in half then steam until tender, about 15 minutes.

        2. On medium low heat, add oil to large rondeau. Add cumin seeds and toast until fragrant, 30 seconds to 1
        minute. Add onion, coriander, chili powder, turmeric, jalapeno and garam masala. Saute until onion is soft and
        spices are fragrant.

        3. Add garlic and ginger and saute for 1 minute more.

        4. Add tomato paste and saute for 4 minute. Add diced tomatoes and saute 1 minute more.

        5. Add cooked potatoes and saute until starting to turn brown. Add cauliflower, stir well to combine.

        6. Add fenugreek, lime juice and fresh coriander and stir well to combine.

        7. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-36043" image="">Serve in the indicated proportion.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-37050" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42319" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In rondeau over medium heat, add oil and butter. Once oil and butter are warm, add garlic, ginger and crushed
        chili. Saute for 2-3 minutes.

        2. Add all spices except salt and sugar. Continue sauteing until spices are cooked out, about another 5 minutes.

        3. Add crushed tomato, salt and sugar. Bring to a simmer.

        4. Add water and bring back to a simmer. Add cream and kasoori methi.

        5. Taste for seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42320" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine yogurt and spices. Mix to combine well. Reserve marinade.

        2. Cut Paneer into 1&quot; chunks and pour marinade over top. Combine gently to get the marinade over all the
        paneer chunks. Allow to marinate at least 2 hours or overnight.

        3. Preheat oven to 500*F. Place paneer on foil lined baking sheets. Broil for 5 minutes or until paneer turns
        golden brown. Reserve for making Paneer Tika Masala

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42356" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Make Paneer gravy as per recipe.

        2. Make and broil paneer as per recipe.

        3. Blanch green peas in hot water, and shock in cold water. Reserve for paneer tika masala.

        4. Thin out gravy with a bit of water and bring to a simmer. When warm, combine broiled paneer, peas and paneer
        sauce. Hold warm for service.

        *This recipe should make enough for one shallow hotel pan/cassrole serving vessel..

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-42358" image="">1) Make Paneer Tika Masala as per recipe.

        2) Upon order, place appropriate amount of paneer masala on top of rice. Serve immediately.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-42370" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-44570" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Amanda

        Allergens:
        Method:

        *NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in
        advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

        2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp
        should reach 165F


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-47340" image="">serve in the indicated proportions</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn
        heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

        Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

        ***Note***

        This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a
        *free* by-product.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.If using put strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t
        find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

        2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the
        water to a FULL boil.

        3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not
        stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
        APPROX 7 MINUTES

        4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all
        pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

        5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-54176" image="">1. Reheat cooked pasta in blancher until hot.

        2. Place hot pasta on plate, top with 2 pieces of chicken and ladle of sauce.

        3. Garnish with chopped parsley.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Thick cut the cabbage and apples.

        2. Sautee the onions and garlic first, add the cabbage, apples, vinegar, salt and pepper. Place a lid on the pot
        and cook out for 20 minutes.

        3. Check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56115" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Amanda

        Allergens:
        Method:

        *NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in
        advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

        2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp
        should reach 165F


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56552" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In a large rondo over MEDIUM heat, add olive oil, onion, peppers, garlic, thyme and S&amp;P and sweat,
        stirring occasionally until fragrant.

        2. Add tomatoes and simmer.

        3. Add eggplant &amp; zucchini and slowly cook until slightly softened. DO NOT LET THESE 2 VEGETABLES TURN TO
        MUSH!

        4. Turn off heat, add chopped parlsey and check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56740" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Heat up tilt skillet over medium/ high heat.

        2) Season chicken with salt &amp; pepper, place skin side down in skillet and sear until skin is golden brown.
        Remove chicken and reserve.

        3) In the tilt skillet add olive oil, onion, celery, bell peppers and garlic and sweat until fragrant (3-5
        minutes). Remove and reserve.

        3) Add tomatoes, capers and dry oregano to the pan. Place seared chicken into sauce and bring to a simmer.

        4) Simmer for approximately 30 minutes or until chicken is fully cooked.(Internal temperature of 165F)

        5) Remove chicken from the sauce and return vegetables into sauce. Check thickness of sauce and reduce if
        needed.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56884" image="">1. Reheat cooked pasta in blancher until hot.

        2. Drain well and toss pasta in mixing bowl with a ladle of ratatouille.

        3. Garnish with parmesan and chopped parsley.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57710" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-57712" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-57808" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Amanda

        Allergens:
        Method:

        *NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in
        advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

        2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp
        should reach 165F


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-57809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Amanda

        Allergens:
        Method:

        *NOTE* 220g of perogy = 7 pieces

        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in
        advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

        2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp
        should reach 165F


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58757" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Amanda

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, drop in prozen perogies and cook till they float. If cooking in
        advance; cool down and reserve for service using HACCP procedure. If using immediately; Hot hold for service.

        2. On an oiled flat top fry the perogies lightly on one side, cook until hot all the way through internal temp
        should reach 165F


        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
