<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-6989" image="">1. Heat up oil in large pot or tilt skillet, add onion and cook till soft and transparent, add garlic and oregano cook for 5 minutes, add in ground beef and break up in to small pieces as it cooks. Cook beef until almost all water is gone and meat is small brown crispy pieces.

2. Remove from and stir tomato sauce in to the cooked beef. Once combined, put in to apropriate container and cool fully.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8202" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.mix together and label store with rest of spices

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9710" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-9712" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredients.
2. Mix all togther.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat well
3.Bake on sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Thinly slice up green onion.

2.  Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine everything and mix thoroughly.
2. Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26056" image="">1. Cut tomatoes in half horizontally. Squeeze romano oil on tomato and season with salt &amp; pepper

2. Grill seed side down for 2-3 minutes or until grill marks are visible and tomato begins to soften.

3.  Hold for service or serve immidiately.

1 portion (ea) of grilled tomato is 2 halves

Allergens:

No known priority allergens.

Average Roma tomato = 90 g
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

NOTE: this is 2 boxes of tomatoes.

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice. Use the same dicing blade for the red onions.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26063" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine half of blueberries and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the blueberries and heat until no longer frozen but still firm, about 5-8 minutes.  You want some texture in the compote.

3. Thicken with corn starch slurry.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and salt, and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil.

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes. In a cycle of letting them brown, and scraping and stirring with a wooden spoon, until onions are a dark golden brown. Add a splash of water cold if the bottom browning is sticking too much.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Dairy
Sulphites
Method:

1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 375*F.  Pull out garlic butter to soften,  or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic wrap until it is spreadable.

2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter.  Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26333" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fine chop parsley and thyme.  Combine with lemon &amp; lime juice, mayo and seasoning.  

2. Taste for seasoning and adjust if necessary.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

1. Preheat oven to 425*F

2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house rub. Mix well.

3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG RATHER THAN ROAST).

4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let cool.

5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

6. Check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1)  Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

2)  Remove baskets from deep fryer.  Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

3)  Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil.  Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

4)  Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil.  Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

5)  Place in appropriate container once cooled.  Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
soy (from tortilla)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1)  In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

2)  Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Egg
Milk

Method:

1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.  

2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28217" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Blend everything together except seasame seed.

3. Place in container stir in seasame seed.


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Utensils needed:blender scale cambro


METHOD
BLEND ALL INGREDIENTS IN BLENDER

ALLERGENS
- SOY
-SESAME
- gluten/wheat, sulphites </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28251" image="">1)  Season and grill chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked.

2)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and garnish with guacamole and lemon herb aioli.  Top cooked chicken breast with cheese until melted.

3) Add tomato, cooked bacon and citrus arugula.

4) Close bun and top with pickle skewer.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28286" image="">1)  Grab your #12 scoop.  Grab scrambled eggs from hot holding vessel.  Put on plate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28291" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. This is 1 whole tomato (2 halves)
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34892" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Scale out ingredients.

2. In a sauce pot combine water and buuter and bring to a simmer, Add powder and stir for a minute.

3. Place in container and hold for service in a WARM place.
 
Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:scale pot whisk bowl container</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Cut lemons in quarters. Crush garlic and slice shallots.

2)  Combine all except chicken breast.  Stir well to combine.

3)  In a non-reactive container (plastic) add chicken.  Add marinade and JUST ENOUGH OIL to COAT not COVER the chicken breasts and mix well.  Allow to marinate for 8 hours or overnight.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35230" image="">1)  In an appropriate sized pot, make veg stock as per recipe.  Bring to a simmer.  Add  seed less guajillo peppers, poblanos and tomatoes together.  Bring back to a simmer and allow to simmer 5 minutes.

2)  Meanwhile, in a large saute pan heat the oil.  When oil is hot, add whole garlic, diced onion and saute until starting to brown.  Save oil.

3)  Blend the tomatoes, chiles, garlic and onion together in blender until very well pureed, about 3 minutes.

4)  Add mixture back to a pot and bring back to simmer for 3 more minutes.  Strain into appropriate sized insert and label, date, refrigerate. 

 Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35272" image="">1) Remove and discard stem, cut letuce in quarters, then shave off thin strips.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.

Average weight of a head of Iceberg is 470g with 10% yield loss for core and outer leaves. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35273" image="">1) Drain liquid from pickles.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35653" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  Preheat grill to high.

2)  Add oil to portobello mushroom and coat well.  Add
salt and pepper, put in oven and roast for 10 minutes or until mushrooms are tender throughout.  Reserve for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35655" image="">1)  Prepare portobellos according to recipe.

2)  Prepare sundried tomato mayo according to recipe.

3)  Place portobello mushroom on grill to heat through.  Place crumbled feta cheese in the mushroom cap and then cover with provolone.  Grill until heated through and cheese is melted, about 2-3 minutes.

4)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill.  Once toasted spread sundried tomato mayo on both sides.  Place grilled portobello on bottom of bun and top with arugula.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35713" image="">1)  Dredge Chicken Breast in house rub.  

2)  Placed dredged breast on parchment lined baking sheet.

3)  Repeat until production for the day is complete.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35714" image="">1)  Dredge chicken breast in cajun spice and grill until 50% cooked and starting to char and blacken.  Put in oven until cooked through.  

2)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill and dress bottom of bun with mayonnaise, lettuce, red onion, and tomato.  Put chicken back on grill and top with cheese. Place under steamer lid to reheat chicken and melt cheese, about 2 minutes.

3)  Place on top of bottom bun with toppings and close bun.  Garnish with dill pickle and serve immidiately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35772" image="">1) Produce as per prep recipe.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1)  Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray.  Place egg in egg poacher cup.  Steam for 8 minutes until cooked.

Allergens:

Soy, Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Sulphite
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor with blade attachments, add drained capers, roasted garlic paste, fresh basil, drained sundried tomatoes and lemon juice.  Blitz until blended together very well.  

2)  Stir in oil WITH A SPOON (do not puree) and season with salt and pepper.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38661" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Make sundried tomato paste as per recipe.

2)  In mixing bowl, combine sundried tomato paste and mayonnaise.  Combine well with a spatula.  Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42353" image="">
Prep:

- Quarter Corn Tortillas. 2.5 Packages of Corn Tortillas will yield 2 Deep Hotel pans full of Corn Chips.

- Using Paper Towel, create a large pan or bowl for draining the excess oil off of the Tortilla Chips, after they&apos;ve come out of the Deep Fryer.

- At 350 Degrees (F) in the Deep Fryer, fry NO MORE THAN HALF OF A STACK OF CORN TORTILLAS (QUARTERED) at a time.

- Using a Spider, or Long Tongs - KEEP TORTILLAS MOVING AT ALL TIMES. 

- Depending on how dark the Deep Fryer oil is, fry the Tortilla Chips until they are brown (keeping in mind that they will cook for a little while longer once they&apos;ve been taken out of the fryer. 

- As soon as the chips are out drying, salt lightly using the Windsor coarse grain salt. The salt will only stick during this stage of production - be sure to catch it!

Label/Date/Store

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43964" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cook chicken on grill.
2. Heat bun.
3. Once chicken is cooked brush both sides with sweet chili sauce.
4. Place bun on plate put chicken on bun top with slaw and top of bun.
5. Serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.steam beets in steamer till soft
3.peel under water once cool enough
4.cut into pieces and toss with remaining ingredients
5. spread on roasting pan
6. Roast 200C/400F 15 minute or till done
7.Hot hold in insert for service covered
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g

Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
serving dish

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48321" image="">Allergen:

egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Cook Eggs, Hollandaise,

Place English muffins on plate, top with bacon, sliced tomato, add an egg and top with hollandaise.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48359" image="">Allergen:

egg, sulphites, milk, wheat, gluten

Icon:

vegetarian

Method:

Cook Eggs, Hollandaise, 

Place English muffins on plate, top with sauteed spinach feta, add an egg and top with hollandaise.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50449" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Put all ingrediets to a food precessor and pulse 5 times. Scrape the sides and pulse the mixture until all ingredients are evenly mixed. If it the mixture looks dry, add olive oil.

2. Transfer into a container and refrigerate for 30 minutes.

3. Shape the chilled chickpea mixture into burger patties. 
150 grams per piece. Lay it flat on a baking sheet.

4. Bake it in 350F for 15 minutes, flip burgers and cook for additional 10 minutes or until browned.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50462" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all ingredient well. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50465" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

Toss chicken in oil and hot sauce, add rough chopped lemon

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50466" image="">Grill up the marinated chicken. 

Brush the cooked chicken with Franks Hot Sauce. 

Toast up the bun.

Put together the sandwich with the blue cheese dressing, the glazed chicken, and the lettuce.

Serve with the pickle spear on the side.   </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50485" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

1) Roughly chop onion in to bit size pieces, add to robocoupe and puree.

2) Add all other ingredients to a bowl and mix well with whisk, and season to taste with salt.

3)cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50488" image="">1) Unwrap smoked brisket, place on meat slicer, and cut to 1/8&quot; slices.

2) Place in an appropriate sized container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50491" image="">1) Butter one side on each piece of rye, and place on the flattop.

2) Put smoked meat on the flattop, drizzle 1-2 tbsp water over the meat to create steam, heat it through.

3) Place saurkraut on flat top and drizzle with 1-2 tbsp of water to create steam, heath through

4) Apply Russian dressing to both sides of the bread while on the flattop, place swiss chesse on 1 side of bread, top with hot smoked meat. top with Saurkraut.

5) place other slice of bread on top of saurkraut &amp; toast until golden on both sides

6) Once the bread is crispy and brown, move to cutting board. Slice diagonally, corner to corner. Place on the plate and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50511" image="">Dip them in the egg mixture and pan fry them. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50527" image="">Nice warm and crispy french toast and on top blueberry compot;Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50555" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Omelet.jpg">1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

2. In one side of the flat top. Add oil, vegetables and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

3. In the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and cheese and folder over. 

4. Garnish with chopped parsly and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50556" image="">1) Preheat flat top 350*F.

2) In one side of the flat top. Add oil,  vegetables and salt. Cook about 2 minutes.

3) in the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg, once egg starts set.Add the sauted vegetables and cheese, folded over, garnish with parsley and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50598" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Put bowl of stand mixer in freezer for about 5 minutes to ensure it&apos;s cool.

2. Add whipping cream to bowl of stand mixer with whisk attachment. Once cream begins to thicken, add icing sugar and lemon zest. Continue to whip until stiff. DO NOT OVERMIX.

3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

4. Can be held for 24 - 36 hours or until it begins to break.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50656" image="">1. Warm up bun on grill/flat top
2. Spread bbq sauce on both side of the bun.
3. Put lettuce on bottom side of the bun, next is tomatoes,chickpea patty, smashed avocado then pickled carrots.
4. Put top bun. Stab with bamboo skewer.
5. Serve!!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50662" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50785" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sauces all together.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50803" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Char jalapenos on the grill until cooked.

3. Clean and de-seed the jalapenos.

4. Blitz jalapeno, lemon juice, salt/pepper in vitamix.

5. Mix honey, jalapeno mixture and mayo.

6. Taste and adjust as needed

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51202" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53056" image="">average roma tomato weighs approx 90g

this recipe makes 26 x 1/2 tomatoes

1 portion = 2 tomato 1/2&apos;s or 1 whole tomato</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53081" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients into food processor or blender and puree on high speed until smooth creamy texture.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53084" image="">Portion burgers to 140g.

Dress bun top and bottom with tahini dressing.

Place cooked burger on bottom bun.

Top with smashed avocado &amp; tomato.

Top with citrus arugula.

Close bun, secure with pick.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54583" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE


Grill the chicken breast with some of the BBQ rub spice and glaze with BBQ sauce when it is nearly done.

Toast the bun and sauce the top bun, put the caramelized onions on the bottom bun. 

Place the BBQ chicken breast on the bottom bun and top it with the lettuce and tomato. 

Place the lid on the bun and serve the pickle on the side.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55116" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Chilaquiles.jpg">1) Warm tomato sauce in a saute pan.

2) Cook egg on flattop.

3) When egg is almost cooked add tortilla chips into pan with sauce and gently fold so all chips get coated in sauce without breaking too many chips.

4) Transfer to plate, add cooked egg on top. 

5) Garnish with crumbled feta, brunoise red onion &amp; cilantro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55131" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Small dice jalapenos and tomatoes. Mince cilantro.

2. In a bowl combine all ingredents. Mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. Check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: Muffaleta

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out all ingredients.

2. In a Robot Coupe add all ingredents and pulse until combined and coarse/slightly chunky.

3. DO NOT PUREE UNTILL SMOOTH this should be a slightly chunky spread with evident pieces of olive and such.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56453" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine half of strawberries and rhubarb and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the fruit and heat until no longer frozen but still firm, about 5-8 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56454" image="">1)  Grill seasoned chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked. 

2) Grill pineapple on both sides.

3) Brush chicken and pineapple on both sides with Teriyaki sauce and quickly glaze on grill. Do not leave on grill too long or sauce will burn. 

4) Place pineapple on chicken, then cheese and melt.

5)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and spread mayo on both sides.

6) Place lettuce, tomato and onion on bottom bun.

7) Place chicken and pineapple on top, close bun and skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56509" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Breakfast Quesadilla.jpg">1. Place tortilla on flattop, spread cheese evenly on both sides (this will be the glue to hold the whole thing together).

2. Add remaining ingredients evenly over the entire surface so each bite gives you all the ingredients..

3. Fold in half and cook on both sides until golden brown and crispy.

4. Cut into 4 even pieces. Place crispy tortilla strips on plate and place quesadilla on top to prevent bottom from getting soggy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56510" image="">1)  Grill or toast ciabatta until crisp and warm.

2)  Sread evenly with guacamole, than top with sweet potato hash and salsa

3)  Garnish with arugula and  toasted pumpkin seeds.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56637" image="">1. Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in eggnog mixture and put on griddle.  Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56695" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56696" image="">1. On flattop make omelet.

2. Warm mushrooms and at the last minute mix w/ pesto.

3. Place mushrooms in the middle of omelet, sprinkle cheese and fold shut.

4. Serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56697" image="">1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

2. In one side of the flat top. Add oil, asparagus and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

3. In the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and cheese and folder over. 

4. Serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1) Spread dry oats on a sheet pan and bake in a 300F oven for 10-15 minutes. This toasting will improve the flavour of the oats.

2)  Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.  

3)  In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, cinnamon, salt and vanilla.

4)  Simmer mixture for 7-10 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still just a little chewy.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56959" image="">1) Pour oats into bowl, place dollop of yogurt in the middle.

2) Garnish with black pepper and strawberry compote.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56966" image="">1) Pour oats into bowl, place dollop of yogurt in the middle.

2) Garnish with maple syrup and thawed diced apples.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57344" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.  

2)  In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, squash puree, brown sugar, cinnamon, nutmeg, salt and vanilla.

3)  Simmer mixture for 25-30 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still just a little chewy.

4)  Hold hot for service, or if preparing in advance, chill in blast chiller and label, date, refrigerate.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Slice strawberries when they are partially frozen(rough is fine) and place in suitable sized pot.

2. Add remaining ingredients except slurry. Bring to a boil.

3. Add slurry to thicken and remove from heat.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-59667" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Grind flax seeds with garlic.

2. Small DICE- Mushrooms, onion. In oil cook onions, mushrooms &amp; garlic mix. Cool down.

3. Combine mushroom mix with rest of ingredients.

4. Chill for 1 hour before scooping into 140g patties.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-59668" image="">


Peel onion, Slice 1/4 inch rings

coat in oil and seasoning

Grill to order</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-59669" image="">


Combined and mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60321" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Soy,
Method:

1. Chill for 1 hour before scooping into 150g and form patty shape

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning: 150GRAMS 

Utensils needed: 150g scoop
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60324" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-61253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place beets in a food processor, pulse 2-3 times.  DO NOT puree, there needs to be texture for the patties to hold together.

2. Fine dice onion.

3. Transfer beets to a large bowl, add other ingredients and stir to combine.  If texture is too mushy, add more bread crumbs until desired consistancy. NOTE the bread crumbs and quinoa will slowly absorb excess moisture over time.

4. Scale and shape burgers and place them on a parchment lined baking sheet. 

5. Bake patties in oven for 15 min, flip over and bake for a further 15 min. Hold for service OR

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:
patty portion weight 160 grams

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61621" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. gather all ingredients, and line up all the 2&quot; hotelpans you need for the number of lasagna you&apos;re making.

2. Combine ricotta and eggs and mix well.

3. build layers in this order

Bottom layer: Meat sauce 750ml
                     Noodles 8
                     Ricotta/egg mixture 500ml
                     Noodles 8
                     Meat sauce 750ml
                     Cheese sauce 500ml
                     noodle 8
                     Meat sauce 750ml
                     Cheese sauce 500ml
Top with:        mozza 500g and parm 100g
If prepairing ahead of time, leave off mozza/parm topper till you&apos;re baking them.

4. Bake at 300f for 45 minutes. Ensure noodles are cooked and internal temperature reaches 160f
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61663" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Rinse black beans well, lay evenly on a baking tray and dry in medium oven.

2. Saute onion, garlic in olive oil until fragrant (about 5 minutes).

3. Working in batches in a food processor, pulse all ingredients ensuring you leave a little texture in the mix.

4. Check for seasoning, form into 160g patties.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61664" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix ground flax meal with water, stir and let stand for 5 minutes. 

2. This is the equivalent to one egg.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61665" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Deforst mango &amp; puree in a blender.
2. Mix with remaining ingredients ensuring there are some chunks of avocado.
3. Check for seasoning.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-12347" image="">1. Warm black bean burger in oven until hot.

2. Toast bun, spread mango avocado sauce on both sides of bun.

3. Top with tomato, lettuce and pickled red onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61687" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62016" image="">completely thaw block of frozen spinach

in small batches, squeeze out excess water from spinach

place squeezed spinach in perforated pan or basket strainer to allow any excess water to drip away

place in appropriate container 

label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-63018" image="">1. Dress top &amp; bottom of toasted bun with tahini dressing.

2. Place cooked burger in.

3. Top with amashed avocado, tomato &amp; citrus arugula.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64882" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Dessed jalapenos.

2. Combine all ingredients in a wide rondo, bring to a boil and simmer stirring occasionally until thick.

NOTE: It wil get thicker once cooled so don&apos;t reduce too much. You can put a small amount on a plate and wait a couple minutes for it too cool to check it&apos;s consistency.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-66101" image="">1)  Season patty and cook on flat-top until well done (71*C). Top TMRW pattie with 1 slice of havarti cheese and melt onto pattie.

2)  While patty is grilling, toast bun on grill and add vegan mayo to both sides of bun add lettuce to the bottom portion of bun.

3)  Place cooked patty on top of lettuce and tomato jam on the pattie. Close with the bun top, pickle and bamboo skewer and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
