<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-57639" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing &quot;S&quot; blade
3.store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26622" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Saute the onion and garlic in the butter unitl softened and fragrant.

2. On a low- medium heat add flour to make a roux.

3. Dilute the roux incrementally with milk stirring vigorously between additions unitl all of the milk is incorporated.

4. Season to taste. Adjust as necassary

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26628" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix, heat to a boil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10502" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27328" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine dry ingredients and mix

Melt butter

Combine wet ingredients and mix, including the melted butter 

Combine wet and dry ingredients and chopped jalapenos and mix unitl just combined ****do not overmix

Pour the batter into a parchment lined hotel pan and bake at 350F until the cornbread is fully cooked and golden brown on the top. 

Cut into portions</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33559" image="">
METHOD:

Prep:

- This recipe should take 2 days - no more, no less, however, the curing process can be elongated, depending on time, to 3-4 days.

- TO CURE: Take Brown Sugar, and Salt - and rub the Pork Belly down thoroughly. Place in a Hotel Pan, SKIN SIDE DOWN, and let the sugar and salt begin drawing out moisture and breaking down the outside of the Belly. IMPORTANT: in the morning, when you come in for your shift the next day - TURN THE PORK BELLY OVER, SO THAT THE SKIN SIDE IS UP AND OPEN TO THE AIR. 

- Pre-Heat the Convection Oven to 325F/180C.

- Cover Pork Belly with remaining ingredients, and roast for 25 minutes. Then, turn the oven to 425F, and finish for and extra 10-15 minutes. 

- Once Pork Belly is cool, remove its skin layer and discard. Cut the meat, and prepare for next steps.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27300" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place perogies in perforated pans lined with parchment and steam for 5-6 minutes 

2. Once steamed; add a small amount of oil to a flat top,  over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add steamed perogies to flat top and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26051" image="">1. Combine lemon juice, herbs, garlic, salt &amp; pepper in a 20 L container, blend with a  immersion blender. Puree everthing to smoth add mayo &amp; sour cream, Puree till everthing is mix.
2. Store in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

Allergens:

Dairy/Milk
Egg
Mustard</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44083" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Prep:

- Basically, this is a bound gel of sweetened Tamarind Paste. 1 Jar is 300g, so the recipe is built around that.

- Fresh Tamarind, which isn&apos;t very widely available here in North America, is not very tart at all like Tamarind Paste. Citric Acid, other additives, and industrial processes force it to be this way - so it needs to be let out and sweetened. Allspice in this recipe is used to mask some of the bendinf that this ingredient must go through. 

- Place all ingredients into a Vitamix. Keep Xanthan Gum aside.

- Start the Vitamix, and slowly raise the speed setting until you&apos;re working with a fine mixture of all of the aforementioned ingredients. On &quot;High&quot; (the button to the left of the speed setting nob), remove the plunger from the pitcher base, and add the Xanthan Gum while the mixture is moving. 

- You should know, with this recipe, and all recipes requiring a binder like Xanthan Gum, how a thickener is doing in its job. To test this mixture, turn the Vitamix off, and dip the plunger into the mixture, then raise it to see how slowly it falls off the plunger. It should fall slowly. If it doesn&apos;t, add more Xanthan Gum binder, and continue. The idea is that this will become like a paste that will get things dipped into it.

- Don&apos;t worry - if you thicken it too much, you can always go backwards and let it out again, easily. This is not like over-cooking a steak. That said, know what you&apos;re looking for, and do it.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32151" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-44550" image="">Allergens:
milk

Icons:
vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-39232" image="">
Prep:

-Cook Potatoes by steaming until tender enough to mash easily

-on low heat, simmer cream, garlic, salt, pepper and butter together 

- In the large Hobart Stand-Mixer near the dish area, combine all of the ingredients except the Cream mixture. Begin mixing when you’re ready, and add cream mixture to reach the consistency you want 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44502" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut broccoli into florets. 

Toss with oil and salt and pepper

Lay out on a parchment lined sheet pan and roast until golden brown at the edges

Toss with lemon juice</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51222" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Trim ends off and peel. Discard

2. Cut and slice as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25381" image="">
PREP RECIPE

combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46500" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Chop, peel, prep all components, mix thoroughly, taste and adjust seasoning as needed.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut okra into slices.

2. Mix water and eggs.

3. Cover okra in flour.

4. Dip okra in egg wash.

5. Coat with cornmeal.

6. Deep fry until crispy.

7. Season as soon as it comes out of fryer.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47196" image="">Allergen:

Peel Daikon, shred into matchsticks.
Heat up pickling liquid.
in two seperate containers, one for carrots one for daikon.
pour liquid to cover them.

label and reserve for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47195" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Peel and small dice lemongrass, shallots
Sautee shallots and garlic until translucent. Add coriander, lemongrass. cook for 10 mins. Add mushrooms, pepper, salt, soy sauce and coconut milk.

Add nutritional yeast. Blitz in a vitamix, check seasoning of paste.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26714" image="">Save all of your green onion, celery, parsley, cilantro, leek  and tomato ends for stocks!!!!!

1. Roast the beef bones for 1 hour at 375-400* then apply the tomato paste and roast for another 40 minutes to and hour.

2. While the bones are roasting - sautee your onions, garlic, leek, carrot and celery on medium heat. Once the onions are soft, add the spices and sautee for another 5 min before putting everything into the steam kettle.

3. Cover the veggies with water and add the bones - bring to a boil and then reduce to just below a simmer. Let it ride for overnight to develop the full flavour - then the next day turn off and add all the vegetable ends and fresh herbs(thyme or rosemary) and let sit for another 30 minutes.

4. Skim off extra fat, strain, downsize and cool down.


The salt in this recipe is an approximate ammount to season the broth if you are using it in a soup etc...</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26308" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 375*F

2)  Place bones on roasting pan or baking sheet and place in oven to roast until golden brown, about 2 hours.  Ensure to move bones around and rotate pan to ensure bones are evenly browned.

3) Once roasted, place bones in large stock pot or steam kettle.  Cover bones with water until just a small amount of bones are sticking out of water.  Bring to a simmer.

4)  Once a simmer is achieved, skim any impurities that rise to the top.  Continue skimming and simmering for at least four hours.  

5)  Add rough chopped onion, celery, and carrot and bay leaf to stock.  Allow to simmer for another 4-8 hours (or overnight).

6)  Remove stock from heat.  Remove bones with tongs and reserve.  Using a pitcher and fine chinous, strain stock into appropriate vessel.  Bones can be covered again with water to make remoulage.   </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56409" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Heat oven to 425F

2. In a large rondeau, heat half of oil over medium-high heat. Working in batches so the mushrooms brown evenly, add half the mushrooms, season with salt and pepper and cook, undisturbed, until browned underneath, about 3 minutes. Stir the mushrooms, then continue to cook until browned all over, about 3 minutes.

3. Transfer to a bowl. Repeat with remaining oil and the remaining mushrooms; transfer them to the medium bowl. Season with salt and pepper and cook, stirring occasionally, until browned and tender, 6 to 8 minutes, lowering the heat as needed to avoid burning. Transfer to the bowl.

4. Reduce the heat to medium and add the butter to the skillet. Once the butter is melted, add the onion, cook until starting to soften, about 5 minutes.

5. Add the kale, garlic, thyme and rosemary, season with salt and pepper and cook out, stirring occasionally, until softened, approx 3 minutes, adding 1 to 2 tablespoons oil if the pan seems dry. Sprinkle with the flour and cook, stirring, until flour is dispersed and lightly toasted, 2 minutes.

6. Stirring constantly, gradually add the stock and  cook over medium heat, stirring occasionally, until thickened, about 5 minutes. 

7. Mix in the parsnips, celery, potatoes, and the sautéed mushrooms and any accumulated juices. Cook untill potatoes and carrots are fork tender. finish with cream and reduce slightly.

8. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed. 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61937" image=""> ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of hot stew at bottom of bowl

2. Top with warm puff pastry

3. Garnish with fresh chopped parsley. 

4. Serve glazed beans and mashed potatoes on side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51265" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve 240g in a bowl if ordered as a side.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26175" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Brisket


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Roughly crush cloves.  Add all ingredients in bowl and mix wel

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62036" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Blend all ingredients together

2. taste for seasoning, Adjust as needed. 

3. Reserve.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over high heat, add oil

2. Once oil is hot and &quot;shimmering&quot;  add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes untill onions are a deep caramel colour.

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37055" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37056" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35815" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52984" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Gently heat bechamel on medium low heat.

2. Once bechamel is hot, add scaled out cheeses, whisking vigerously to incorporate cheese. turn off flame and ensure all cheese is fully melted.

3. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26965" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Fine dice Jalapenos and set aside 

2. In mixer with paddle attachment add bag of corn muffin mix and water.

3. Mix for 1 minute at 2nd speed, scrape down sides, mix  untill batter is smooth.

4. Add corn, jalapenos and cheese, mix just untill thuroughly combined

5. Allow batter to rest for 30 minutes for best results

6. Place in well oiled hotel pans (2&quot; pans half full) Bake at 325F untill fully cooked in the centre and golden brown
aprox 15-20 minutes. Do a cake test to ensure fully baked.

7. Allow to fully cool and cut into portions.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

PREP RECIPE 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51210" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34541" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

*** for yeilding purposes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Gather All ingredients

2.Cut all veg into apropriate shape and size; Dice onions into 1/4 inch pieces dice all peppers the same, removing stems and seeds (discard)

3. Reserve for service


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service quickly steam green beans and toss with s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53256" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine all ingredients. This is used both as marinade and reduced for sauce.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32657" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Marinate chicken in sauce in large container 1-2 hours. 3.5L per box of chicken.

2. Place marniated chicken thighs in large rondeau with the marinating liquid. Bring to a boil and turn down to a simmer and cook chicken until thighs reach internal temperature of 160F. (Roughly one hour) Be sure to stir occasionally.

3. Once chicken is cooked, remove chicken from rondeau in to half hotel pans. Boil remaining sauce on high, until thick and syrupy, pour over chicken.

4. Hold hot for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32658" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Julienne peppers and onions

2.  Heat up oil in wok.  When hot add vegetables and garlic and stir fry for 2 minutes on high heat.   

2. Reserve for Adobo

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54677" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Cut your tofu blocks into 50g pieces. Mix soy with water/lime juice.

3. Slice ginger/chilies and mix them into soy sauce.

4. Marinate tofu in soy for 1 day.

5. Grill for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54827" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of hat potatoes in small service bowl

2. garnish with fresh parsley

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55074" image="">method:

-Combined all ingredients and mix well
-put in a squeeze bottle for service
-store the rest in the fridge, labelled</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

4) Season with salt &amp; pepper. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26181" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Pre heat rationale oven to 250F

2) Remove excess fat from brisket, score fatty side. Rub brisket in Berbere rub.  Set aside.  Brisket can be rubbed up to two days before.

3) Place brisket and braising liquid in deep 6&quot; hotel pan, cover with parchment and then cover insert with aluminum foil.  Fold aluminum foil back about half way so you can see meat and braising liquid.  

4)  Place insert over burners or on french top and bring to a boil.  

5) Place in rationale oven and cook for 12 hours or until tender.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55420" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Cut off top. Scoop out seeds. Peel off exterior skin.

3. Cut into apropriate shape / Size for recipe uses.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55769" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-55766" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-61306" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cut tofu in to 150g, steak style portions. (long flat rectangles)

2. Season with salt, pepper and oil. Grill to add grill marks.

3. Cool and keep for service time. Service time, heat to 74C and hot hold for service.

*cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:















1) Cut tofu in to 150g, steak style portions. (long flat rectangles)

2) Season with salt, pepper and oil. Grill to add grill marks.

3) Cool and keep for service time. Service time, heat to 74c and keep for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37093" image="">1)  Blanch cooked pasta in hot water until it is hot throughout.  Place hot pasta in serving bowl.

2)  Top with 3 meatballs and 180ml of tomato sauce.

3)  Garnish with parmesan cheese and parsley.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62405" image="">This is a yielded prep, not a recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56113" image="">1. Thick cut the cabbage and apples.

2. Sautee the onions and garlic first, add the cabbage and apples. Cook out for 20 minutes, add vinegar, salt and pepper and taste.

Serve hot.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56630" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toss portion of succotash with diced tomato &amp; chives

2. Serve portion in bowl

3. Garnish with basil &amp; crisp shallots

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56629" image="">Method:

-  heat reserved oil from cooking the tofu in large pot or tilt skillet, add diced onion &amp; garlic, saute for 3-4 min until translucent
- add corn, red pepper, okra, beans, green onion, diced seeded jalapeno - saute, stirring frequently until veg is al dente
- add coconut milk, water and simmer for 8-12 minutes uncovered until flavors come together and 1/2 of the liquid evaporates creating a thick creamy &quot;sauce&quot;
- stir in the tofu, check and adjust seasoning ( reserve the remaining tofu for garnish
- remove from heat &amp; hold for service</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9738" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredient
2.trim if not already done and wash
3.cut to 1/4&quot;
4. label, date and refridgerate
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56374" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

1. In large kettle heat oil, add in mirepoix (carrot, celery, onion) and bell pepper. sautee untill onions become translucent and tender.

2. Add in all remaining ingredents. let cook out on lowest setting, stirring often.

3. Beans are done when Pinto beans are tender and all other ingredients become homogeneous and sauce has thickened.

4. Hot hold for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56559" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Sides

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

1.Heat a large saute pan over medium heat. Add the oil, ginger, and minced garlic and saute for 30 seconds. Raise the heat to medium-high, add the beans and stir-fry for 2 minutes.

2. Add  water to the pan. Cook for another 3-4 minutes, partially covered. With 1 minute left, add the maple syrup soy sauce and sesame oil and swirl around the pan to form a glazy sauce.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56328" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Jambalaya bowl, Braised Kale

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


 1.Cut the sausage into 1/4 inch rounds.  In a large rondeau sear the chicken and sausage. Cook until the chicken is cooked through and the sausage is lightly browned. remove chicken and sausage reserve.

2. In the same rondeau (leaving the good bits of chicken and sausage on the bottom of the pan to add flavour)  Sauté the onion, bell pepper, celery, jalapeño and garlic until soft and translucent. 

3. Add rice, liquids and seasonings.  Add in the uncooked rice, chicken stock, crushed tomatoes, old bay seasoning, oregano, cayenne and bay leaf.  Give everything a good stir. reduce to low flame.

4. Cover and cook  25-30 minutes, being sure to stir the mixture every 5 minutes or so (to prevent burning) until the rice is nearly tender.

5.  Add the shrimp.  And cook for a final 5 minutes or so, until the shrimp is pink and opaque. 

6. Add the chicken and sausage back in.

7. Taste and adjust seasoning as needed.  

HOT HOLD/SERVE
   
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56406" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Side dish

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. In a hotel pan place Quinoa, salt and veg stock.

2. Place in steamer until stock is fully absorbed and quinoa is cooked and fluffy.

5. Finish by seasoning with remaining ingredients. Taste for seasoning, adjust as needed and serve immediately.

**Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48263" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Heat the cheese sauce over a medium heat once sauce has reached 165F add the cooked (al dente) noodles and thuroughly mix.Please ensure the noodles are &quot;saucy&quot; before putting into pans. No one likes a dry mac &amp; cheese)

3. Distribute the noodle cheese sauce mix evenly into 2 x 4&quot; hotel pans. Top with mozza and Persiallde (garlic seasoned panko) bake in 350F oven untill cheese is melted and persiallde is a golden brown internal temp should hit 165F.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Dice eggplant, red pepper, zucchini, red onion(keep the red onion seperate for the sauce componant) into half inch cubes, keeping seperate (as they have different cooking times) toss in olive oil and salt and pepper to taste.

2. Roast seperately on baking sheets lined with parchment (do not crowd pan or veg will steam rather than roast!) roast veg 15-20 minutes at 375F undil golden and slightly charred around the edges.

3. In a large stock pot heat the olive oil, once the oil is hot add the onion, keep the flame on high and stir frequently caramelizing the onions, add the chopped garlic and sautee out for 2-3 minutes and tomato paste and cook out 10-15 minutes to get rid of the &apos;tin&apos; taste and to build flavour.

5. Add the diced tomatoes, veg stock, salt &amp; pepper and let stew out another 10-15 minutes.

6.Remove from heat; Add Roasted veg and fold into sauce. finish with fresh basil and parsley. Taste for seasoning and adjust salt as needed.

7. SIDE NOTE; Add more veg stock as needed. Looking for a slightly loose stew concistancy. as it reduces during hot holding use veg stock to loosen it up.

Hot hold/Serve 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Ratatouille

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Puree garlic and olive oil in robot cupe untill smooth. Set aside.

2. Fine mince parsley. Set aside.
 
3. Scale out panko and in a lrge bowl combine all ingredents untill panko thuroughly is coated in garlic oil and parsley mixed throught. 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56950" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot ratatouillie in base of serving dish

2. Add toasted persiallde to the top of the ratatouille and garnish with fresh crumbled goat cheese and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56899" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: SIDES

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Slice tomatoes in half, dice cucumber on a mandoline thinly slice fennel.

2. In a large bowl combine all ingredients thouroughly for even distribution.

3. Ready to serve

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Kale&amp;Quinoa/Green salad

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out all ingredients

2. In a vitamix Add Dijon, Honey &amp; lemon juice

3. Emulsify by slowly streaming in oil while vitamix is on.

4. once fully emulsified add in fresh thyme and blitz quickly on a short pulse ( do not blend to hard at this point the thyme will turn the dressing green)

5. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56995" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Jambalya Garnish

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large bowl toss the corn oil, salt, and pepper together till evenly distributed.

2. On a parchment lined baking sheet evenly spread the corn into a single layer.

3. Place in a 400 F oven for 3-5 minutes rotate and cook for another 2-3 minutes (or as needed)

4. once corn has a slightly light brown char around the edges.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56550" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large stock pot heat a small amount of oil and sautee the celery, peppers and onion.

2. Add the veggie &quot;meat&quot; and seasonings, cook for 5mins

3. Add the remaining ingredients and simmer on a low flame for 3-4 hours.

4. Taste for sesonings and adjust as needed.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61015" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 

Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, herbs, garlic, salt &amp; pepper in a 20 L container, blend with a  immersion blender. 

2. Puree until smooth. Then fold in mayo &amp; yogurt. 


**Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
 

1. Preheat oven to 400*F.

2.  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, butternut squash and carrots. season with salt &amp; pepper.  Distribute among parchment lined baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3.  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4.  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5.  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50679" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove rosemary needles from the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. Using a sharp knife, pile the rosemary in a bundle and rough chop. Continue this until rosemary is a course or fine as needed for recipe.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50588" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove just the tips/ends of the cucumber

2. Using a sharp knife,slice/chope cuke into desired shape and size appropriate for recipe use.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56779" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Drain tomatoes from their reserved liquid.

2. Chop into desired shape and size required for recipe use.

3. Store in appropriate size insert/cambro

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56621" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Dry the beef with a few paper towels for better browning. Sear the beef on all sides in a rondeau. Set aside.

2. In the Rondeau once the beef is removed, add the diced carrots and onions; sautée in fat until browned, about 3 minutes. 
 
3. Add the beef back to the pot. Season with coarse salt and  pepper. stir. Sprinkle the flour over everything and stir to coat everything evenly. Place in the center of the oven for 5 minutes @ 400F

4. Remove pot from oven; Stir beef and place back in the oven for 4 more minutes. Remove the rondeau from the oven and reduce the heat to 325°F.
  
5. To the rondeau, add the wine and stock. The liquid should barely cover the meat and vegetables. Add the tomato paste, garlic and thyme. Bring to a light simmer on the stove top, then cover and simmer in the oven for 3 to 4 hours, or until the meat fork tender and is easily pierced.
   
6. In the last hour of cooking, bring 1 1/2 tablespoons butter and 2 teaspoons oil to a medium heat in a sauté pan.  Add the pearl onions and toss around in the fat until they&apos;ve browned, 8-10 minutes. Then stir in 250ml of beef stock, a small pinch of salt and pepper and the herbs bundle. Reduce the heat to low and simmer the onions for about 20 minutes, until the liquid has evaporated, and the onions are tender.
 
 7. Remove the onions and set aside. Discard the herb bundle and wipe out the skillet. Add the remaining butter and oil and bring to a medium heat.
 
8. Add the mushrooms and cook for about 5 minutes, shaking the pan to coat with the butter.
   
9.Place a colander over a large pot. Drain the beef stew through the colander and into the pot. Place the pot with the sauce over a medium heat and simmer for about 5 minutes, skimming any fat on top. Pour the beef and vegetables back into therondeau. Add the pearl onions and mushrooms to the pot. Pour the sauce over the beef mix and simmer an additional 3 to 5 minutes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51293" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast baguette lightly

2. Spread pate on inside of toasted baguette

3. Top with tofu, shredded lettuce, pickled veg drizzle of mayon on top in a zig zag pattern and fresh cilantro

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



Weigh each block of tofu before cutting. they vary in weight so this is a helpful step to maintain consist protions

-then cut each piece into 50g 

-two pieces of tofu per sandwich

Toast a baguette and add all of the ingredients listed in the proportions indicated</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57191" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. discard unsavoury outer leaves

2.Remove core and discard

3. Cut and trim lettuce as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56114" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam in the steamer for for 3-5 minutes. Cautious not to over cook them as they will burst. Better to undercook slightly as they will be cooked again when they get fried! Reserve for service.

2. Once ready for service; add a small amount of oil to a saute pan / flat top, heat pan over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add steamed perogies to pan and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through. HOT HOLD / SERVE

3. PLATING; Arange the perogies  around the plate in a circle, top with caramelized onions; Each plate gets 240g of perogy (8pieces) slice the smokie into bite size slices (bias cut) arange around the perogies alternating around the plate.
4. Garnish with green onion. Sauerkraut and sour cream are served on the side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57233" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe: Various

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. in a perferated hotel pan inside a deeper non perforated hotel pan, place the already processed and cut to size for use broccoli florets.

2. place in the steamer and allow to steam for 6-8 minutes. Broccoli should be a vibrant green and still retain a crunch in the centre as it will be cooked further when added to other dishes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57284" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cut ends off carrots and peel thinly. Discard

2. Slice, Dice and shred carrots as needed for recipe use.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57301" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cut the potatoes in half

2.  In a large pot, cover potatoes with water and season generously with salt. Bring water to a boil and cook until potatoes are tender and easily pierced with a knife; (aprox15 to 20 minutes.) Drain and let cool fully before transferring to a large bowl. (This can be done in the steamer as well)

3.   In a large tilt skillet over medium heat, cook diced bacon until crispy. Reserve about 2 tablespoons of fat in pan, and transfer bacon to a paper towel-lined plate to blot exess fat. 

4.  Add red onion and cook over medium heat until starting to soften, about 3 minutes. Whisk in in apple cider vinegar, water, olive oil, Dijon mustard, and sugar. Bring mixture to a simmer, then turn off heat and season with salt and pepper. 

5.  Toss  in green onions and gradually pour mixture over potatoes.
    
6. Toss to combine and serve warm. 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50539" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Start with egg yolk, capers, garlic, worstershire, tabasco and lemon, blend for 30 seconds and then start slowly adding oil.

2. Add oil faster as dressing emulsifies.

3. Thin out with water as needed.

*Note* dressing should be thich but &quot;pourable&quot; this should not be the consistancy of mayo

**Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55163" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

**NOTE: Veggie dog and regular dog are reflected in this recipe to capture a ratio, the guest gets a choice of one or the other, not both.**

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Steam hot dogs in perferated hotel pan inside a non perforated hotel pan in the Rational untill fully cooked (5-7 minutes) dogs should not split (overcooked)

3. Building your dog!

-Put steamed dog on the grill/flat top to heat up (and get some awesome grill flavour) 
-In an steamed/warm bun spread your smashed avocado
-Top avocado with shredded lettuce
-Place grilled dog on top of lettuce base
-Drizzle green goddes dressing on hot dog
-Garnish with crumbled bacon and

SERVE!


HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55162" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

*Note both veggie and beef hot dogs are reflected in this recipe to capture a a sales ratio: for service it is one or the other*

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Steam hot dogs in perferated hotel pan inside a non perforated hotel pan in the Rational untill fully cooked (5-7 minutes) dogs should not split (overcooked)

3. Building your dog!

-Put steamed dog on the grill/flat top to heat up (and get some awesome grill flavour) 
-In an steamed/warm bun place your hot dog
-top with relish/mustard
-Garnish with tomato, onions and pickle
-Sprinkle lightly with Celery salt
-pepperoncini on top

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56900" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: SIDES

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Slice tomatoes in half, dice cucumber, thinly slice radish on a mandoline

2. In a large bowl combine all ingredients thouroughly for even distribution. Garnish with sunflower seeds

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45011" image="">1)  Put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher.  You will regret life if you do not do this step.  Trust me.

2)  In large kettle, bring water to a boil.  

3)  Add egg noodles and turn heat down by half.  Simmer egg noodles for 3-5 minutes or until al dente.  

4)  Drain water.  When water is completely drained, add cold water back into pot along with 3 grey lugs of ice.  Until pasta is completely covered.  mix gently.  

5)  Drain water and repeat step 4.  It&apos;s very important to stir the pasta gently to ensure that it is cooled throughout, especially when making large batches.

6)  Strain water again and add cooked pasta to appropriate vesself for storage.  Add a small amount of oil and stir into noodles to avoid having them stick.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60791" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Tuscan chicken Penne

Allergens:Dairy, Wheat(gluten)

Method:

1. In a large rondeau add olive oil and cook the chicken on medium high heat for 3-5 minutes until brown and no longer pink in center.

2. Remove chicken and set aside

3. To the Rondeau add the heavy cream, chicken stock, garlic, basil, oregano, and parmesan cheese. Whisk over medium high heat until it starts to thicken.

4. Add the spinach and sundried tomatoes and let it simmer until the spinach starts to wilt.

5. Add the chicken back to the pan. Toss with Penne for service

6. Taste and adjust seasoning if necassary.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60795" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Dice the onions. Sautee in in oil until translucent add garlic and cook out till fragrent.

2. Add tomato product, ground fennel, chili, oregano and basil.

3. Cook out the sauce. approx 1 hour.

4. Reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44916" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED
STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredient
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  With pork belly skin side down, rub belly with Porchetta Rub generously.  

2)  Roll belly into a tight log.  You may need a buddy to help you hold the belly in place.  Tie butchers knots on each end of porchetta than one good tie in the middle to secure.  Continue making butchers knots 1&quot; apart until fully tied.

3)  Combine kosher salt and baking powder.  Rub over skin of porchetta.

4)  Store in fridge, uncovered for at least 24 hours, or up to 3 days.

5)  Preheat oven to 300*F.  Place porchetta seam side down on cooling rack inside of roasting rack.  Roast until internal temperature of 60*C (140*F) is reached.

6)  Increase oven temperature to 500*F and roast for 20-30 minutes until skin is blistered and very crispy.

7)  Rest for 15 minutes and serve.  


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26323" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In saute pan over medium heat, toast peppercorns and fennel until fragrant.  Allow to cool and grind in spice grinder.  Add chili flakes and reserve.  

2)  Combine parsley, cilantro, garlic cloves, canola oil, lemon juice and cumin.  Blitz into a paste with robot coupe.  Reserve.

3)  Combine herb paste with fennel, peppercorns and chili flakes and S&amp;P.  

4)  Reserve for porchetta.

* An 8 oz. recipe will make enough for 2 (two) porchetta.
.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot bring the water to a boil. Add the rice, lentils, bayleaf and 1/2 the salt. Bring back to a boil, turn heat down to medium and lid, leaving lid slightly ajar.
Simmer for 30-35 minutes or until the rice and lentils are tender. Drain, reserving at least 1 1/4 C (281g) of cooking liquid (it will be used later to make the sauce). Place the rice and lentils back in their cooking pot, lid and set aside off heat.

2. *A note about the veggies. Be sure they&apos;re diced small, otherwise they&apos;ll be crunchy-ish at the end of cooking. We&apos;re looking for them to be soft.

3. In a large Rondeau add the oil and heat until shimmering.  Add the bell pepper, onion and celery. Turn the heat to low. Stir. Cook, stirring occassionally for about 12-15 minutes. The veggies are done when the they&apos;re tender/soft and brown bits (fond – the brown bits that stick to the bottom of the pan) are just starting to appear in the pan. 

4. To the pan of veggies, add the tomato paste, garlic, Cajun or Creole seasoning and remaining 1/2  salt. Stir to coa the veggies. Pour in 3/4 C (180g) of the reserved cooking liquid from the lentils and rice. Stir.

5. To the pan, add the drained kidney beans. Stir. Heat should be on medium-low to low. Lid the pan and gently cook the beans through for about 8-10 minutes. Check on the beans a few times while cooking and If needed, add just a bit more cooking liquid from the reserved liquid. Your beans should be saucy, and moist, not dry.

6. Turn the heat to low and transfer the drained rice and lentils to the bean mixture. Add Worcestershire sauce. Add the lemon juice and to taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary;  then gently fold all the ingredients together.
If needed, to loosen the mixture or if it starts to get too dry, add a splash of cooking liquid - you&apos;ll probably not use it all - thats okay. Taste for salt. Lid. Leave on low heat for 3-5 minutes just to warm though, checking to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking - the pan should be almost dry, with a moist (but not sticky) rice mixture.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9519" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather all ingredients.

2.Blend in food processor.

3.Put in container label place in fridge.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:na

Utensils needed:food processor cutting board scale container

ALLERGENS
-NONE

Icon:

n/a- just a sauce

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55498" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61008" image="">Method:

- toss portion of wings with hot sauce
- garnish with green onion
- serve with portion of green goddess</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61916" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place portion of hot chicken stew at bottom of the bowl

2. Tope with warm baked herb puff pastry

3. Garnish with fresh chopped parsley

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Chop jalapenos in robot coupe until finely chopped.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well using hands with gloves on.  

3. Adjust seasoning To taste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26318" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 350*F

2)  Brush circles with garlic butter, and season with chopped rosemary, thyme, salt and pepper.

3)  Par bake puff pastry in oven until about 80% cooked.  Reserve for service.

4)  Just before serving, finish puff pastry in oven.  Brush with garlic butter and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32656" image="">1)  Bring water up to a boil.  Add concentrate.  Stir throughly to combine.  Use immidiately or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61907" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Process Cauliflower into small pieces (to resemble the size and texture of ground meat)

2.Heat the oil in a large pan on medium-high heat.
Add in the garlic, diced pepper and diced onion and cook until just lightly golden brown, approx. 2-3 minutes.

3. Add in the cauliflower and cook, stirring frequently, for 2 minutes.

4. Add all the remaining ingredients, up to the parsley, and stir together. Make sure to really break the tomato paste down into the sauce and cook out.

5. Turn the heat up to high and bring to a boil. Then, reduce the heat to medium and simmer, stirring occasionally, until the liquid evaporates and the mixture is thickened (but still moist and saucy!) This takes about 10 minutes.

6. Hot hold / Reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61909" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast Kaiser bun

2. Top toasted kaiser with150g of sloppy cauliflower mix

3. Garnish with fresh red onion rings, close and skewer bun.

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61769" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Pot Pies

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

1. Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F.
  
 2. Place the chicken on a baking sheet and rub them with olive oil, salt and pepper. Roast for 20 to 25 minutes, or until cooked through. Reserve.
  
3. In a small saucepan, heat the chicken stock. In a large rondeau melt the butter and add the flour and cook over low heat, stirring constantly, for 2 minutes. Add the hot chicken stock to the sauce. Simmer over low heat for 1 more minute, stirring, until thick. cook out and remove from heat.

4. Add salt,pepper, and heavy cream. Add the chicken, carrots, peas, corn, mushrooms, onions and parsley. Mix well. cook untill veg is slightly tender. Put into hotel pans and serve immediately or store in appropriate cambro cool with ice wand/ice bath. 
   
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57361" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. At tthe bottom of the bowl place the hot chicken stew portion

2. Top with warm herb puff pastry round, garnish with fresh chopped parsley

3. serve glazed beans and potatoes on side

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57360" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot portion of chicken stew at bottom of bowl

2. Top with warm herb puff pastry


3. Mashed potatoes and glazed beans served on side

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61935" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of hot stew at bottom of bowl

2. Top with warm puff pastry

3. Garnish with fresh chopped parsley. Serve

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61936" image=""> ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of hot stew at bottom of bowl

2. Top with warm puff pastry

3. Garnish with fresh chopped parsley. 

4. Serve glazed beans on side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61505" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of dressed salad at botom of bowl

2. Garnish with chifinade of fresh basil

3. Serve with kindness

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61947" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:Gluten, dairy
Method:

1. Place a large saute pan over a low to medium-low heat. Add the 1 /2 of the oil followed by onion &amp; garlic and reduce heat to low. Season with salt and pepper and cook, stirring occasionally, for 15 to 20 minutes, until the onions are golden brown.

2. Remove the onions from the pan and return the pan to the heat.  Add the spinach and cook until wilted.

3. Remove from the spinach from the pan and leave to cool.

4. Increase the heat to medium/high and return the pan to the heat. Add the remaining oil and place the cleaned mushrooms, top side down. Cook until lightly golden (approx 5 minutes) before turning over and cooking for a further 5 minutes or until golden. Remove from the heat, and drain on paper towel top side up as they will release a lot of liquid as they cool. 

5. Transfer the onions, spinach and mushrooms to the refrigerator and cool completely. 

6. Preheat the oven to 390F. On a parchment lined pan place the puff pastry sheet on top. Spread half the caramelized onions over the middle third of the pastry, making sure to leave an extra 2cm border at the edge of the pastry. Top with half of the baby spinach. Spread the dijon mustard over the mushrooms and season well with salt and pepper. Place the mushrooms on top of the spinach. Top the mushrooms with thyme and the remaining baby spinach and onions.

7. Very carefully roll the pastry over the top of the mushroom mixture until you have a log. Press down to seal the edges. Roll over the log so that the seam is facing the bottom.

8. Whisk eggs together to make an egg wash . Very lightly coat the outside of the pastry log with the egg wash. Place the pastry in the freezer for 10 minutes before repeating with another layer of egg wash and freezing the pastry for a further 10 minutes.

9. Bake in the oven for 30 to 35 minutes, or until golden and flakey. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Gluten, Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1. With a serrated or carving knife cut a clean portion sized slice of wellington (Approx 1&quot; wide)

2. Place on centre of plate and garnish with fresh chopped parsley

3. 60ml of vegan (putine) gravy goes on side

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61950" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Gluten, Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1. With a serrated or carving knife cut a clean portion sized slice of wellington (Approx 1&quot; wide)

2. Place on centre of plate and garnish with fresh chopped parsley

3. Place 150g of rosemary potatoes next to mushroom welly!

4. 60ml of vegan (poutine) gravy goes on side

5. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61952" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Gluten, Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1. With a serrated or carving knife cut a clean portion sized slice of wellington (Approx 1&quot; wide)

2. Place on centre of plate and garnish with fresh chopped parsley

3. Place 150g of rosemary potatoes and 120g of parsnip/carrots next to mushroom welly!

4. 60ml of vegan (poutine) gravy goes on the side

5. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44510" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50006" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Make beef stock as per recipe. Reserve for making sauce.

2. Dice pickles 1/8&quot;.

3. Make Sauteed mushroom, onions, pickles. Add wine, and reduce till most of the liquid is gone and pan is nearly dry. Remove from tilt skillet, and reserve for making sauce.

4. In large stock pot bring beef stock to a simmer, and reserve hot.

5. In tilt skillet on low, melt the butter till it&apos;s no longer frothing, whisk in flour to make a roux, cook out for 2 minutes. Gradually add warm stock to roux while stiring with whisk, until all stock is incorperated.

6) Add sauteed veg to thicken stock and season to taste. If using right away hold warm, or 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57391" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62351" image="">processed parsnip has a 84.4% yield</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61504" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1. Slice tomatoes in half, slice bocconccini in half

2. Toss with olive oil and balsamic glaze, season with salt and pepper

3. Reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61968" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Dairy, Sulphites
Method:

1.Coat the bottom of a large rondeau with oil and put on medium heat until hot.

2. Season the chicken on both sides with salt and pepper and then brown, skin side down for about 15 minutes, until the skin is nice and crisp. Flip the chicken and cook for another 15 minutes, or until done. (The meat should read 160F) remove from rondeau and reserve.

3. Add the shallots and garlic to the rondeau and saute, stirring constantly, for a couple of minutes. Then add the white wine and let it bubble down while you scrape up the browned bits from the bottom of the pan.

4. Add the chicken stock, heavy cream, and sun dried tomatoes, thyme and cook the sauce for a few minutes until it starts to thicken, stirring frequently. Scrape up everything from the bottom and sides of the pan into the sauce. 

NOTE: This isn&apos;t a super thick sauce, but it will thicken somewhat as it reduces.

5. Add the cheese and stir until fully incorporated. Add the chopped spinach and fresh tomatoes to the pan, and cook until the spinach has wilted. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed.

6.  Add the chicken back into the rondeau and heat through before serving.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61969" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: This recipe is calculated for 1 chicken thigh per portion and some sauce

1. place chicken thigh on plate, laddle over the chicken apox 60ml of sauce being midful of ensuring a few tomatoes and spinach is incorparated into that portion of sauce.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 1 chicken thigh (approx 130g) + 60ml of sauce</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61976" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Gluten
Method:

1.Combine the barley and stock:  in a hotel pan. Add salt and pepper.

2.  Cook In steamer.  Keep an eye on the  barley as it will give off a lot of foam at first and can  boil over.

3. For pearl barley, start checking at 25 minutes. The barley is done when it has tripled in volume and is soft yet chewy. Add more water if the pan becomes dry before the barley has finished cooking; check every 5 minutes until desired chewiness is reached.

4. Drain the barley (if necessary): When the barley is done, it will have absorbed most of the water. If there is a little water still left in the pan, just leave the barley to sit for 10 minutes, covered, until it has all been absorbed. If there is a lot of water left, drain the barley in a strainer over the sink.

5. Fluff the barley!  With a fork, fluff the barley to separate the grains. this is an imprtant step with all our steamed grains! 

2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61971" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: This recipe is calculated for 1 chicken thigh per portion and some sauce

1. place chicken thigh on plate, laddle over the chicken apox 60ml of sauce being mindful of ensuring a few tomatoes and spinach is incorparated into that portion of sauce.

2. Place portioned amount of sides next to chicken. garnish chicken with parsley and bocconcinni salad with fresh chiffinade of basil.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61979" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: This recipe is calculated for 1 chicken thigh per portion and some sauce

1. place chicken thigh on plate, laddle over the chicken apox 60ml of sauce being midful of ensuring a few tomatoes and spinach is incorparated into that portion of sauce.

2. Place portioned omount of sides next to chicken. garnish chicken with parsley and bocconcinni salad with fres chiffinade of basil.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56115" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam in the steamer for for 3-5 minutes. Cautious not to over cook them as they will burst. Better to undercook slightly as they will be cooked again when they get fried! Reserve for service.

2. Once ready for service; add a small amount of oil to a saute pan / flat top, heat pan over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add steamed perogies to pan and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through. HOT HOLD / SERVE

3. PLATING; Arange the perogies  around the plate in a circle, top with caramelized onions; Each plate gets 240g of perogy (8pieces) 

4. Garnish with green onion. Sauerkraut and sour cream are served on the side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62037" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in Rational FOR 1HR MIN.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast baguette lightly

2. Spread pate on toasted baguette

3. Top with pork belly, lettuce, pickled veg and garnish with mayo drizzle in a zig zag pattern and fresh cilantro

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot ratatouillie in base of serving dish, 

2. Add toasted persiallde to the top of the ratatouille and garnish with fresh crumbled goat cheese and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62263" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62264" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62272" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61941" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Steam hot dogs in perferated hotel pan inside a non perforated hotel pan in the Rational untill fully cooked (5-6 minutes) dogs should not split (overcooked)

3. Building your dog!

-Put steamed dog on the grill/flat top to heat up (and get some awesome grill flavour) 
-In an steamed/warm bun place your hot dog
-Top with portinioned amout of chili
-garnish with shredded cheddar
-Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56993" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of Jambalaya in bottom of serving bowl

2. Garnish with roasted corn and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57156" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62399" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toss the salad base with the dressing, place at bottom of bowl

2. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro and chopped roasted cashews

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62398" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast baguette lightly

2. Spread pate on toasted baguette

3. Top with pork belly, lettuce, pickled veg and garnish with mayo drizzle in a zig zag pattern and fresh cilantro sprig

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62400" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast baguette lightly

2. Spread pate on inside of toasted baguette

3. Top with tofu, shredded lettuce, pickled veg a drizzle of mayo in a zig zag pattern and fresh cilantro

4. Salad served on side

5. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut cauliflower into 1&quot; flourettes.

2. Toss in batter until completly coated.

3. Toss in 3/4 of panko. Take remaining 1/4 of the panko and bltz in robocoup until fine ( about 5 min).

4. Toss the wings in the fine blitzed panko and spread out on a sheet pan lined with parchment.

5. Bake in 350f oven for 20 min, remove from heat, stir, bake for an additional 15 min or until just golden.

6. Hold hot for service.

**Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62406" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35251" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and weigh ingredients
2.blend everything together except oil
3.once smooth slowly add oil to form sauce
4. label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47149" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26947" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Side

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat the oven to 400 degrees F.

2. Cut the potatoes into quarters and place in a bowl with the olive oil, salt, pepper, garlic and rosemary; toss until the potatoes are evenly coated.

3. Dump the potatoes on a baking sheet and spread out into 1 layer(no crowding, leave space between); roast in the oven for at least 1 hour, or until browned and crisp. Flip twice with a spatula during cooking to ensure even browning.
 4. Remove the potatoes from the oven, season to taste with salt and pepper as needed and serve.

 *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes

2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well

3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All ingredients
2. Chopped capers to desire size
3.  Store in container

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting Board, knife, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54176" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Reheat cooked pasta in blancher until hot.

2. Place hot pasta on plate, top with 1 piece of chicken and ladle of sauce.

3. Garnish with parm &amp; fresh chopped parsley


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47654" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-56700" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine flour, spices and wisk together.

2. Add soy milk and stock, wisk together to create batter.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50007" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1.in a mixing bowl add warm noodles, beef portion and hot stroganoff sauce, mix to incoporate thuroughly.

2. Place mixed noodles in bottom of serving bowl

3. Garnish with teaspoon of sour cream, parsley, parm.

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:measuring cups, measuring spoon, blender
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-39336" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-66018" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot ratatouillie in base of serving dish, place hot grilled chicken on top.

2. Add toasted persiallde to the top of the ratatouille and garnish with fresh crumbled goat cheese and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-67284" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

METHOD:


1. Gather all ingredients. Wash potatoes

2. Toss in oil, salt and pepper

4. Bake in Oven at 425F for 45-60 minutes (should be easily pierced with a fork and tender)

5. Transfer to service ware and hot hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53002" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU** Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. cut off tip and tail of fennel
2. rinse in lemon water
3. cube to 3cm x 3cm x 3cm
4. store in acidulated water labeleed and rotated 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67542" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

 This recipe is for 3 tacos! ( each taco gets 2 tortillas on on top of the other, filling only goes in the top tortilla, make sense?)

1. Place Marinade ingredients in a food processor and buzz until smooth.

 (Try not to touch the Marinade with bare hands to avoid getting chili on your hands)

2. Reserve for chicken.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67543" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Place chicken into lexan pour marinade over, ensure chicken is fully covered in marinade for maximum flavour!

2. Allow to sit in marinade for at least 4 hours minimum and no longer than 24 hours maximum.

3. Ready to cook? Remove chicken from marinade. Reserve marinade.

4. Preheat oven to 350F place chicken on a parchment lined pan (dont over crowd the pan) roast for 25 minutes

5. Turn chicken over and baste with reserved marinade. Roast for another 25 minutes untill chicken is fully cooked and reaches 165F


*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67671" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingedients

2. Place the cashews, water, salt, nutritional yeast and garlic in a high-speed blender and blend until silky smooth, for 1-2 minutes

3. Reserve for service. Will last in Cooler for 3 days.


*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56740" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat up tilt skillet over medium/ high heat.

2) Season chicken with salt &amp; pepper, place skin side down in skillet and sear until skin is golden brown. Remove chicken and reserve.

3) In the tilt skillet add olive oil, onion, celery, bell peppers and garlic and sweat until fragrant (3-5 minutes). Remove and reserve.

3) Add tomatoes, capers and dry oregano to the pan. Place seared chicken into sauce and bring to a simmer.

4) Simmer for approximately 30 minutes or until chicken is fully cooked.(Internal temperature of 165F)

5) Remove chicken from the sauce and return vegetables into sauce. Check thickness of sauce and reduce if needed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny


Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Wash and trim off stem
3. cut to correct size for what you need

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52943" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
1.BBC|Prawn Taco|POP

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.Cut neat and tidy leaves and tips into sprigs measuring between 5cm &amp; 7 cm
2.Store on a damp paper towel
3. Label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 1-2 pieces as a garnish

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57499" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.
OR cut by hand if small amount  

2)  Set up an insert to catch onion as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60792" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of hot pasta in bottom of serving bowl

2. Garnish with shredded parm and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68203" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large rondeau or tild skillet, sauté the vegan sausage over medium-high heat for about 5 minutes, until browned.

2. Add the garlic and cook, stirring constantly, for 30 seconds until fragrant.

3. Pour in the vegetable broth, coconut milk, lemon juice, dried basil &amp; oregano, chopped sun-dried tomatoes and gnocchi. Give everything a good stir.

4. Bring to a boil, then lower heat to medium and cook, uncovered for 5 minutes, stirring occasionally.

5. Add salt + pepper to taste, and stir in the spinach. Cook for another 2 minutes, until the spinach has wilted.

6. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68204" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of gnocchi in bottom of bowl

2. Garnish with frsh basil

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67193" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place potatoes and green beans on serving plate

2. Place crispy chicken parm on top

3. Garnish with fresh basil

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68210" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Fry chicken until golden brown, remove and drain excess oil on paper towel

2. Lay chicken on parchment lined sheet tray. Top each chicken with tomato sauce, mozza &amp; parm

3. Put garnished chicken in oven until cheese is melted and bubbly, ensure chicken has reached an internal temp of 165F

4. Remove and hot hold for service.

NOTE: as this is a crispy fried item, do not do this process to far in advance or chicken will end up a soggy mess and no one wants that!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56300" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cut eggplant in to thick slices aprox 100g.

2. Lightly dust eggplant slices with salt, let drain for 1-2 hours. Rinse well to remove all salt and pat dry with paper towel.

3. Once dry, dredge in flour, tap off exess flour and dip in egg wash, once fully coated put in panko and fully coat.

4. Flash eggplant in deepfryer to par cook. Cool on sheets and put in cooler until needed. You can freeze them if made a few days a head.

5. To finish for service top with tomato sauce and cheese and bake until fully cooked and cheese is browned on top.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57354" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place potatoes &amp; green beans on serving plate

2. Place cooked eggplant parm on top of potatoes and beans

3. Garnish with fresh basil

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32659" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam yukon gold nugget potato&apos;s for 8 minutes. If steaming ahead of time cool properly and store for later.

2. Combine oregano with oil, lemon juice, garlic and salt and pepper.  Pour marinade over potatoes.

3. Pour potatoes onto parchment lined baking trays and roast @ 450*F for 15 minutes or until potatoes are crispy and brown.  Serve immidiately or hold for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68213" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67344" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. place rice and beans on serving plate next to each other

2. Place jerk chiken on top

3. Garnish with fresh cilantro and serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47164" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65589" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together and put in steamer


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65593" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Dice everything the same size (1/8&quot;)

3. Mix everything together. taste. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68218" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67288" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Make Veg stock as per recipe. Reserve for making sauce.

2. Dice pickles 1/8&quot;.

3. Make Sauteed mushroom, onions, pickles. Reduce till most of the liquid is gone and pan is nearly dry. Remove from tilt skillet, and reserve for making sauce.

4. In large stock pot bring veg stock to a simmer, and reserve hot.

5. In tilt skillet on low, melt the butter till it&apos;s no longer frothing, whisk in flour to make a roux, cook out for 2 minutes. Gradually add warm stock to roux while stiring with whisk, until all stock is incorperated.

6) Add sauteed veg to thicken stock and season to taste. If using right away hold warm, or 



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67287" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1.in a mixing bowl add warm noodles, mushroom portion and hot stroganoff sauce, mix to incoporate thuroughly.

2. Place mixed noodles in bottom of serving bowl

3. Garnish with teaspoon of sour cream, parsley, parm.

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68220" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: This salad is served WARM

1. Place portion of warm potato salad in small service bowl

2. Garnish with fresh chopped green onions and sour cream

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55300" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Steam hot dogs in perferated hotel pan inside a non perforated hotel pan in the Rational untill fully cooked (5-6 minutes) dogs should not split (overcooked)

3. Building your dog!

-Put steamed dog on the grill/flat top to heat up (and get some awesome grill flavour) 
-In an steamed/warm bun place your hot dog
-Top dog with pickle veg, spicy mayo nori shreds and furikake

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62431" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of mashed potatoes &amp; green beans on plate

2.Place portion of bourguignon next to mashed

3. Garnish with fresh chopped parsley

4, Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67285" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

**NOTE: This Recipe is to Capture a Ratio. Guest can choose any and all items as they wish.

1. Place Backed potato on small serving plate, guest can add as many garnishes of choiceto inside of potato

2. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredents
2.place in food processor, process till smooth
3.place in cambro label and date
4. refridgerate
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a bowl mix portion of warm ravioli in the correct volume of pesto, ensuare even coating

2. Place in service bowl and garnish with chopped sundried tomatoes, parmesan cheese and gresh minced parsley.

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68426" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toss portion of kale with measured volume of dressing

2. Place in service bowl and garnish with croutons and parm.

3. Serve with kindness!

NOTE: Do not toss the croutons in the bowl with the dressing, this prevents them from going soggy and keeps the bowl gluten free!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56938" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62255" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56937" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of glazed beans on service plate

2. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64887" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
