<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-33709" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Heat wok over high heat. Pour in oil, then stir in carrots and peas; cook about 30 seconds. Stir in cooked rice. Shake in soy sauce, and toss rice to coat. Drizzle with sesame oil, and toss again.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26883" image="">

-Cook noodles for 5 mins in the steamer or
-Cook noodles for 3 mins in boiling water at the station</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33438" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Combine and blend thoroughly wtih immersion blender

3. You may not need the full amount of water, so test it out with less (half) to start with and add more incrementally until the desired texture is achieved. 

4. Taste for seasoning, adjust if necassary.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41312" image="">ALLERGENS:

Prep:

- Cut all vegetables into large pieces. Do not spend more than 10 minutes cutting these vegetables, as all of them will be discarded, and no one will see your lovely cuts if you put effort into them.

- Heat a pot in the background with a small amount of oil. You can even start this process with water if you want. Start cooking out anything in the onion family first - this approach can be used with all stock making.

- Once you&apos;ve cooked out your onions (can no longer smell gas coming off of them, and you start to smell sugars coming from them), then add all remaining ingredients EXCEPT CILANTRO - as well as water - and bring to a boil. 

- When the pot is at a boil - let boil for about 20 minutes. Then, turn it down to a simmer. ADD CILANTRO (stocks and all), simmer for 40 minutes with salt, and take off heat. Once off heat, let rest for 45 minutes to an hour, and strain using the fine chinois.

- Label / date / store appropriately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42160" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix. 

Use a blender if you like, it is easier. A whisk will work too. 

***Please make sure to mix tahini before you use it as it settles and separates. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43212" image="">

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1. Gather spice and herb stems and put into a cheesecloth tied loosely with twine
 
2. Rough chop the daikon and reserve. 

3. Rough chop: shallots and garlic, Set aside.

4. In a pot/skillet/kettle/wok  add oil, and sweat out shallots and garlic until softened

5. Add coconut milk and cheesecloth spice sachet and chopped lemongrass.

6. Bring to a simmer for about 20 minutes to let those flavours infuse, and then add daikon.

7. Cook out daikon, and then remove daikon once cooked (it will be used again for the final product).

8. Add water, and prepare a corn starch slurry at the same time. 

9. Thicken just enough to give it some body, but keep it in the broth realm and not as thick as a sauce. Make sense? 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43341" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and allow the pickle juice to pickle the cabbage. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44082" image="">ALLERGENS: WHEAT, GLUTEN

Prep:

- Take the Coriander Seeds, Cumin Seeds, Ajwain Seeds, Black Pepper and Garam Masala - and toast, then grind in the Vitamix into a fine powder. The toasting, as mentioned in other recipes, is key to developing flavour and aroma.

- Amchur Powder is not a spice, but a powder made of green mango. It should not be toasted. Opinions differ on this, but - for this recipe, do not toast this ingredient.

- Normally this recipe would be made into a paste with lemon juice and a small amount of water. We use this as a more dry rub, in combination with alread-wet ingredients like potatoes that have been boiled and chickpeas that sit in &quot;aqua fava&quot; (literally: bean water).

- If this spice mix is low, talk to a Chef about it. Some of these ingredients come from a specialty provider with an indented delivery schedule - and will need to be ordered several days in advance in order to allow for proper prep time.

Any questions - Ask Chef!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43346" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Slice onions into thin rounds on a mandoline

2. place onion rings into buttermilk 

3. Remove onions from buttermilk and dredge into seasoned (salt and pepper) flour, shake off excess flour and place into fryer basket, drop into 350F hot fryer oil. stir while cooking to prevent clumping.

4. Remove crispy onions from fryer and drain on tray lined with paper towl to blot off exess oil, season with salt and pepper right away, cool and reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44311" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix.

Mix again every time you use it as it is not an emulsified dressing and it will separate. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44392" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.in non reactive pot place everything except eggs
3.bring to a simmer
4. Crack egg into simmering water and cook soft
5. pull from water and put in ice bath to cool rappedly
6. place in container place enough cold water in container to keep eggs loose so they do not break
7. Label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Pot slotted spoon containers</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44571" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

Notes:

This is a fresh garnish that should be the cornerstone of our Wok station offerings. ALL Wok offerings should be garnished with something fresh - Bean Sprouts and at least Cilantro if not Mint too - as well as a dash of citrus juice, in order to be what they were meant to be. Without this citrus accent, the offerings will not be balanced, and each bite will be a uniform flavour (the journey through the dish will be the same step, over and over, without punctuation or alteration/elevation.

This means that extra special care of the fresh herbs and bean sprouts needs constant attention. Please do your part, and let the stocking employees know if they are not doing their part - the Chef will do his part, and you will hear about it you are not doing yours.

Any questions? - Ask Chef...</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44641" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tofu and season with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44677" image="">

PREP RECIPE:

Cut Cucumbers in slices that are 1cm thick

Boil up sugar, vinegar, soya sauce and spices to dissolve the sugar. 

Once dissolved combine the pickling liquid with the cucumbers to pickle.

***if the liquid is poured over hot it speeds up the process.*** </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44686" image="">
Method:


- Using a rondeau, begin to saute your ginger, onions and garlic, with your oil. Once cooked out, add other ingredients and stir - lowering heat. Raise to a boil, and then let simmer. 

- Using a Corn Starch slurry, thicken the mixture slightly. 

Taste.

Use this sauce for both Dan Dan Pork and Dan Dan Tofu/Tempeh.

Either use immediatley, or hold hot for service, or chill rapidly for later use.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27334" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Soak bread in Royale (toast batter) for 2 minutes

2. Place on flat top till each side is golden brown

3. Cut in half diagonally

4. layer on top of each other on place on plate with a side of maple syrup. Make sure syrup is given on the side or it will disapear ont he toast and guest will wonder if the recieved it!

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44319" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Method:

Place 105g portion of Tabouleh into side bowl

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44841" image="">
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44846" image="">Allergens:
sesame, soy

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44873" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Arrange attractively in a bowl in the indicated proportions. 

2. Ensure rice is on the bottom and other ingredients are arranged in quadrants so that as much variety as possible is visible. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligenty</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44502" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut broccoli into florets. 

Toss with oil and salt and pepper

Lay out on a parchment lined sheet pan and roast until golden brown at the edges

Toss with lemon juice</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44933" image="">
Prep:

- Garlic and Ginger - use the Pre-Minced products that are available in the prepped items fridge.

- Cut 1/3rd of a packet of Red Thai Chilis. Each packet that we get from Freshpoint is 300g.

- Large Dice: Cabbage, Onions,  

- Heat the Wok. This side can be done at the station for effect or in the back, in hiding. 

Either way --&gt; THIS IS AN ITEM THAT SHOULD NEVER SIT IN OUR WARMERS, AS IT WILL LOOK HORRIBLE (WORSE THAN THE FACE THAT CHEF WILL MAKE IF THEY FIND IT IN THE WARMERS AT ANY POINT, OR BEING DONE AN HOUR BEFORE SERVICE), AND THE FLAVOURS WILL DEGRADE IMMENSELY.

- Starting with the Onions - in the hot Wok - begin to fry these ingredients. Spoiler - this is going to happen fast, and you&apos;re really just going to want to put some colour on the onions, before throwing in the Cabbage and deglazing with 2 Cups of Water. When you do this, throw in your Ginger and Garlic 

- Add remaining ingredients, and bring to a boil. Immediately turn off heat at this point, and while it&apos;s still at a boil, make a Corn Starch Slurry out of your remaining Cup of Water in this recipe - adding it slowly while stirring. At this point, you&apos;re pretty much done. 

- It would be best to do this infront of the students, as it will draw attention to the amazing job you&apos;re doing and the flavours that you&apos;re representing. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44934" image="">ALLERGENS: SOY, SESAME, SULPHITES 

Icons:

Vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45456" image="">Allergens:
sesame, soy, sluphites, gluten, wheat

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan 

Method:

4 oz ladle of sauce
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51222" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Trim ends off and peel. Discard

2. Cut and slice as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45422" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Rinse Rice 3 times

Combine rice in a 1:1 water ratio.

Slice up Ginger into slices, please do not use a puree. Add ginger to water and rice. Add salt to rice.

Steam the rice

While the rice is steaming Combine Mirin and Rice Wine Vinegar.

Stir the vinegar/mirin mixture into the rice to complete the seasoning.

***A portion of rice on the plate is 150g***
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45423" image="">PREP RECIPE

Combine all ingredients, and blitz together with an Immersion Blender or mix thoroughly with a whisk.  

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately




 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45425" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Either wok fry or deep fry the tofu to give it a crust.

Combine fried tofu and warmed sauce in the indicated ratios.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55129" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-47229" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Method:

- Steam carrot, potato and daikon
- Sautee leeks, garlic, ginger and onions in oil
- Add steamed vegetables and gravy.
- Season to taste

***Alternately the carrot, potato and diakon could be simmered in the gravy to cook through as well.***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1)  Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray.  Place egg in egg poacher cup.  Steam for 7 minutes until cooked.

Allergens:

Soy, Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65606" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-62271" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amound of roasted broccoli in small service bowl.

2. Serve with kindnes!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41318" image="">


in a large rondeau, toast curry powder. Add all ingredients except the slurry. Bring to a boil then add the slurry to thicken into a gravy.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50600" image="">Save all your parsley, leek, cilantro, green onion and celery ends for stocks!!!!!

1. Gather all your ingredients first.

2. Char the ginger on the grill.

3. Sautee the onions, leek, ginger, garlic and lemon grass.

4. Add the water and bring to a boil. Turn down right away to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. After that, turn off and throw in the leek, cilantro, parsley, green onion and celery ends for 30 minutes.

5. Strain, down size and cool down.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32747" image="">

PREP RECIPE

***This is a neutral base for any number of quiche flavourings.


Whisk together the eggs, milk, cream, and salt until frothy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47518" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Dressed arugula

Allergens: Mustard, Sulphites

Method:

1. Mince shallots, add apple cider vin, alt &amp; pepper &amp; mustard.

2. Whisk together, continue whisking while adding the oil

3. Taste for seasoning, adjust as needed

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54422" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place a 200g portion of warm prepared nasi goreng into service bowl and garnish with additional green onion, fresh tomato, cucumber slices and bean sprouts. 

2. If guest requests add a fried egg on top

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57157" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

Preheat deep fryer to 350F

1. Slice sweet potato width wise into 1/2 - 1 cm thick slices.

2. Toss evenly in flour, then liquid egg then panko and reserve on full sized sheet pans. 

3. Working in batches deep fry slices 1-2 minutes until sweet potatoes are golden brown and just cooked through.

4. Remove from fryer, shake off excess oil, place on wire rack and season immediately so the salt will stick to the sweet potatoes.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44649" image="">Preps:

Allergens:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PREP/PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Method:
1. Cut squash in half, tip to tail
2. Clean out cup of squash with a sharp spoon
3. Toss in oil salt and pepper
4. bake with skin on until fully cooked, set aside for reheating later
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
 
Portioning:


Utensils:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51245" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Stirfry veggies in wok. (mushroom, garlic, peppers, and onion)

2. Cube and lightly fry tofu.

3. Combine sauce and tofu into wok and stirfry briefly to combine. 

4. remove from heat and add green onion and cilantro.

5. Reserve for service


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65941" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

!. gather ingredients
2.Blend together everything except for honey and lemon
3. when mixture is smooth folk in lemon and honey tasting to be sure of flavor balance
4. label, date, and refridgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45692" image="">ALLERGEN: SESAME, SOY

-Heat wok over high heat. Pour in oil. Stir in cooked rice. Shake in soy sauce, and toss rice to coat. Drizzle with sesame oil, and toss again.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over high heat, add oil

2. Once oil is hot and &quot;shimmering&quot;  add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes untill onions are a deep caramel colour.

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46845" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm mushroom filling inside steamed warm bao bun. top mushroom with slaw and garnish with sesame/nori seasoning.

2. Place filled bao on plate and put warm rice and veg next to the bao (prop the bao up on the rice and veg for hieght.

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60391" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-49969" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Heat oil on flat top

2. add onions garlic and peppers

3. cook till tender, season with salt and pepper

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51301" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm rice on bottom of plate

2. Place tofu base on top of rice

3. Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50835" image="">

Combine everything except cornstarch and water in a pot and mix.

Bring to a boil over high heat, then reduce to a simmer.

Drizzle in a cornstarch slurry whilst stirring until desired consistency is reached. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9720" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Trim all excess and cut the cauliflower in small     florettes
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53995" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss mushrooms with salt and pepper and oil. 

Roast on a parchment lined sheet pan in a hot oven until the water from the mushrooms cooks away and the mushrooms are browned and flavorful</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44811" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51266" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve 1 toasted pita (grilled or baked), cut into wedges with 125 ml of hummus</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46280" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients attractively on the plate in the proportions indicated. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54343" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut in half or in quarters as needed. 

Steam in an perforated hotel pan. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54396" image="U:\PICTURES\1412850392_CHINESE MIXED VEGETABLES RECIPES.jpg">
PREP RECIPE

Chop all veggies and gather mise en place

Dilute the vegetable stock concentrate in the water

Make the cornstarch slurry

To Cook- add oil to a hot wok and add garlic and ginger. 

Strifry the garlic and ginger to toast and and develop flavour.

Add the vegetables to the wok and stirfry in oil, deglazing with the vegetable stock and soya sauce to both prevent burning and sticking and to provide steam to cook out the vegetables.

A moment before the veggies are cooked to their sufficient doneness, add the cornstarch slurry and stirfry it through to give the broth/sauce some body, so that it will cling to the veggies. 

Hold or serve.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50571" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cook rice with half of the turmeric in the recipe. RESERVE
  
2.  Add oil to wok and allow to get hot.  Add shallots saute for 1-2 minutes until beginning to soften. Add garlic cook for 1 more minute. Add curry powder and the remaining turmeric and saute and toss to combine. Add tofu and saute and toss for 1-2 minutes.  

4.  Add rice and continue stir-frying until rice is warm throughout and then add the Kecap Manis. Add cabbage, green  onion, cilantro and bean sprouts and mix until it is well incorporated.  


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54778" image="">


























***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 1/2&quot; Dice the sweet potatoes

2. Toss the sweet potatoes with the oil and salt and pepper.

3. Lay out the oiled seasoned sweet taters on sheet pans lined with parchment in even layer and roast until tender and golden brown around the edges.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67350" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather ingredients and equipment

2. Heat oil in a large skillet over medium. Add onion; cook 5 minutes, until softened. Add garlic, paprika, salt, chili powder, oregano, black pepper, and cayenne; cook 2 minutes, stirring often, until aromatic.

3.  Stir in rice; cook 2 minutes, until slightly translucent. Stir in tomatoes, beans, and veg stock. Bring mixture to a boil, reduce to medium-low, and simmer, covered, until liquid is absorbed and rice is tender, about 25 minutes.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35848" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Zest and juice your 2 lemons.

2. Finely chop dill.

3. Process Cucumbers. These should be pulsed in the RoboCoupe. PULSED - NOT LEFT ON TO BECOME A SOUP. What you want is something about the consistency of a small dice. When this is done, transfer this mixture into a bowl with Cheese Cloth. RING OUT AS MUCH WATER AS YOU CAN. THIS WATER IS DELICIOUS. I RECOMMEND DRINKING IT FOR ITS ELECTROLYTE PROPERTIES. Unfortunately, it just doesn&apos;t belong in the Yoghurt in this recipe, as it would turn into Cacic.

4. Combine lemon juice and garlic. Let sit for 10 minutes. Salt this mixture to &quot;cook out&quot; the garlic as much as possible.

5. Fold all ingredients into one another. Taste for Salinity, Acidity, and add honey if the Sweetness needs a little kick.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



NOTES: It&apos;s important to note that this is an opportunity for using old or slightly old Cucumber! For instance: look at the recipe for Taboulleh Salad Mix - Cucumber cores should be saved, and then processed and strained in Cheese Cloth for this recipe - otherwise it will be too watery.

In Turkey, there is a dish known as Cacic - a watery version of Tzatziki. The ingredients are more or less the same. What we know as Tzatziki is actually made with Labneh, which is pressed Yoghurt. Since we use regular Yoghurt in this recipe, we have to limit the amount of water content in it, otherwise it will be an undesirable AND low-quality product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36666" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.start building this bowl with the beans and rice hot in the bottom of the serving vessel

2. add remaining ingredients topping with poached egg and avocado fan

3. ask the customer if they would like chili flakes on this dish every time

4. Serve with kindness!

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9778" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry
2.process as needed
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58716" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast bread to warm and toast slightly. Brush with olive oil.

2. Warm mushrooms slightly, adjust seasoning and pile on top of grilled bread.

3. Garnish with parsley.

4. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32800" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Drain chickpeas, lightly mash into a course texture using a food processor.  Do not blend into a smooth paste.

2. Add green onion, red pepper, cilantro, vegan mayo, garlic, ginger, turmeric, lemon juice and salt and pepper into chick peas.  Mix well to combine.

3. Adjust seasonong.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano until desired texture achived (course or fine)

3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
 Chef Johnny


Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.tim cabbage
3. run threw food processor &quot;S&quot; blade
4. Label,date and refridgerate

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64724" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP,  an in house made ingredient recipe
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Dip small batches (2-3orders at a time) of cauliflour in batter, letting excess drip off
2. Fry in 350 degree oil until floaring/ golden brown, being sure not to let batter clump together when they get placed in the oil
3. skim the oil with each batch to remove scraps of batter 
4. Rest cooked florets on a resting rack to let the steam out. While they&apos;re hot season with s&amp;p
5. keep warm in a warmer open so that the batter doesnt get soggy/soft

-cool excess product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning: 


Utensils needed: resting rack, tongs, 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55942" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Deep fry falafel until it is crispy and hot all the way through

2. Prepare all side dishes and accompaniments

3. The rice, pita (cut into triangles) and falafel are served warm/hot

4. The hummus, salad, and pickled cabbage are served cold

PLATING;

1. place rice on side of plate, cut pita into 4 and stack next to rice

2 Add salad to other side of plate.
add hummus and pickled cabbage next to the salad, try to keep the cold things together and the hot things together on oposite sides of same plate.

3. place the 5 pieces of crispy/hot falafel on top of the rice. Serve

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 





















</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50498" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Warm up crepe on the flattop.

2. Spread apple compote.

3. Fold in triangles.Put it on a plate

4. Pipe whipped coconut over crepes.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62547" image="">Slice the grape tomatoes in half length wise</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56766" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Slice tomatoes in half

2. Toss in bowl with olive oil and salt and pepper till evenly coated

3. On parchment lined tray place tomatoes cut side up.

4. Put in oven at 400F for 6-10 minutes (may need longer) 

5: check for doneness; most liquid should have evaporated and tomatoes should be slightly dried around edges but not &quot;leathery&quot; or burnt.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36566" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. comine all ingredients into large cambro
2. Blend with the BIG BAD WAND until smooth 
3. Adjust seasoning to taste
4. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-66113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2. peel sweet potato
3. Label, date and refridgerate
4. if doing for frying later do not put in water 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9768" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather peppers
2.wash and cut 1/4 inch size
3.put into correct container and reserve with label in fridge till required
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57581" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of rice on base of plate, top with katsu veg and top veg with crispy sweet potato

2. Sauce around the plate.

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9738" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredient
2.trim if not already done and wash
3.cut to 1/4&quot;
4. label, date and refridgerate
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat a heavy pan over medium-high heat and add the canola and sesame oils.

2.  Add the beans and cook, stirring occasionally until they start to turn golden.

3.  Add the ginger, garlic, green onions, soy sauce, sugar and Sriracha and cook a few minutes more, stirring often, until the garlic is golden, the beans are deeper golden and the sauce has reduced and become sticky. The sauce should coat and cling to the beans well

4. Sprinkle with toasted sesame seeds.

Hot Hold/Serve imeediately

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Ratatouille

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Puree garlic and olive oil in robot cupe untill smooth. Set aside.

2. Fine mince parsley. Set aside.
 
3. Scale out panko and in a lrge bowl combine all ingredents untill panko thuroughly is coated in garlic oil and parsley mixed throught. 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56430" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Blueberry Pancakes

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Boil water, sugar, and lemon zest in a 1-quart heavy saucepan, uncovered, 5 minutes.

2. Discard zest. Stir in blueberries and simmer, stirring occasionally, until blueberries begin to burst (aprox 3 to 5 minutes)  Remove from heat and stir in lemon juice. Serve warm or at room temperature. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Saute the onions and pureed lemon grass until translucent, add ginger and garlic and cook out for another 5 minutes. Add sugar and cook for another 5 minutes.

3. Add Green Curry Paste and cook out for another 5 minutes to develop flavour.

4. Add coconut milk, bring to a simmer, add lime leaves and season.

5. Thicken with slury, thicken so that sauce coats the back of a spoon and sticks.

6. Add lime juice just before you take it off the heat.

7. Throw in the thai basil and cilantro and blend in the sauce to give it it&apos;s green color.******

****** If you are making the sauce for the next day, DO NOT add the cilantro/thai basil as it will go brown and discolor.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57192" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Lightly trim the tougher base( bottom of stem) from mushrooms (not much needs to be discarded as mushrooms have about a 93% yield)

.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57233" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe: Various

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. in a perferated hotel pan inside a deeper non perforated hotel pan, place the already processed and cut to size for use broccoli florets.

2. place in the steamer and allow to steam for 6-8 minutes. Broccoli should be a vibrant green and still retain a crunch in the centre as it will be cooked further when added to other dishes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51527" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place all your rice noodles in a deep mixing bowl, (trying to snap as few of them as possible as you remove them from the package). Bring a good amount of water to boil. Pour the boiling water over the rice noodles until they are completely submerged. 

2.  Stir constantly to prevent clumping/sticking. When they are completely limp, give them a taste to see if they’re cooked through. The thread-like vermicelli noodles  will cook through in just a few minutes. The flat rice noodles might take upwards of ten minutes depending on thickness. Pay attention and test the noodles frequently because they’ll become mushy if they overcook.

3. Once the noodles are tender, drain them and run them under cool water to stop the cooking. Toss them with a small bit of sesame oil to keep the noodles from sticking to each other if you’re not going to use them right away. 

4. The noodles will be used in a stir-fry dish like pad thai, you definitely want to under-cook them a little bit. They will absorb more moisture and cook the rest of the way through once in the stir fry. If your noodles are perfectly cooked to start, they will turn to mush in the stir fry. 

NOTE: Even with a bit of sesame oil, the noodles still tend to clump up after you drain them. They will loosen again once you mix the noodles into your dish

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather ingredients.

2. Put frozen corn in mixing bowl.

3. Add other ingredients and mix.

4. Spead out on roasting pan and bake 190C 375F for 15 minutes or till roasted (lightly coloured).

5. Place in insert label, cover and place in warmer for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:30G

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52043" image="">Method:

Lay out almonds on a sheet pan in a layer not exceeding half and inch 

Bake in a 325 oven, shaking or stirring every 6-7 minutes

Bake for 10-20 minutes or unitl golden brown.

Please use a timer, almonds are expensive and burning them is preventable. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44335" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1.Drain Cannelini Beans. The Yield on these beans has been calculated in this recipe - roughly the loss of over a Kilogram in &quot;Aqua Fava&quot;. A quick rinse is valued, but not entirely necessary. 

2. Half all Grape Tomatoes. You will notice in this recipe that 5 LBS is the measured amount require. This is because each box of Grape Tomatoes that comes in from Freshpoint is 10 LBS - meaning: use half of a box for this recipe. Easy enough?

3. Small Dice yellow Onions. Saute with Cumin and Cayenne, adding 1 Bag of Frozen Corn and Red Pepper to the mix along the way. Do not roast this Corn in the oven for any reason - its starches develop and it becomes tough texturally. Deglaze this mixture with Apple Cider Vinegar, and season.

- Pick Oregano. Don&apos;t bother picking the Cilantro, as some stem is fine in this recipe. Rough Chop both of these, and reserve to add into the rest of this recipe.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...


NOTE: This recipe will last if properly refrigerated for up to 5 days. This is a large batch for this item, since it&apos;s new to the menu and may not sell well depending on diner preferences. Do not make more than this until it&apos;s proven that it will move. Waste not want not!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50555" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

2. On one side of the flat top. Add oil, vegetables and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

3. On the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and cheese and folder over. 

4. Garnish with chopped parsely and serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50855" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Half all cherry tomatoes
3. Toss in ponzu sauce and drain

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: mixing bowl, measuring cups, rubber spatula, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-15353" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny Crash overide
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

READ THE LABEL ON TEMPURA MIX

1.Dump wet mix into large square cambro
2. Slowly pour in dry ingredients while mixing with wooden spoon or gloved hand to avoid lumping
3. Lable &amp; rest in fridge for 1/2 hour beore use to proof. You will be able to tell its ready by the batter pubbling up and gaining volume.
4. Prepare batter in as small batches as possible, as often as possible

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



- </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64725" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Place the rice at the bottom of a slanted bowl and     make a well in the middle

3. Place the crispy cauli into the well, drizzle with thin lines of mayo (pointy tip squeeze bottle)

4. Arrange all ingredients around the cauliflower

6. Garnish with minced green onion and chopped cilantro



Portioning:

Utensils needed: Slanted white bowl
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides.  Allow to cool.

2)  Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender.  Blend well until combined into a paste.  Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

3)  Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix.  Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame seeds and korean chili flakes.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68129" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large rondeau or tilt skillet over medium heat, add  oil. Add in the already roasted potatoes and spread them out into an even layer. Cook for about 4-5 minutes without stirring or until browned.

2. Add in the onions, garlic, bell peppers, mushrooms &amp; vegan sausage, and old bay, and continue cooking until the potatoes are cooked through about 8-10 minutes.

3. Mix in the spinach and black beans. Allow it to cook for 2 more minutes or until the spinach has wilted and the beans have warmed.

4, Remove from heat, taste and adjust seasoning as needed.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53617" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut the onion into small dice lightly bigger than brunoise
3. 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35734" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Add thai chili to kecap manis, heat to a boil and remove from heat.   Reserve for mushroom mix.

2)  On grill, or working in batches in large rondeau over medium high heat, add canola oil.  Add onions when oil is hot and saute 1/4&quot; diced onions until translucent, about 5 minutes.  Add garlic and ginger and continue sauteing for another minute.  Add mushrooms and continue sauteing until mushrooms are evenly cooked.  

3)  Add kecap manis mixture and remove from heat.  Let mixture rest for 15-20 minutes and strain, reserving liquid.  
4)  Bring mushroom liquid to a boil and add hoisin sauce.  When the sauce gets sticky and reduced, add to mushrooms and reserve for service. 
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56923" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Remove timatillios hood and compost as trim
2. toss lightly in oil and salt + pepper
3. roast at 375F for 25 minutes
4. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7139" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Mix the remaining ingredients.


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

Approx 20% yield loss due to cooking pumpkin.

1. Cut pumpkin into 5cm chunks ( approx size ).

2. Fine chop the rosemary.

3. Toss the pumpkin with olive oil, salt, pepper, rosemary and maple syrup.

4. Spread out in even layer on a sheet pan lined with parchment. 

5. Roast in a 400f oven until soft, lightly caramelized. (should be able to mash with a fork)

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Seasoning and serve.

3. If left over cool, label and refriderate


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36669" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast bread 

2. assemble ingredients on top

3. Serve with a kindness!

**A fried egg on top is an awesome add on to this dish, if the guest requests one

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62009" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Mushrooms &amp; Broccoli

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. combine all inredients thuroughly, Reserve


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62010" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Mushroom &amp; Broccoli

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.In a large rondeau heat Oil. Once hot, add the thinly-sliced mushroom and cook on medium heat. Suate until they begin to brown just slightly. About 6-8 minutes. Make sure that the heat isn’t too high so as to burn the mushrooms.

2.While the mushrooms are cooking, steam the broccoli  until it is bright green. Approx 3-4 minutes. Once steamed, transfer to a colander and rinse with cold water to stop the cooking process.

3. When the mushrooms are fully cooked, add the steamed broccoli to the skillet and pour the sauce over the mushrooms. Stir constantly to avoid lumps and cook for 1-2 minutes over medium heat. 

4. Reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20368" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. gather ingredients
2. cut Chard into strips
3. wash and dry
4. place in contain label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.weigh out into cambro
3.Blend with hand blender, taste and adjust seasoning
4. Label and put in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:30ml

Utensils needed:hand blender scale</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Chop jalapenos in robot coupe until finely chopped.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well using hands with gloves on.  

3. Adjust seasoning To taste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

1. Preheat oven to 425*F

2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house rub. Mix well.

3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG RATHER THAN ROAST).

4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let cool.

5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

6. Check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26074" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny


1. Combine all well
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date, and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Peel and Sice the Sweet potatoes into 1/2 inch cubes. Toss in oil, salt, pepper, garlic and Paprika; add to a parchment lined baking sheet. Roast in oven untill soft inside and golden brown on outside. Reserve

2. Dice red peppers, and onion same as potatoes, toss with sliced mushrooms and chili peppers in oil, salt and pepper and place on parchement lined sheet. Roast in oven untill tender and slightly blistering. Reserve.

3. While the potatoes and pepper/onions/mushroom mix is still warm toss wiith prosessed kale and sliced tomatoes to wilt. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61906" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. This Dish is concidered a vegan option untill the addition of  eggs and Holly; please keep that in mind the base is to be kept vegan and eggs and holly are added on top to complete!

2. Place portioned amount of hash base at bottom of bowl.

3. Top hash with  2 medium poached eggs and 60ml of hollandaise.

4. garnish with fresh minced green onion and serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55779" image="">Allergen: soy



-Toss tofu with sauteed peppers and onions in Sweet &amp; Sour sauce, until well coated
-garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onion</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water from the pan runs clear

2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7135" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.: In a Robd coupe,Blend Basil and parsley until fine and smooth.
2:Add Salt And Pepper , Oil in the mixing bowl.
3:Portion evenly in squezze botles and put in fridge.
4. Label and date.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26140" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Preheat oven to 400*F
2.In large mixing bowl, combine tomatillos, poblanos, jalapenos, garlic, oil and S+P.  Mix well to coat.
3.Place cooling rack over med high flame on burners.  Roast tomatillos, peppers and onions until charred all over.  Place on baking tray.  Add garlic.
4.Roast until peppers, onions and tomatillos are cooked through and soft enough to blitz in food processor, about 10-15 minutes.
5.In bowl of food processor, add roasted vegetables, cilantro leaves and stems, lime juice and salt.  Process until a unalagos consistency.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62166" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place rice at the bottom of the bowl

2. Top with portion of hot mushroom broccoli mix

3. Garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onion, serve!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57154" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Whisk all ingredients together ensuring sugar is dissolved. Warm ever so slightly if needed to melt sugar.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-14479" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Juice &amp; zest oranges

2. Combine all ingredients in large bowl including orange zest and juice

3. Wisk together, hold for service. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9710" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.run threw processor S blade
3.label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44312" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook and cool quinoa

Chop all other ingredients

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58353" image="">Method:
- spread coconut ribbons on parchment lined sheetpan
- Toast in oven ( low fan ) at 375f until golden
- remove from oven, allow to cool
- label &amp; date
- hold for service

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-20248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess oil.

use is associated recipes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

2. Add mushrooms and rice, sautee 1 minute to toast rice slightly.

3. Pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

4. After 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. 

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62388" image="">this is just a yielded ration, not a recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46637" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.gently clean mushroom stems

2.cut down portions to approx the same size

3.Saute shallots, garlic,  in oil until translucent

4. Fold in thyme leaves and saute 1 min

5. Saute until mushrooms have expressed most of their liquid

6. Remove from heat, toss with fresh squeezed lemon juice, chopped parsley

7. Season with salt &amp; pepper

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, rondeau pot, insert, rubber spatula
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10115" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cut in cube of approx. 3/4 inche
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-65609" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7565" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Whisk all ingredients in a bowl
3.  Place in cambro Label, date and refridgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: mixing bowl, Rubber spatula, measuring cups measuring spoon whisk
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60377" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Allergens: Gluten/Dairy
Method:

1.In a large Rondeau over medium-high heat, melt  butter. Add the sausage and cook, stirring with a wooden spoon to break the meat into small clumps, until browned. 

2.Transfer the sausage to a large mixing bowl, leaving the fat in the pan.
Turn the heat down to medium, then add the onions to the pan along with 1 tablespoon of butter. Cook the onions, until soft and translucent, 

3. Add the onions to the mixing bowl with the sausage, along with the bread cubes, grated cheese, green onions and parsley. Toss well, then spread the mixture evenly into the prepared baking pan.

4. In a seperate bowl, whisk together the eggs, cream, salt and pepper.
Pour the egg mixture evenly over the bread mixture. 

5. Cover tightly with saran wrap and refrigerate for at least a few hours (Best overnight)

6. Preheat the oven to 350°F. Bake for aprox. one hour, uncovered, until puffed and golden brown. 

HOT HOLD/SERVE 

**Note** The cook time is based on cooking the bread pudding directly out of the refrigerator. If it&apos;s left to sit out at room temperature before baking, check for doneness after 45 minutes.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26019" image="">1. Combine well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32886" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.  Place appropriate amount of brown rice as well as spinach and kale in mixing bowl.  Dress with cumin lime dressing, mix well and place in serving bowl.

2. Top with chickpea salad portion, papadum crackers and crispy chickpeas.

3. Place chutney in corner of bowl.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54342" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and Tools
2. Build bowl: rice on the bottom, asian slaw, carrot/beet slaw, edamame, sprouts and pickles red onion all around the ring of the bowl.
3. pile tofu in the middle and garnish with nayo and green onion.
4. sevre with a smile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam rice.

2. Once rice is out of the steamer add all ingredients - oil, lime juice &amp; spice mix - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

3. When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65536" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a medium saucepan, combine vinegar, soy sauce, oil, ketchup &amp; brown sugar. Whisk well.

2. Bring the mixture to simmer.
In a small bowl, whisk together cornstarch and water (cold, tap).

3. Add cornstarch mixture to the sauce and whisk well. Simmer until it starts to thicken. Remove from heat.
Add pepper flakes.

Cool the sauce completely. It will continue to thicken with carry over cooking even more.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27405" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine warm brown rice or quinoa and sweet potato hash with 30 ml of cumin lime dressing and season well.  Place in serving bowl.

2.  Top with tomatillo salsa, pico de gaillo, crispy corn tortilla strips, avocado fan &amp; pickled jalapeno slices 

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26517" image="">1)  Rinse and drain bean sprouts under cold running water very well.  Allow to drain  

2)  Combine slaw mixture, angle cut green onion, julienne red onion, daikon and asian slaw dressing.  Toss well to incorporate and evenly distribute dressing.

4)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26048" image="">1. Combine balsamic vinegar,  dijon, garlic, maple syrup, salt &amp; pepper.

2. Begin blending with immersion blender till smooth add oil slowly and blend till emulsion
3. Store in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

Allergens:

Mustard
Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55057" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Build warm rice into bottom of the bowl, topping rice with 1 portion of greek salad then ask them if they would like feta and serve the proper portion amount  
2.Top with chick peas, a scoop of hummus and then parsely


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56777" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36621" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67599" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Preheat oven to 400F 

2. Gather ingredients.

3. Place broccoli and cauliflower florets in perforated pans and put in to steamer.  Steam for 5-6 minutes until just tender and still bright colour

4. In large rondeau over medium heat melt the butter, whisk in the flour and form a roux, cook out while whisking 1-2 minutes
 
5. While continuously whisking add in milk and cream a little at a time until thick and fully incorporated, continue to whisk auntil smooth and no lumps. cook out 5-6 minutes.

6. whisk in garlic powder, salt &amp; pepper, onion powder, and nutmeg.

7. Remove from heat, stir in small amounts of cheese (reserve half the mozza) and mix until incorporated.

8. Stir in broccoli and cauliflower florets, stirring to coat.
Grease a 2&quot; hotel panwith butter.

9. Pour in broccoli/cauliflower mixture and spread out into an even layer.

Top with remaining  shredded mozza cheese and bread crumbs.

10. Bake about 35 to 40 minutes or until golden, bubbly and the cheese has melted.


*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67601" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Dice tofu into bite size cubes (1&quot; x 1&quot;)

3. Whisk together all marinade ingredients

4. Toss marinade and tofu together till well coated and place into a sealed container and allow to marinate for a minimum of 4 hours (can be done a day ahead and left overnight)

5. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67606" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. small dice cucumbers, slice tomatoes in half.

3. Finely mince parsley and mint.

3. make dressing from lemon juice, olive oil salt &amp; pepper

4. in a large bowl combine cucumbers, tomatoes, herbs and lemon dressing

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67607" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. place rice and quinoa at the base of the bowl

2. place tomato/cucumber salad on top of rice, place marinated tofu on top of salad and garnish with tahini drizzle and fresh chopped cilantro

3. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67672" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. In a rondeau, add the oil and heat for 15 seconds
Gently add the spinach to the oil and let it wilt to half its size.  Don’t stir

2. Add the corn, black beans, tomatoes, seasonings and salt.

3. Cook for about 6-8 minutes on medium heat

4. Turn off the heat, taste for seasoning and adjust if needed. Reserve.


*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67673" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Loaded sweet potato

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Whisk together all ingredients, Put into squeeze bottles and reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67674" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

Baking the potato;

1. Set oven to 400F to bake sweet potato / yam

2. pierce each potato with a fork / knife all over to allow steam to escape. lightly toss potatoes in oil and place on a parchment lined tray.

3. place in oven and bake for 45-60minutes (this will depend on size. If the potato can be easily pierced with a knife its ready.

Assembly

1. Cut the sweet potato in half lengthwise

2. Gently open it up and top it with the warm black bean filling mix.

3. Hot hold for service (these do not freeze will so consider portions!)

 

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: Gluten, Dairy
Method:

1.Grease hotel pan (13x9 2&quot;) with butter

2. Spread Nutella on ALL sides of bread the put 2 slices togeter to make &quot;sandwiches&quot; cut each &quot;sandwich into cubes (1&quot; x1&quot;) set aside in a bowl

3. In a seperate bowl whisk together eggs, milk, cream, sugar and vanilla to make a custard.

4. Pour custard over nutella bread cubes.

5. Mash the bananas (making sure to use the ripest bananas possible!) and mix into the bread and custard. Mix to evenly incorporate.

6. Pour into the prepared greased hotel pan &amp; let stand 1-2 hours, ocasionally mixing to ensure bread is being evenly soaked.

7. Preheat oven to 350F. Bake until pudding is set in the centre. Aprox 45-50 minutes. Serve warm.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60381" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out the correct portion of warm bread pudding 

2. Garnish with minced green onions

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46870" image="">Allergens:

none
Icons:

n/a

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.zest the most outer layer of the lemon using a fine microplane
2. Set aside zested lemon to be used first/ juiced 
3. Use zest as close to recipe execution as possible but any excess is to be Stored, labeled and rotated correctly with any older product diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43674" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools

2. Combine all ingredients and mix well

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:mixing bowl, rubber spatula, insert

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58715" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a saute pan/ rondeau over medium/ high heat add butter, garlic and salt/ pepper.

2. When garlic is soft and fragrant (1 minute) add chopped mushrooms and cook until they are soft strirring occasionally.

3. When 90% cooked add whipping cream and reduce until mushrooms bind together slightly.

4. Turn off heat, add lemon zest, pesto &amp; parsley. Adjust seasoning if necassary.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50569" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: 58 g = 1/2 of an average peeled banana. 

1. Warm up crepe on the flattop.

2. Slice banana in to 1/4&quot; slices and place evenly along the middle of the crepe.

3. Spread Nutella along side of bananas. place coconut whip on top of bananas.

5. Fold and serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with seran wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50784" image="">1. Slice avocado and take pit out.
2. Scoop avocado meat in a small cambro.
3. Add PULP, lime juice, salt and pepper.
4. Smash it up and taste it
5. does it taste good?
If yes, then:
6 A. spatula avo out into a big cambro, label it and date it and rotate with older product properly
If no, then: 
6 B make it taste good and go back to step 6 A </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add  red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7341" image="">1: Add Meat sauce With vegetables.
2: Cook Penne 10 MIN
3: Place 6 oz pasta in sourghdouh bread bowl.
6: top with cheese.
7:bake 375 F untill golden .</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny


Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.pick leaves, wash and pat dry
3. Label, date and refridgerate

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny


Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Wash and trim off stem
3. cut to correct size for what you need

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46639" image="">Allergens:
n/a

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan, made with out gluten

Method:
- rince rice in a chinoise until water runs clear, let drain
- dice onions
- in skillet over med heat saute onion &amp; garlic until translucent but not colored
- add rice and saute for 3-5 min until rice begins to color
- add stock, bring to a boil, reduce to a simmer and cover
- cook over low heat until water has been absorbed
- remove from heat &amp; &quot;fluff&quot; with a fork or wooden spoon
- hold hot for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35895" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
CAL|Bowl|Havana

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and rinse rice in 4inch hotel pan
3.then place all ingredients except herbs in with rice and stir
4. Place pan in steamer and steam for 35 minutes
5. once cooked fluff with fork and cover with plastic wrap
6. place in warmer for service
7. garnish with greens for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:120G 

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9712" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Run threw food processor with S blade
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35880" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients

2. Using the food processer with julienne blade, run the carrots and beets through

3. Combine all ingredients

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26075" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Prep recipe:

1. Combine coleslaw mix and dressing.  Combine well.

2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate


Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55419" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Sweat garlic, shallot, lemon grass in oil
3. add curry paste and cook until encorperated
4. add cocnut milk and simmer for 45 minutes
5. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58350" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat olive oil in large saucepan or Dutch oven over medium heat, add onion and pinch of sea salt and sauté until onions are soft and tender (about 5-8 minutes) stirring frequently.

2. Add garlic and saute for additional 3 minutes, add the pumpkin puree, tomato sauce, sugar, and water stirring to combine, turn the heat to low and simmer for 10 minutes.

3. Add the coconut milk, cinnamon, rosemary, sage and stir to combine, simmer for 5 minutes, add sea salt and cracked black pepper to taste.

4. Add the cooked pasta &amp; roasted pumpkin and stir to combine.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9782" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry tomato
2.Cut by hand or if doing big amount then. Put together R2 with proper slicing and dicing blades
3.place insert and perferated pan under to catch the diced tomato and to strain excess liquid
4. once done lable and place in fridge
5. Clean R2 parts by hand and return to office.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:60g

Utensils needed:blue scoop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47377" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Gather ingredient.
2. pick into garnish sprigs
3. wash,dry and label date

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36571" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.trim mint if not already done
3.blend all but oil
4.Slowly add oil to incorperate
5.Label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. slice taro on correct slicer # (the thickness of a hard bite potato chip) 

3. cook in deep fryer until crisp and golden and let rest on a rack to breathe

4. season heavily, while hot, with salt &amp; pepper

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 175 grams a bag
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingerdients
2.Peel beets
3.Cut to desired needs

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50333" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at the base of the bowl

2. Place rosted squash, carrots and corn around the rice along the side of the bowl

3. Drizzle with lemon mint dressing

4. garnish with alfalfa sprouts and crispy taro chip

5. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10113" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Slice
3. Label, date and refridgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7635" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny Bravo

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Open can
2.Drain in strainer and wash throughly
3.Place drained beans in insert label and place in fridge
4. Heat in steam required amount

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:90G Blue scoop

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26515" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather ingredients
2.mix all togther
3.label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-40621" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2. 
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57372" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny


Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes until soft
2. place of resting wrack and let steam out full
3.roll into cool and full chill potatoes 
4. Gentle place in an insert to keep intact + store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

!. gather ingredients
2.Roast spices 300F 10 minutes
3. Blend together
4. label, date, and refridgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-65942" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cook scrambled eggs softly, not over cooking

2. Place a scoop of potatoes into the bottom of the bowl 

3. Place scamble centered in the botom of a bowl and top with warm chili miso sauce, 

3. Place slaw beside eggs and garnish with cilantro

4. Sprinkle crispy chickpeas over the dish

5. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.run threw food processor with grater attachment
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice by hand unless you need alot then.  Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51215" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Start off with rice on one side of the bottom of the bowl and beans on the other side

2. In between the gaps that appear around those two mounds add salsa and guacamole in the correct portions

3. Gently place eggs on top

4. Garnishes last

5. Serve with kindness!
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56906" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of prepared bak choy in small bowl

2. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44790" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Grab can 
2.open
3.Drain and rinse
4.place in container label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water
4. place in steamer and steam 30 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out your ingredients

2. Add quinoa + soy milk in a rondeau. Set the heat to low and cook for 18-20 minutes or until the quinoa is completely cooked (cover the saucepan with a lid - important). 

3. Add cocoa powder + maple syrup + salt. Mix well, cover the lid, and cook for 2 more minutes over low heat. 

4. Turn off the heat, transfer the quinoa to a serving dish, reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67922" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of prepared quinoa at base of bowl

2. Garnish with fruit around the bowl in quadrants

3. Top with toasted almonds 

4. Serve with kindness!!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67923" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place quinoa at base of bowl

2. all other garnishes in quadrants around the bowl.

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67926" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place warm quinoa at base of bowl

2. Place all warm garnishes in quadrants around the bowl

3. Top with poached egg and pesto garnish with fresh chopped parsley

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50739" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine half of apples and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the apples and heat until about 8-10 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-59581" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
CAL|Bowl|Havana

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredients

2. Measure and place all but the tofu in cambro

3. Stir to mix throughly

4. Add tofu and stir again

5. Label and place infridge

6. Cook propper amount for service time.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:90G

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35896" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:
SAUCE|Avocado Crema
YIELD|Tofu|Cumin &amp; Lime
COOKED|Rice|Coconut Pilaf
SALSA|Pico de Gallo
ROASTED|Corn

Method:

1.Place rice in bottom of bowl

2.Scoop other ingredients around the edge

3.Avocado Crema in middle

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51250" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2. Cut tofu into 1&apos; by 1&apos; cubes
3. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9741" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and clean ingredients.
2.Slice
3.Lable and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9857" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Toss the potato with oil, sale and pepper
3.  Spread on a baking sheet evently
4. Bake in oven at 350F for 15-20min, until they are cooked but still a little crunchy

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:scale, mixing bowl, baking sheet, oven
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. core the pepper composting craps
2. cool, store, label, wrap and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-39167" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2. cut by hand or if bigger amount process threw food processor using 3/4&quot; dice plate and blade.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58351" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Heat pasta sauce in frying pan, or hold hot in bain marie

2. Add hot pasta, chopped swiss chard, cinnamon, 1/2 rosemary, salt &amp; pepper and stir until chard has just wilted

3. Add 1/2 of the pumpkin pieces &amp; tomato and toss together.

4. Place pasta in appropriate service dish, top with remaining pumpkin, tomato

5. Garnish with pumpkin seeds, toasted coconut, remaining rosemary &amp; sage

6. Serve with kindnes!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67182" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Remove fully cooked warm quiche from tin and place on small plate.

2. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix.  Blend well.  

2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26401" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat deepfryer to 350*F

2. Drain and dry chick peas very well.

3. Fry the chickpeas in the hot oil.

4. Place crispy chickpeas in mixing bowl and season with chickpea spice.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools.

2. Toss in potato starch and shake off excess.

3. Fry at 350F.

4. Place on sheet with paper towel to absord excess oil

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: bowl, sieve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55778" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of rice at bottom of plate

2. place green beans next to rice

3. Place portioned amount of sweet &amp; sour tofu on top of rice and beans

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57499" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.
OR cut by hand if small amount  

2)  Set up an insert to catch onion as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68130" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot portion of hash in the bottom of the bowl

2. Garnish with fresh avocado fan (1/4 of avo) and fresh chopped parsley

3. Serve with kindness!



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46911" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Slice yams.

2. Deep fry.

3. Season. 

4. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67600" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. place portion of warm gratain on plate, garnish with fresh chopped parsley

2. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68139" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. On a parchment lined sheet pans lay out the case of beyond sausages (dont overcrowd pan)

2. Roast in oven until internal temp reaches 165F

3. Reserve for service.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68140" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

NOTE: Not only is this product Vegan it is also Halal

1. Place hot sausage on small servign plate

2. Place 25ml on side of plate next to sausage

3. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68187" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 450F. Grease 9 cups of a standard size muffin tin.

2. Divide the potatoes evenly between the prepared cups (do not tamp down). Bake in the preheated oven for 20 minutes.

3. In a bowl, whisk the chickpea flour, water, nutritional yeast, oil, baking powder, paprika, salt and pepper until blended and smooth.

4. Distribute the bell pepper &amp; green onions evenly over the baked hash browns; ladle the chickpea flour batter over the vegetables (cups will be filled to the rim).

5. Bake in the preheated oven for 18-20 minutes until the omelet cups are puffed and just set at the centers. Transfer to a cooling rack; cool at least 10 minutes before running a knife around the edge of each cup to remove.

6. Reserve for service. Serve warm


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68188" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm egg bites on small service plate. garnish with fresh chooped parsley.

2. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67351" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice &amp; beans in the bottowm of the serving bowl

2. Garnish with sliced olives, fresh chopped parsley and a lemon wedge(make sure there are no seeds in the lemon!)

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-26808" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Remove quiche from baking tin

2. Place warm quiche on small serving plate

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Remove Quiche from baking tin

2. Place warm quiche on small plate

3. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68201" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place hot cooked portion of tater tots in small bowl

2. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26044" image="">1)  In a sauce pot, combine half of berry mix, lemon juice, vanilla extract, sugar and water.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow water to reduce slightly and sugar to dissolve.

2)  Combine corn starch and cold water to make a slurry.  Add to simmering compote to thicken.

3)  Add remaining berries and allow to heat through until no longer frozen.  Add more water if necessary if mixture is too stiff.

4)  Store in appropriate vessel.  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61731" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Warm crepes on the flattop

2. place berry compote in centre of crepe, top with coconut whip

3. fold over into a triangle and place on service plate

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68232" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Drain and rinse chickepeas

3. Small dice cucumbers, red peppers, tomato. Julienne carrot, finely mince thai chili pepper (do not leave large pieces this will be very spicy)

4. Finely mince cilantro and mint leaves

5. In a large bowl toss together with dressing and ensure everything is evenly coated!

6. Reserve for service.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68233" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredients

2. Blend together and taste for seasoning. Asjust if needed.

3. Reserve


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67556" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place warm portion of rice at bottom of bowl

2. Put warm portion of mushroom kung pao base on top of rice

3. Garnish with roasted cashews and fresh minced green onion.

4. Serve with kindness.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place loaded/baked sweet potato in centre of plate

2. Using a squeeze bottle drizzle yogurt dressing in a zig zag patern acros the top of the potato

3. Garnish with fresh minced green onions

4. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredents
2.place in food processor, process till smooth
3.place in cambro label and date
4. refridgerate
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62187" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Oil the hot flat top

2. Crack 1 fresh egg and season lightly with salt &amp; pepper.

3. Fry egg it to the guest preference (sunny side, over easy, over medium, over hard)

4. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50636" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
