<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather ingredients
2. Weigh out into cambro.
3. Blend with hand blender, taste and adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:30ml

Utensils needed:hand blender scale</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7445" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9767" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Thinly slice up green onion.

2.  Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19209" image="">1) Slice celery to 1/8&quot; pieces.

2) Place in apropriate sized container, lable, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tahini, garlic, lemon juice, water and salt in large mixing vessel.  

2. Combine well with immersion blender.

3.  Add chopped parsley.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26091" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 320F

2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice.

3.  Slice each butt in half, and season pork with salt and pepper.  Make sure to get in all the cracks.

4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer on french top before putting it in the oven.

5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 3.5 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart

6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks, removing large pieces of fat. Add back some of braising liquid in pork to keep moist

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand. Add water, 1:1 with rice.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir to fluff and loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26328" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In appropriate sized sauce pan, combine rice vinegar, salt, sugar, and simmer until salt and sugar are dissolved.  Add thai chilis and ginger, turn off heat and allow mixture to cool to room temperature.

2)  Meanwhile, add carrot and daikon radish to 4L cambro container.  Add room temp pickling solution, and wiegh down vegetables with parchment to keep them submerged.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.  Vegetables are best if left to pickle for at least 24 hours.

Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine water and salt in a large pot.  Bring to a boil.

2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.  This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26489" image="">1)  Bring water to a simmer in a large pot.  

2)  Add noodles and turn off heat.  Allow noodles to soak about 5 minutes until cooked through.

3)  Drain noodles and rinse EXTREMELY THROUGHLY under cold water.  This will ensure that the noodles will not stick together.

4)  Reserve in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26497" image="">Preheat oven to 325*F


Spread walnuts out over baking tray and toast in oven until toasted and fragrant, about 15-20 minutes.  Ensure to stir the nuts and rotate pan about half way though cooking to ensure even toasting.  Allow to cool.

Store in airtight container.  Label, date and store in a cool, dry place.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26883" image="">

-Cook noodles for 5 mins in the steamer or
-Cook noodles for 3 mins in boiling water at the station</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat up oil in large sauce pot over medium low heat.  

2. Add garlic and and gently cook for 10 minutes.  That&apos;s right, 10 minutes.  Then add ginger puree and continue gently cooking for another 5-10 minutes. Stir it alot to make sure it doesn&apos;t burn, but really cook it out. 

3. Add kecap manis and rice vinegar.  Bring to a simmer for 10-15 minutes over medium heat.  Add corn starch slurry and simmer for another 5 minutes until thick.

4. Do not strain.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fill kettle with ROOM TEMPERATURE water. Do Not tutnr the kettle on.
2. Place the noodles into the water fully submerging the noodles. Mix the noodles around until they have loosened up and move freely and un-forzen
3. Noodles should be firm but not crispy.
4. Remove from kettle and let drain.
5. Lightly oil the noddles and store them labeled and rotated correctly.
6. Noodles are to be cook &quot;a-la-minute&quot; on the station as needed 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28994" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients in Robocoupe.  Mix in baches if doing large amount and season to taste.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-29391" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Kung Pao.jpg">1. Add oil to wok over medium heat.  Add thai chilis and allow to infuse the oil for about 30 seconds.  Add chicken and stir fry to 70% cooked.

2.  Crank the wok full blast and add vegetables and continue stir frying until chicken is fully cooked and vegetables are tender, about 4 minutes.  Add hunan sauce and hold warm.

3.  In the same wok, add chow mein noodles and stir fry with a small amount of sauce until hot throughout.  Hold warm.

4. When ready to serve customer, add 6 oz. chow mein noodles, and an 8 fl. oz scoop of chicken and vegetable mixture. 

5. Garnish with roasted cashews and green onions.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35245" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35787" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  Combine all well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37093" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Spaghetti.jpg">1)  Blanch cooked pasta in hot water until it is hot throughout.  Place hot pasta in serving bowl.

2)  Top with 5 meatballs and 6 fl. oz of tomato sauce.

3)  Garnish with parmesan cheese and parsley.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37167" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Add oil to large rondo/ pan over medium heat.

2) Add aromatic mix and cook stirring constantly until fragrant.

3) Add onion and continue cooking, stirring regularly until soft.

4) Add rice and toss to combine.

5) When rice is hot and everything is combined, turn off heat and season with soy sauce &amp; chopped cilantro.

6) Reserve and keep hot. OR

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37171" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41548" image="">Preps:
- De-stem Chilis (20 Minutes)
- Cut Onions (4 Minutes)
- Half Tomatoes (10 Minutes)
- Combine Water, Vinegar and chilli&apos;s mixture: reserve for later...

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

Pre-Oven
- Place Remaining Ingredients in 2 Deep Hotel Pans
- Oil, Salt - Toss (10 Minutes)
- Roast in Convection Oven at 400F for 1.5 Hours
- Stir Occasionally (Top will Caramelize)
- Add Water If Necessary

Post-Oven
- Add Remaining Ingredients: H20 / Vinegar
- Blend Thoroughly In Vitamix (30 Minutes)
- Season w/ Salt to taste
- Add Vinegar

Post-Processing
- Cool Down, and let Rest overnight.
- Vaccuum Pack in 2L Bags
- Label/Date &amp; Freeze for future use...

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam rice.

2. Once rice is out of the steamer add all ingredients - oil, lime juice &amp; spice mix - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

3. When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41574" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. PRE-SOAK Beans overnight!
   - 2 X 20L CAMBRO Containers
   - HALF of the Beans in Each
   - Filled with 12L of Water Each

2. Drain beans from their hydration liquid. Your cooking water should be different from your soaking water.

3. Using the small steam kettle, cook beans slowly in 20 extra liters of water. They should be good to start at 250F.

4. Cook the beans until they are soft, but not decomposing. During the cooking process it is important to skim off the foamy protein that will accumulate at the surface of the cooking beans&apos; water - this, if unchecked, will lead to a poor bitter taste and a lesser shelf life for the beans themselves.

5. While the beans are cooking, saute your onions in oil, until dark brown. Caramelize them as far as they will go, and then add cumin and garlic. Saute cumin and garlic for 5 minutes, and then take off heat.

6. Turn off steam kettle when the beans are cooked, and let beans sit. Take 4L of the cooking water, and set aside.

7. Drain beans, and then transfer them into a neutral container greater than 40L in volume. Get the large Immersion Blender.

8. Add the onion mixture with the garlic and cumin, as well as half of the salt, and half of the brown sugar. The remaining halves - set aside, and use to SEASON TO TASTE. 

9. With the Immersion Blender, blend about 4L of the bean mixture into a puree - and then add back into the rest of the beans, and mix. Add reserve liquid from the cooking, until you get - not a soup - beans with a puree of more beans.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42160" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix. 

Use a blender if you like, it is easier. A whisk will work too. 

***Please make sure to mix tahini before you use it as it settles and separates. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42355" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP,  an in house made ingredient recipe

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Open 2.8L cans of pineapple.

2. Drain Liquid - KEEP ON THE SIDE!

3. In the convection oven - at 400 Degrees (F) - roast the drained pineapple for 10 Minutes, or until darkening and caramelizing on the outside.

4. Remove from oven, and let sit until they&apos;ve reached room temperature...

*IN THE MEANTIME*

5. Set up the Vitamix!

*THEN*

6. In batches (4-5), begin mixing the lime juice, the drained pineapple juice from the cans, salt &amp; coriander - letting the Vitamix do its job until the mixture is at a fine puree! 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42364" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine and mix.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43341" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and allow the pickle juice to pickle the cabbage. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine and mix

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43680" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pot over medium low heat, add oil.  

2)  Process garlic as you normally would in food processor, but stop before a fine paste forms.  You want chunky bits of garlic.

3)  Add garlic bits for warm oil and fry, stirring frequently for 4-5 minutes until garlic is crispy.  Strain through fine mesh strainer and reserve oil.  Place cripsy garlic on papertowel to soak up excess oil.

4)  Once dry, place crispy garlic in appropriate container, lined with papertowel and lid tightly.  Garlic can be stored at room temperature for about 3 days.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43690" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients well.  Reserve for recipe.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43691" image="">1)  Make spicy eggplant, jasmine rice and crispy garlic as per recipe.  

2)  Place appropriate amount of rice in bowl, top with spicy eggplant, bean sprouts, chiffonade thai basil and cripsy garlic.  Serve immidiately.

Allergens:

Soy
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43692" image="">1)  Thaw beans, slice into bite sized chunks.

2)  Dice Eggplant into 3/4&quot; chunks, discard end piece with green top.

3)  Add oil to wok, then turn heat to high.  Immediately add thai chilis, and infuse in oil until beginning to char.

4)  Add diced onion and saute until beginning to soften.  Add garlic and saute 30 seconds more.  

5)  Add green beans, and continue sauteing for 2 minutes.  Add eggplant and saute 1 minute more.  Add stirfry sauce and combine well.  

6)  Hold hot for service.  

Allergens:

Soy

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44308" image="">SEQUENCE:

1. Rice
2. Beans
3. Sriracha Sour Cream
4. Pulled Pork
5. Roja
6. Pineapple &quot;Sauce&quot;
7. Cabbage Mix
8. Crispy Shallots




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine and mix.

2. Mix again every time you use it as it is not an emulsified dressing and it will separate. 

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44312" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cook and cool quinoa.

2. Chop all other ingredients.

3. Combine and mix.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Spread the brocoll evenlly on perforated pans
3. Steam untill aldente (4 min)

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Steamer, perforated hotel pans 2&quot;
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44362" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Method
1. Place tabouleh (65g) and fried cauliflower (60g) to plate.

2. Add hummus (30 ml), pickled cabbage (10 g) and a lemon wedge (1/6 slice).

3. Garnish with tahini drizzle and warm grilled pita (.25pc).

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44363" image="">PREP RECIPE

1. Trim and cut cauliflower into florets

2. Deep fry the cauliflower and toss in salt
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44601" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Toast and grind the cumin &amp; coriander.

2. Add remaining ingredients into large robot coupe with spatula attachement and puree to a smooth paste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


Prep:

- Process all ingredients into a size that will fit easily and not cause problems in the Vitamix. Also, find the PLUNGER for the Vitamix, as you will not be able to do this job without it.

- The Coconut Milk in this recipe will be used to loosen then process of Puree-ing the Green Curry Base Paste. Use Water only if necessary.

- Once processed ingredients and Coconut Milk are ready to go, Vitamix all of these ingredients into a paste. 

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

***This can be made in large batches, and frozen for future use if vac-packed. A Green Curry &quot;Base&quot; recipe only contains 4.62Kg of this base (HALF), to the rest of its ingredients.

Any questions? - Ask Chef...

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44641" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Fry tofu and season with salt and pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44686" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1 Toast peppercorns in a dry pan over low heat until fragrant. Pulse in nutribullet to break down 

2. Using a rondeau saute ginger, onions and garlic in oil. Once cooked out add other ingredients and stir - lowering heat to simer.. 

3. Raise to a boil and using a Corn Starch slurry, thicken the sauce slightly. 

4. Taste.

Use this sauce for both Dan Dan Pork and Dan Dan Tofu/Tempeh.
  
-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44866" image="">
Method:

***please note the malt vinegar and chili oil components are garnishes, please do not use in recipe, they are only in here for the costing purposes.***

The bok choy is steamed.

The noodles are cooked.

The sauce, including the tofu is finished and hot.

Place noodles in the base of a bowl, top with a 125 ml (4 fluid oz) ladle of sauce as well as 60 grams (2oz) of tofu. Place the 100g of steamed bak choy along one edge of the bowl. 

Top with the garnishes of bean sprouts, green onion and cilantro. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45416" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Thaw ground pork if it is frozen.

2. Heat oil in a large rondeau and add pork - saute well until done, add sauce and mix thoroughly.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

***Portions for this recipe are 4 (fluid) oz - approximately 160g
Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45419" image="">
Method:

***please note the malt vinegar and chili oil components are garnishes, please do not use in recipe, they are only in here for the costing purposes.***

The bok choy is steamed.

The noodles are cooked.

The sauce, including the ground pork is finished and hot.

Place noodles in the base of a bowl, top with a 4 (fluid)oz ladle of sauce. place the 100g of steamed bak choy along one edge of the bowl. 

Top with the garnishes of bean sprouts, green onion and cilantro. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50372" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1) Split pork loin in to quarters lengthwise. Should have 4 tube like pieces. In shallow pan or bag marinate pork for 24 hours making sure it&apos;s fully covered by the marinade.

2) Remove from marinade and place on a lined baking sheet on top of a wire rack. 

3) Roast pork at 425F atop a wire racks on a tin foil lined sheet pan until an internal temp of 144F is achieved. Reserve leftover maridande to recude until proper consistency to coat the cooked meat is reached.

3) Allow the meat to rest. Coat with reduction as needed 

4) Reserve excess marinade reduce in a pot until thick and syurupy. Cube up pork in to 1/4&quot; pieces and toss with reduced marinade to add flavour and moisture back in.

Portioning: 115g

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50386" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Method:
1.Combine all ingredients.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50480" image="">1) Put strainer in steam kettle, add chicken bones, and rinse with cold water. Drain.

2) Add all other ingredients to the steam kettle and cover with cold water.

3) Simmer for 4-6 hours uncovered, drain the stock and cool, lable and store.

4) Discard bones and other solids, clean and sanitize the steam kettle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Slice cucumber lenghtwise on a mandolin, do not use the core, as it is too soft and the cucumbers will break.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50686" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Remove the cabbage core and shred cabbage finely.

2) Place water, vinegar, and sugar in a pot and warm until the sugar is dissolved, add salt, cool completely then pour over the cabbage.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50690" image="">1. Pre heat oven 375F.
2. In a baking sheet, lay flat cashew.
3. Roast it for about 8-10minutes or until golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50694" image="">1) Heat up puttanesca sauce, place in half hotel pans, add artichoke hearts and hold for service.

2) For service, heat pasta per portion in hot water basket. Once hot, drain well, add to tossing bowl, add 40ml of puttanesca sauce, 15g of arugula. Toss well with tongs to combine.

3) With tongs gather pasta and add it to serving bowl, pour rest of toppings from tossing bowl over pasta and garnish with chopped basil and parm cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50700" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Teriyaki Tofu Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place rice in bowl and top with tofu/sauce mixture, zucchini.

2. Top with all vegetable ingredients in quadrants around the bowl. (Mushroom, cabbage, carrots, cucumber are served cold)

3. Garnish with sliced green onion.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:
sauce: 2oz ladel
rice: 1.5 white scoop
cabbage: yellow scoop
zucchini: yellow scoop
teriyaki: white scoop
mushroom: yellow scoop


Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50746" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Combine all ingredients in a pot, heat at medium until sugar dissolves. Then remove from heat.

2) Cool fully before using as marinade or if using later, store in appropriate sized vessel, label, date, refrigerate.

3) Make 1L per loin. Reserve sauce after marinating and reduce slightly.

4) Chill completly and pour sauce over cooked &amp; diced pork and mix well.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50795" image="">1. Thaw Corn. 
2. Saute onion. Add corn and spices. Salt if needed..</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50826" image="">1. Mix sour cream and water.
2. Put in a squeeze bottle. 
3. Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51828" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51922" image="">1. In large rondeau, heat oil and sautee garlic until browned, then add chili flake, chopped roma tomatoes, capers, olives, oregano. Stir until fragrant.

2. Add artichoke hearts, remove from heat. Label, date, refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52039" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Heat oil in a large Rondeau and add Tofu. Stir to crumble.

2. Add Dan Dan Sauce and continue to stir until tofu is fully coated.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess oil.

use is associated recipes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together EXCEPT green onions.

2. Add sliced green onions last.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54174" image="">1. Place warm rice in centre of bowl.

2. Ladle beef and sauce over. Place cucumber slices off to the side and sprinkle with diced tomato.

3. Garnish with cilantro/ green onion.

RICE- White Ice Cream Scoop

STEW- 6oz. Ladle

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54344" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Mass to volume conversion recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55083" image="">1. Peel and diced parsnip.
2. Combine the rest of ingredient in mixing bowl.
3. Roast.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55141" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Ensure corn is defrosted and all excess water removed.

2. In a mixing bowl combine corn, onion, oil, chili powder and salt and pepper and mix evenly.

3. In a 450*F oven cook until corn takes on some dark colour and is slightly caramalized.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55419" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
2. Sweat garlic, shallot, lemon grass in oil.
3. Add curry paste and cook until encorperated.
4. Add coconut milk and simmer for 15 minutes.
5. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55564" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1) Rough chop ginger and shallots.

2) Put everything into a blender and blend, slowly adding oil until everything turns into a smooth paste.

3) Reserve and use within 3 days.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56556" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix beef well to ensure even coverage.

2. Beef should marinade for a minimum of 12 hours. 

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56557" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Ginger Beef

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. In a large saute pan or rondo over medium heat add oil. Once warm add ginger/garlic mixture and sweat, stirring until fragrant.

2. Add vegetables and chili and saute until fragrant. Ensure vegeatbles are NOT OVERCOOKED and have a bit of bite in them.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56558" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56631" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Use a vitamix to make this sauce. It is essential that you use a blender strong enough to puree the cashews in the sauce so it is not grainy.  If you do not have a vitamix, pre soak the cashews in hot water for a minimum of 1 hr before making the sauce. 
2. Place all ingredients in the vitamix, puree until smooth

3. Adjust consistency with water until desired consistencty is reached.

4. Adjust seasoning - acid (tamarind), heat(sambal), sweet(sugar), salt(veg fish sauce) to desired taste.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56816" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1) In food processor puree chilies, shallots, garlic, turmeric, ginger and galangal to a smooth paste. Marinade beef overnight.

2) Season beef with salt and pepper.

3) In a large rondo or tilt skillet over medium heat add marinaded beef and fry to bring out the flavours of the marinade. Stir often until quite fragrant.

4) Wrap up lime leaves, bruised lemongrass &amp; cinnamon sticks in a bouquet garnish to add to liquid.
5) add salt, pepper and coconut milk and simmer, stirring occasionally to prevent sticking.

6) Simmer for 2-3 hours or until beef is tender, adding water if it gets too dry.

7) Remove lemongrass &amp; cinnamon stick Bouquet garnise and adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56834" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Ginger Beef

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Remove beef from marinade and dredge liberally in corn starch. ENSURE EACH PIECE OF MEAT IS COMPLETELY COATED IN CORN STARCH.

2. Shake off excess corn starch and in batches deep fry until crispy (2-3 minutes). Reserve on tray.

3. In a large rondo or wok add sauce and bring to a boil.

4. Add corn starch, return to a boil while whisking. Turn off heat and add fried beef, turning to coat.

5. Hot hold for service.

Portioning:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56835" image="">1. Place rice in bottom of bowl.

2. Top with beef, then vegeatbles, green onion and sesame seeds.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56853" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Brussle Sprout Pesto Pasta

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. In food processor combine parsley, olive oil, walnuts, garlic, salt &amp; pepper and pulse until chunky consistency is reached.

2. Using a spatula scrape down sides of bowl add parmesan cheese and pulse one or two times to combine.

3. Taste for seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56855" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Trim &amp; thinly slice brussel sprouts.

2. In a rondo over medium heat add olive oil, garlic and chili flakes and sweat strirring often for 1-2 minutes.

3. Add sliced brussel sprouts, salt &amp; pepper and saute until sprouts are slightly soft.

4. Add cream and stir to combine. Do not over reduce cream. It should coat sprouts and slightly bind them.

5. Hold for service.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56895" image="">1. Drop precooked pasta into blancher to heat through.

2. Strain off excess water and place pasta in mixing bowl. Add a ladle of sauce, pesto, salt &amp; pepper and toss to combine ensuring even coverage.

3. Check seasoning and place in bowl.

4. Garnish with parmesan cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic, turmeric and lemongrass and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.  Add yellow curry paste and saute until fragrant, about 1 minute more.
   
2. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  Strain through fine chinois. Add fish sauce and adjust seasoning. 
3. Thicken with corn starch.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56995" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Jambalya Garnish

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large bowl toss the corn oil, salt, and pepper together till evenly distributed.

2. On a parchment lined baking sheet evenly spread the corn into a single layer.

3. Place in a 400 F oven for 3-5 minutes rotate and cook for another 2-3 minutes (or as needed)

4. once corn has a slightly light brown char around the edges.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58343" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Sweat until fragrent but not soft.

2. Use or...

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58654" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a rondeau sauté the onion, bell peppers and garlic until soft and translucent. 

2. Add rice, liquids and seasonings.  Add in the uncooked rice, stock, crushed tomatoes, Cajun/Creole seasoning, cayenne and bay leaf.  Give everything a good stir. reduce to low flame.

3. Cover and cook  25-30 minutes, being sure to stir the mixture every 5 minutes or so (to prevent burning) until the rice is nearly tender.

4.  Add the tofu and okra and cook for a final 5 minutes.

5. Taste and adjust seasoning as needed.  

HOT HOLD/SERVE
   
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-59591" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. de-stem chillis
2. Simmer chilli&apos;s in water 15 minutes and let cool overnight.
2. strain chilis out, reduce liquid by 1/2 and cool
3. Add liquid and chilis (COLD) to vitamix and blend smooth
4. add vinegar and salt
5. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61685" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Place coconut oil in a rondo over medium heat.
2. Once warm add curry paste and sweat until fragrant, stirring so paste does not burn (3-4 minutes). You want to draw out as much flavour as possible in this step.
3. Add coconut milk, lime leaves (no stems) and bring to a simmer.
4. Simmer until desired consistency is reached.
5. Remove from heat, add fish sauce &amp; palm sugar and adjust seasoning. Remove lime leaves.
6. Curry should be spicy/ sweet/ salty &amp; slighty sour.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61764" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62501" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. All veg should be 1/4&quot; dice (except jalapenos which can be minced).

2. Adjust seasoning and keep cool.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62502" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Season salmon with S&amp;P.
2. Make cross hatch grill marks on the presentation side of salmon (top).
3. Finish in oven until medium well.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62503" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-64438" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Mix well. This can be mixed in advance as the quinoa will soak up the dressing.
2. Taste for seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67824" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Toss each vegetable SEPERATELY in olive oil, caraway seeds and seasoning.
2. Roast at 425F on seperate full sized baking sheets until just cooked and slightly coloured.
3. Once cooled mix together, label and store.

Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67917" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix all ingredients well.
2. Bring to a boil and thicken with slurry.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67990" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Carefully seperate dry noodleas without breaking.
2. Without using the baskets drop into 350F deep fryer.
3. They should puff up and be cooked in 5 seconds.
4. Remove with a spider and place on paper towel lined tray to cool.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67993" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE
Final product handed to the customer

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE***

Method:
1. Dress soba noodles, edamame, diakon &amp; carrots in miso dressing and place in middle of bowl.

2. Drizzle with sriracha yoghurt.

3. Garnish with green onion, pickled ginger, wasabi peas and sesame seeds.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67995" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Soak raisins in boiling water for 1 minute and drain well.
Toast pistachios. 
Reserve both for the end.

2. In a rondo or tilt skillet warm oil over medium heat.

3. Sweat onion, turmeric &amp; cardamom stirring often until fragrent. Add rice and mix well.

4. Add stock and salt and bring to a boil. Reduce heat to a simmer, cover and cook until rice is done. (30-40 minutes)

5. Mix well to break up rice and stir in rasins, pistachios &amp; green onions.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68207" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  Dredge diced pork in salt, pepper &amp; flour until evenly coated.
2. Over medium heat in tilt skillet add oil and working in batches sear pork until golden brown. Remove and reserve.
3. In skillet add onion, carrot, garlic, diced poblanos, jalapenos and spices and cook out until fragrent (4-5 miinutes) stirring often.
4. Add tomato paste and cook out (2-3 minutes).
5. Add stock and pork and bring to a simmer.
6. Add diced potatoes after 30 minutes.
7. Simmer until pork is tender (apprx 30 minutes).
8. Adjust seasoning.
 
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
