<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25107" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-25415" image="">1. Grill the King Oyster mushroom with some oil and salt &amp; pepper.

2. Blanch the bok choy

3. Place quinoa in center of bowl, top with the mushrooms and ladle the warm vinaigrette over.

4. Place the bok choy on the side of the quinoa. 

5. Garnish on the top with the beets and carrots.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients
2. Slice onions with food prossecer slicing blade
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion
4. cool down and store in cambros

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water from the pan runs clear

2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26022" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place apples, cinnamon, and brown sugar together in a pot.

2. Add water if needed (the frozen apples will purge some liquid, but be prepared to add some if it seems to not be enough) Bring to a boil and reduce to a simmer for  about 5-10 minutes

3. Make a cornstarch slurry and pour it in incrementally, while stirring the pot. Be careful to add a bit at a time, and check the consistency between additions, because once the sauce consistency has been acheived, no more slurry should be added. 

4. Spread out on baking tray to cool.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tahini, garlic, lemon juice, water and salt in large mixing vessel.  

2. Combine well with immersion blender.

3.  Add chopped parsley.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26140" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Preheat oven to 400*F
2.In large mixing bowl, combine tomatillos, poblanos, jalapenos, garlic, oil and S+P.  Mix well to coat.
3.Place cooling rack over med high flame on burners.  Roast tomatillos, peppers and onions until charred all over.  Place on baking tray.  Add garlic.
4.Roast until peppers, onions and tomatillos are cooked through and soft enough to blitz in food processor, about 10-15 minutes.
5.In bowl of food processor, add roasted vegetables, cilantro leaves and stems, lime juice and salt.  Process until a unalagos consistency.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26173" image="">1. Drain chickpeas in a large sauce pot, cover with cold water and simmer for 5 minutes. Retain water

2. Puree garlic, ginger, jalapenos and cilantro into a paste.

3. Heat oil in large rondeau or tilt kettle over medium low heat. Once WARM, add cumin seeds, fry until aromatic, about 2 minutes.  Next add garam masala, coriander, chili powder and turmeric.  Continue sauteing with cumin seeds for another 2-3 minutes.   Add onion and turn heat to medium.  Continue sauteing onions for 10-15 minutes until very brown and spices are cooked out.

4. Add paste to onion and spice mixture, saute for 2 minutes stirring frequently.

5. Stir in mashed tomatoes, chickpeas, water and salt. Bring to a simmer then turn heat to medium low until sauce begins to thicken.

6. Stir in lemon juice. Garnish with cilantro.

7. Allow to cool, transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

1. Preheat oven to 425*F

2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house rub. Mix well.

3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG RATHER THAN ROAST).

4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let cool.

5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

6. Check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix.  Blend well.  

2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26385" image="">1)  Combine olive oil, lemon juice, crushed red pepper and crushed garlic and seasoning.  Combine well with a whisk.

2)  Pour marinade over torn kale leaves.  Toss to coat and refrigerate overnight in an appropriate container.  

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine water and salt in a large pot.  Bring to a boil.

2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.  This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26401" image="">

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat deepfryer to 350*F

2. Drain and dry chick peas very well.

3. Fry the chickpeas in the hot oil.

4. Place crispy chickpeas in mixing bowl and season with chickpea spice.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1)  In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

2)  Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Egg
milk

Method:

1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.  

2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279



1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26883" image="">

-Cook noodles for 5 mins in the steamer or
-Cook noodles for 3 mins in boiling water at the station</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27275" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Black Bean Bowl.jpg">1)  Combine Quinoa with half of cumin lime dressing, place in bowl.

2)  In a saute pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once hot, add potato hash and dressing and sauce until warm throughout, about 1 minute.  Drop poached egg into warm water.  

3)  Add chopped cilantro to hash and plate on top of warm quinoa.  Place avocado on top of hash, make a well for the egg and put egg in.  Garnish with more cilantro and serve. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27383" image="">1)  In mixing bowl, combine cooked quinoa and 30 ml of lemon tahini dressing.  Place in serving bowl.

2)  Combine shredded beets, edamame, matchstick carrots, spinach and roasted yam with remaining dressing.  Combine well and place on top of quinoa.  Garnish with roasted sesame seeds and lemon wedge.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27405" image="">1)  Combine warm brown rice or quinoa and sweet potato hash with 30 ml of cumin lime dressing and season well.  Place in serving bowl.

2)  Top with tomatillo salsa, pico de gaillo, crispy corn tortilla strips, avocado, jalapeno slices and lime wedge.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28293" image="">Allergens:
Gluten, Wheat, Mustard, Soy, Egg

Icons:
N/A


1)  Fry chicken strips according to package directions.  Double check that they are fully cooked by using a probe thermometer and taking the temperature.  Chicken strip should register at least 70*C to ensure it is well done.  Hold for service in food warmer.

2)  Serve with choice of sauce.

*Recipe assumes 2.0 oz avg. weight per chicken strip.  4 per order.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28994" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients in Robocoupe.  Mix in baches if doing large amount and season to taste.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32800" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Drain chickpeas, lightly mash into a course texture using a food processor.  Do not blend into a smooth paste.

2. Add green onion, red pepper, cilantro, vegan mayo, garlic, ginger, turmeric, lemon juice and salt and pepper into chick peas.  Mix well to combine.

3. Adjust seasonong.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32886" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Curried chick pea.jpg">1.  Place appropriate amount of quinoa or brown rice in mixing bowl.  Dress with cumin lime dressing, mix well and place in serving bowl.

2. Top with chickpea salad portion, papadum crackers and crispy chickpeas.

3. Place chutney in corner of bowl. Garnish with lemon wedge (1/8th of a lemon- please remove ALL seeds).</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35255" image="">1) Cut cucumber in quarters lenght wise, cut out seads.

2) Cut remaining pieces in to 1.5 inch lenght pieces and cut in to 1/16th inch sticks.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: soy
Method:

1)  Combine kombu, ginger, garlic, star anise and water.  Bring to a boil, then remove from heat and allow to infuse for a few hours, or preferably overnight.  

2)  Add miso and bring back up to heat, ensuring to stir often until miso is disolved and broth is hot.  Add tofu and soy sauce.  Taste for seasoning. (80*C at least)

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35319" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Miso Dumpling Soup.jpg">1. Heat the broth, bak choy, gyoza, mushrooms and the noodles.

2. Assemble all of the ingredients in the bowl.

3. Garnish with green onion, radish and chili oil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35337" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Milk
Dairy

Method:

1)  Preheat oven to 300*F

2)  In appropriate sized pot, combine water, garlic, shallot and thyme bring to a simmer, then take off heat and allow to infuse for about 20 minutes.  Strain out aromatics and add cream. Reserve warm.

3)  Combine cornmeal and salt.  Pour cornmeal mixture into stock and cream while whisking constantly

4)  Add mixture to hotel pans, and put in oven.  bake for 45 minutes, stirring every 15 minutes.

5)  Add butter and parmesan cheese.  Taste for seasoning and reserve for service, or 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35338" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor, combine half of the oil, vinegar, basil, parsely, arugula, garlic puree and seasoning.  Process until smooth.  Do not strain.  

2)  Add remianing oil and STIR with a spoon or spatula to combine. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35341" image="">1)  Place warm polenta in bottom of bowl.  Top with marinated kale and radish, then egg, and garnish with salsa verde.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35460" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Set aside cut tomatoes, chopped herbs and onions. 

2. Mix tabouleh with all remaining seasoning  

3. Gently fold in tomato and herbs

4. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35461" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Tabbouleh Bowl.jpg">1. Scoop appropriate amount of tabouleh into mixing bowl.  Combine with dressing and mix well.  

2. Top with hummus, crispy chickpeas and grilled pita bread.
 
3. Garnish with seedless lemon wedge.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35514" image="">1)  Cook lentils in water or steamer until tender.  Cool on large baking tray and reserve for recipe.

2)  In large frying pan or rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onion and sweat, approx. 3-4 minutes.  Add house rub and cook until seasoning is fragrant, approx 1- 2 minutes.  Be carefuly not to burn.

3)  Add garlic, shallot, carrot and tomato paste and saute for 2 mintues more, stirring frequently.  

4)  Add BBQ sauce, lentils and a little bit of water to thin out if necessary.  Stir to combine and taste for seasoning.  Hold for service or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35515" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Sloppy.jpg">1)  Toast bun on grill.  Add sloppy joe filling.  Toss arugula with lemon juice, and S&amp;P.  Place on top of sloppy joe filling and close bun.  

2)  Serve with greens salad</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35653" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  Preheat grill to high.

2)  Add oil to portobello mushroom and coat well.  Add
salt and pepper, put in oven and roast for 10 minutes or until mushrooms are tender throughout.  Reserve for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35655" image="">1)  Prepare portobellos according to recipe.

2)  Prepare sundried tomato mayo according to recipe.

3)  Place portobello mushroom on grill to heat through.  Place crumbled feta cheese in the mushroom cap and then cover with provolone.  Grill until heated through and cheese is melted, about 2-3 minutes.

4)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill.  Once toasted spread sundried tomato mayo on both sides.  Place grilled portobello on bottom of bun and top with arugula.  
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35689" image="">1)  Rinse sorghum grain VERY THROUGHLY!!! in china cap strainer and water.  You can make this easy by putting the strainer in a large soup pot and running the water over the sorghum until the water runs clear from the pot.

2)  Add water to rinsed sorghum and bring to a rapid simmer over medium high heat.  Stir every once in a while to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking to the pot.

3)  When the water comes to a rapid simmer, cover with aluminium and turn to very low heat.  Sorghum will take about 30-40 minutes to cook.  When Sorghum is finished it will have a pleasant, chewy consistency.

4)  Rinse under cold water until cool and store in appropriate vessel.  Label, Date, Refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35732" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F

2)  mix diced eggplant with salt.  Place in perforated hotel pan to allow water to leech out for about 10-15 mintues.  Rinse well and allow to dry slightly.

3)  In a large mixing bowl, combine oil and diced sweet potato.  Mix well and put in roasting pans.  Roast at 400*F for about 10 minutes or until just beginning to soften.

4)  Meanwhile, combine drained eggplant and oil with a bit of salt and pepper and roast on seperate pan in the same oven as sweet potato, about 5-10 minutes.  Pull out both sweet potato and eggplant together.

5)  In large rondeau over medium high heat add some remaining canola and sesame oil.  Once hot, add diced onion and saute for about 5 minutes, or until beginning to soften.  Season.  Add garlic and sambal and saute for 1 minute more.  turn down heat, and add miso.  Mix very well until fully incorporated into onions.  

6)  Add maple and soy and allow to thicken slightly.  

7)  Add roasted sweet potato and eggplant and carefully stir to blend together.  Reserve mixture for service, or cool and store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.      </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides.  Allow to cool.

2)  Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender.  Blend well until combined into a paste.  Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

3)  Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix.  Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame seeds and korean chili flakes.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35782" image="">Layer ingredients into the bowl in the indicated amounts in a visually appealing manner, with the rice or quinoa in the bottom of the bowl.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35787" image="">1)  Combine all well.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35801" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  In large mixing bowl, combine oil, yams, and salt and pepper.  Mix well.

2)  Put seasoned yams on parchment lined roasting pan, and roast yams until well caramalized and tender, about 15 minutes.  Make sure to rotate pan and mix product half way through cooking to ensure even roasting.

3)  Make sure to not smash up yams.  We need them to be nice and unsmashed.

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37090" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients except for corn starch and water in sauce pot.  Bring to a simmer.  Blend well with immersion blender.

2)  Combine water and corn starch to make a slurry.  Add to simmering sauce and allow to simmer until thickened.  Sauce should be a light, sticky consistency.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37091" image="">1)  Dice tofu into 3/4&quot; chunks.  Lightly fry in deep fryer and reserve for making sweet and sour stir fry.

2)  In wok on medium high heat, add oil.  Add onion and stirfry for 30 seconds to a minute.  Add diced red pepper, tofu and pineapple chunks.  Continue stirfrying for another minute until peppers and onion are beginning to soften.  

3)  Add sweet and sour sauce and bring to a simmer.  

4)  Place appropriate amount of coocnut brown rice in bottom of serving bowl.

5)  Top with sweet and sour tofu sauce and vegetables.  Garnish with green onion and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Sulphite
Method:

1)  In bowl of food processor with blade attachments, add drained capers, roasted garlic paste, fresh basil, drained sundried tomatoes and lemon juice.  Blitz until blended together very well.  

2)  Stir in oil WITH A SPOON (do not puree) and season with salt and pepper.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38661" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Make sundried tomato paste as per recipe.

2)  In mixing bowl, combine sundried tomato paste and mayonnaise.  Combine well with a spatula.  Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43735" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In medium sauce pan over medium heat, add berries and maple syrup.  Simmer for 5-7 minutes, or until berries are soft and have released all their liquid.

2)  Mush up berries real good with a spoon.

3)  Add chia seeds and stir to combine.  Turn heat to low and stir frequently for 8-15 minutes until liquid has reduced and mixture is slightly thickened.

4)  Remove from heat and stir in vanilla and lemon zest.  Transfer to a bowl and allow to cool.  The mixture should thicken and have a jam like consistency when it&apos;s cold.  Taste for seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43736" image="">1)  Add almond butter to a large cambro container.  Add about 1/4 or the coconut milk and, using a large immersion blender begin incorporating.  

2)  Add remaining ingredients, except chia seeds. Continue incorporating well with immersion blender until everything is mixed really well.  

3)  Add chia seeds and incorporate well with a spatula.  Allow to rest overnight in the fridge to thicken.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43737" image="">1)  Bring water to a rapid boil in an appropriate sized pot.  Gently lower eggs into boiling water with a slotted spoon.

2)  Cover pot with aluminum foil and turn heat off completely.  Allow eggs to sit in hot water for 8-9 minutes.  

3)  Strain eggs, and shock in ice bath to stop eggs from cooking further and to make them easier to peel.

4)  When eggs are completly cool, peel them.

5)  Egg whites should be fully cooked, and yolk should be slightly runny.

6)  Store in appropriate contianer.  Label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Egg

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43738" image="">1)  Prep soba noodles as per recipe, and portion.

2)  Prepare Dobanjiang Sauce as per recipe.

3)  Place chilled soba noodles in mixing bowl and mix well with dobanjiang sauce.  Place noodles in serving bowl and garnish with remaining vegetables. Zigzag a squirt of sauce on top of vegetables, then garnish with sesame and nori and soft boiled egg. Cut the egg in half and present the cut side. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43918" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

***This recipe does not need to be heated, put all of the ingredients in a bowl and whisk well.***

1. Combine all well. 

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44349" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Chana Mansala.jpg">Place rice on plate

Top with Chana masala, stick in a wedge of naan and garnish with yogurt and cilantro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44604" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Raspberry.jpg"/>
	<Recipe id="P-45255" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat

Icons:
N/A

Method:
 70 pcs average per case

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46507" image="">1) Cut cherry tomatoes in half, toss with oil and salt and pepper mix, roast in a hot oven 450F briefly 10 min or so, just to soften up and brown lightly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46842" image="">1)  Rinse rice well under running water, until the water begins to run clear.

2)  Pour coconut milk and over rinsed rice and mix well.  

3)  Steam for 20-25 minutes or until rice is tender.

4)  Spread out on a baking sheet to cool, or add to appropriate vessel and hold warm for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46913" image="">1. Spread ingredients evenly inside the tortilla, fold in half and grill on the flat top, ensuring both sides are golden brown and crispy.

2. Cut into 4 even pieces.

3. Place tortilla strips on plate and put quesadilla on top to prevent the bottom getting soggy.

4. Garnish on the side of the plate with salsa and sour cream.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47435" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Chana Mansala.jpg"/>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49249" image="">1) Combine and whisk. place in an appropriately sized container, cover, label and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-49250" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Eggplant.jpg">1. Cube tofu and toss thoroughly in cornstarch.

2. Deep fry tofu and when it crispy, drain well and toss in a little bit of the miso glaze and set aside. 

3. Dice eggplant and place on a sheetpan. 

4. Roast at 425F for 8-10 minutes or until softned and has browned nicely, flip them all over, baste with the miso glaze and return to oven for a couple minutes for the glaze to bake on. 

5. To serve, place rice in middle of bowl, add eggplant, top with some glazed tofu cubes and sprinkle with sesame seeds, add a mound of pickled carrots and green onion to garnish. 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50373" image="">1) Add all ingredients to bowl of mixer, with paddle attachment mix till well combined.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50375" image="">1)  Grill or toast bread until golden brown, crisp and warm.

2) Add the cream cheese spread and top with the salsa</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50380" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a bowl combine mustards, garlic, shallots,  capers, red wine vinegar and seasoning.

2. Whisk together. (this is a &quot;broken&quot; dressing and not an emulisified one, it must be stirred well when it is being used).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50395" image="">1) Coat artichokes in oil and season

2) Place on grill cook until there are good grill marks on the artichokes. Cool, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50397" image="">1) Combine well, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50401" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Mezze Platter.jpg">1) Gently grill the pita bread, artichoke hearts and lemon wedges to get grill marks, then slice pita into 8 wedges.

2) Place the raita &amp; hummus in the the center of the platter and neatly arrange the vegtables and pita around the sauces. Garnish with 2 grilled lemon wedges.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50468" image="">1) Boil the crap out of the barley until it is as smooth as porridge texture. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50471" image="">1) Heat porridge and hold for service.

2) Ladel porridge into a bowl, top with apple compote, sprinkle with raisins and top with coconut cream.

*****It is possible to make many variation on this recipe in fresh fruit in season, nuts, savory sausage or bacon and frozen or dried fruit.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50513" image="">1. Combine 3/4 frozen peaches, sugar, lemon juice. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the peaches and heat until about 8-10 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry. (Add the cornstarch slurry incrementally, allowing the compote time to thicken between additions, once the desired consistency achieved, stop adding) finish with vanilla extract.

3. Allow to cool, label, date and refrigerate or if using immediately, add to hot holding vessel.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50517" image="">1) Remove softer fronds of the dill from the harder stems. Chop well for garnish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50526" image="">1. Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg mixture and put on griddle.  Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with compote, whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50555" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Omelet.jpg">1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

2. In one side of the flat top. Add oil, vegetables and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

3. In the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and cheese and folder over. 

4. Garnish with chopped parsly and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50556" image="">1) Preheat flat top 350*F.

2) In one side of the flat top. Add oil,  vegetables and salt. Cook about 2 minutes.

3) in the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg, once egg starts set.Add the sauted vegetables and cheese, folded over, garnish with parsley and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50651" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Ensure bok choy has been very carefully washed to remove any grit inside.

2. Blanch in boiling salted water.

3. Shock in ice bath.

4. Remove when cooled.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


1. Blanch Bock Choy in a boiling water
2. Put in bain Marie during service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50672" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Saute the peppers and onion in oil.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with hot liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50894" image="">1) Add dressing to greens and mix well.

2) Top with cucumber, carrots, sunflower seeds, tomatoes, radish, red pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51006" image="">Seed cucumbers and dice, dice tomatoes, place in a bowl. 

Add other ingredients, toss and mix.

Taste and adjust as needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51210" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-52812" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53616" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut Stem and seed off of pepper
3. cut into Small dice, lightly bigger than brunoise

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. core the pepper composting craps
2. cool, store, label, wrap and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56923" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Remove timatillios hood and compost as trim
2. toss lightly in oil and salt + pepper
3. roast at 250 for 25 minutes
4. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61660" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method: 
1. Peel beets.
2. Using mandoline, julienne beets.
3. Rinse in cold water until water runs clear so beets don&apos;t bleed into other foods.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
