<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9741" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and clean ingredients.
2.Slice
3.Lable and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27317" image="">ALLERGENS
NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-30552" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine hot water and beef base and bring to a boil to incorporate.  Set aside.

2. Combine sesame oil and canola oil in large pot over medium low heat.  When oil is warm (not hot!) add garlic, black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, korean red pepper flakes and korean chili paste.  Infuse in oil until garlic is soft and spices are aromatic, about 5 minutes.  

3. Add warm beef stock, soy sauce and sugar and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 15-20 minutes until flavours are well incorporated.  

*It may be necessary to thicken sauce with corn starch to bring to desired consistency.  General rule of thumb is about 4 oz of corn starch slurry per litre of sauce. 


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergens:

Sesame 
Soy
Wheat
Gluten

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-36599" image="">1)  In a pot, mix tamarind paste and water and palm sugar.  Heat until sugar has dissolved.  Add korean chili paste.

2)  In a seperate pot, heat oil and cook garlic puree for about 10 minutes until it is no longer bitter to smell.

3)  In 20 L cambro, combine fish sauce, vinegar, and tamrind paste mixture and garlic.  Blend with immersion blender, thicken with corn starch slurry.  Label, Date, Refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38561" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic and lemongrass and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.  

2. Add red curry paste and tomato paste and saute until fragrant, about 1 minute more.
   
3. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

4. Season with fish sauce. 

5. Strain through fine chinois.  

6. Thicken with corn starch.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.steam beets in steamer till soft
3.peel under water once cool enough
4.cut into pieces and toss with remaining ingredients
5. spread on roasting pan
6. Roast 200C/400F 15 minute or till done
7.Hot hold in insert for service covered
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g

Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
serving dish

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45370" image="">Allergens:
sulphites, </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45371" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45373" image="">Allergens:
sesame, soy

Icons:
made with out gluten

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45374" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49176" image="">makes topping for 9 portions
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50858" image="">1.Sautee peppers &amp; onions until slightly soft and fragrent.

2. Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with mashed confit garlic. 

3. Evenly spread spinach then sauteed peppers &amp; onions.

4. Lay down sliced tomatoes.

5. Sprinkle feta cheese and olives.

6. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52214" image="">Important amounts from recipe
- Cloves - 5 pcs
- Allspice berries - 5 pcs
- Bay leaf - 1 ea

KEY INFO: the chocolate needs to be unsweetened.  If the chocoalte listed in the recipe is too sweet, please use unsweetend bakers chocolate.  Chef Brad can pick up if necessary. 


Instructions:
- Place the ground beef in a large pan, cover with approx 1 ltr of cold water.  Bring to a boil, stiring and breaking up the beef with a fork to a fine texture.
- Slowly boil until the meat is thoroughly cooked, about 30 min
- remove from heat and refridgerate the pan overnight
- Skim off the solid fat from the top of the pan and discard.
- place the beef mixture over medium heat, stir in the onions, tomato sauce, vinegar, worchestershire sauce, garlic, chocolate, chili powder, salt, cumin, cinnamon, cayenne, cloves, alspice berries and bay leaf.  
- Bring to a boil, reduce to a simmer
- cook, stirring occationally for 3 hours. Add water if necessary to prevent the chili from burning. 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-52215" image="">This will be a feature for Homecoming day on September 14th 

KEY ITEM - the cheese needs to be very finely shredded ( &quot;fluffy&quot; in texture ) I am unsure that the cheese listed here will be shredded finely enough.  We need to check this prior to the 14th and ensure that this will work otherwise we need to buy block cheddar and shread it ourselves on a box grator or the finest setting on the robocoup.

The hot dog listed in this recipe is Nathans - this MUST be the hotdog used for this recipe - no exceptions.

There is a possibility that Santa Ono will be coming to serve this at the location

This is actually an authentic Cincinati Chili recipe that Santa and Andrew Parr love. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-52217" image="">Note, 

the cracker is not saltines, it is meant to be Oyster crackers but they are not in MIL yet. 

The Cheddar cheese needs to be very fine angel hair style not thick grated, and piled high
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together EXCEPT green onions.

2. Add sliced green onions last.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53067" image="">Method:
- Pre Heat oven to 400f
- place sweet potato on baking sheet lined with parchment. prick skin with fork
- bake in oven until tender and soft
- remove from oven, split yam along the long edge with a knife, opening it up like a taco shell
- place rice/bean mixture into sweet potato
- top with cabbage
- top with salsa
- top with Guac
- top burrito with hot sauce if desired
- serve. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53081" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients into food processor or blender and puree on high speed until smooth creamy texture.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53084" image="">Dress bun top and bottom with tahini dressing.

Place cooked burger on bottom bun.

Top with smashed avocado &amp; tomato.

Top with citrus arugula.

Close bun, secure with pick.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53086" image="">in a med pot, add oil and increase heat to medium
stir in flour until a thin paste forms
stir in chili powder, garlic powder, cumin, onion powder &amp; cayenne until combined
cook for 2-3 min or until fragrant
stir in tomato paste until combined
stir in stock
wisk until smooth
bring to a simmer over med-low heat.  Simmer until thickened
adjust seasoning
hold for service. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53087" image="">Soak cashews in room temp water overnight ( or in boiling water for 1 hour min )
drain and rinse the soaked cashews
add the soaked cashews, cilantro, garlic, lime juice, avocado, sea salt, garlic powder, water into a Vitamix
puree until smooth and creamy
adjust seasoning
hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53088" image="">lightly oil a hotel pan, set aside
steam sweet potato until fork tender - do not overcook
in a large rondoux or tilt skillet heat oil over med heat, stir in onion and garlic, saute for 3 to 5 min. season with salt &amp; pepper
pre heat oven to 350f
add roasted red peppers, sun dried tomatoes, sweet potato, spinach and black beans into tild skillet with onion and garlic.
cook, stirring gently over med heat until spinach is wilted
add 90 ml of the enchilada sauce, lime juice, chili powder, cumin and salt, stir together
add 300 ml of enchilada sauce to bottom of the greased hotel pan, spread over bottom evenly
divide filling into 6 equal portions
place filling in tortilla and roll closed
place seam side down in dish
spread remaining enchilada sauce over top of filled tortillas
bake uncovered in 350f oven for 20 to 25 min ( until enchiladas are heated through
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53089" image="">Bake enchiladas as per recipe
remove from oven, place 1 enchilada on plate
garnish with drizzle of cashew lime cream sauce
top with chili flakes, diced avocado, green onion &amp; cilantro
serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place beets in a food processor, pulse 2-3 times.  DO NOT puree, there needs to be texture for the patties to hold together.

2. Fine dice onion.

3. Transfer beets to a large bowl, add other ingredients and stir to combine.  If texture is too mushy, add more bread crumbs until desired consistancy. NOTE the bread crumbs and quinoa will slowly absorb excess moisture over time.

4. Scale and shape burgers and place them on a parchment lined baking sheet. 

5. Bake patties in oven for 15 min, flip over and bake for a further 15 min. Hold for service OR

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:
patty portion weight 160 grams

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
</Recipes>
