<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Thinly slice up green onion.

2.  Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tahini, garlic, lemon juice, water and salt in large mixing vessel.  

2. Combine well with immersion blender.

3.  Add chopped parsley.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

NOTE: this is 2 boxes of tomatoes.

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice. Use the same dicing blade for the red onions.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26140" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Preheat oven to 400*F
2.In large mixing bowl, combine tomatillos, poblanos, jalapenos, garlic, oil and S+P.  Mix well to coat.
3.Place cooling rack over med high flame on burners.  Roast tomatillos, peppers and onions until charred all over.  Place on baking tray.  Add garlic.
4.Roast until peppers, onions and tomatillos are cooked through and soft enough to blitz in food processor, about 10-15 minutes.
5.In bowl of food processor, add roasted vegetables, cilantro leaves and stems, lime juice and salt.  Process until a unalagos consistency.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand. Add water, 1:1 with rice.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir to fluff and loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 200*F

2)  Combine all in large sauce pot.  Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming rapidly)

3)  Put pot in oven for 3 hours.  Strain, reserving garlic.  Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to cool.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

1. Preheat oven to 425*F

2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house rub. Mix well.

3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG RATHER THAN ROAST).

4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let cool.

5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

6. Check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix.  Blend well.  

2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26401" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat deepfryer to 350*F

2. Drain and dry chick peas very well.

3. Fry the chickpeas in the hot oil.

4. Place crispy chickpeas in mixing bowl and season with chickpea spice.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27405" image="">1)  Combine warm brown rice or quinoa and sweet potato hash with 30 ml of cumin lime dressing and season well.  Place in serving bowl.

2)  Top with tomatillo salsa, pico de gaillo, crispy corn tortilla strips, avocado, pickled jalapeno slices and lime wedge.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28994" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Combine all ingredients in Robocoupe.  Mix in baches if doing large amount and season to taste.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32800" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Drain chickpeas, lightly mash into a course texture using a food processor.  Do not blend into a smooth paste.

2. Add green onion, red pepper, cilantro, vegan mayo, garlic, ginger, turmeric, lemon juice and salt and pepper into chick peas.  Mix well to combine.

3. Adjust seasonong.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32809" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32886" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Curried chick pea.jpg">1.  Place appropriate amount of quinoa or brown rice as well as spinach and kale in mixing bowl.  Dress with cumin lime dressing, mix well and place in serving bowl.

2. Top with chickpea salad portion, papadum crackers and crispy chickpeas.

3. Place chutney in corner of bowl. Garnish with lemon wedge (1/8th of a lemon- please remove ALL seeds).</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35318" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: soy
Method:

1)  Combine kombu, ginger, garlic, star anise and water.  Bring to a boil, then remove from heat and allow to infuse for a few hours, or preferably overnight.  

2)  Add miso and bring back up to heat, ensuring to stir often until miso is disolved and broth is hot.  Add tofu and soy sauce.  Taste for seasoning. (80*C at least)

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35319" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Miso Dumpling Soup.jpg">1. Heat the broth, bak choy, gyoza, mushrooms and the noodles.

2. Assemble all of the ingredients in the bowl.

3. Garnish with green onion, radish and chili oil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35460" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Set aside cut tomatoes, chopped herbs and onions. 

2. Mix tabouleh with all remaining seasoning  

3. Gently fold in tomato and herbs

4. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35461" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Tabbouleh Bowl.jpg">1. Scoop appropriate amount of tabbouleh into mixing bowl.  Combine with dressing and mix well.  

2. Top with hummus, crispy chickpeas and grilled pita bread.
 
3. Garnish with seedless lemon wedge.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35689" image="">1)  Rinse sorghum grain VERY THROUGHLY!!! in china cap strainer and water.  You can make this easy by putting the strainer in a large soup pot and running the water over the sorghum until the water runs clear from the pot.

2)  Add water to rinsed sorghum and bring to a rapid simmer over medium high heat.  Stir every once in a while to make sure it isn&apos;t sticking to the pot.

3)  When the water comes to a rapid simmer, cover with aluminium and turn to very low heat.  Sorghum will take about 30-40 minutes to cook.  When Sorghum is finished it will have a pleasant, chewy consistency.

4)  Rinse under cold water until cool and store in appropriate vessel.  Label, Date, Refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36077" image="">METHOD
TURN OVEN TO 425
CUT SQUASH IN HALF LENGHTWISE SCOOP OUT SEED
LAY FLESHSIDE DOWN USING A FORK POKE HOLES 
COOK FOR 20-30 MINUTES TILL SLIGHTLY SOFT 
COOL AND USING A FORK SCOOP OUT THE SQUASH

ALLERGENS
- NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36566" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine all ingredients into large cambro.
2. Blend with the BIG BAD WAND until smooth.
3. Adjust seasoning to taste.

4. Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat pan up on medium heat and add oil
2. Drop pasta in small strainer cup into hot water bath
3. Add sauce to hot pans and mix gently with rubber spatula until the sauce is fully liquid and heated through
4. Lift pasta from the water alowing most of the pasta water to drain off- toss it into the heated sauce and bring up to a quick simmer
5. Toss the halved tomatoes into sauce fully incorporating them while trying to not have them loose their shape.
6. Taste the pasta with a spoon and season to taste
7. Spatula pasta into the correct bowl creating as much height as you can.
8. Ask the guest is they would like cheese added
9. Garnish with basil &amp; arugula - cheese (if requested)
10. Have a great day


Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44475" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Set up robot coupe slicer for 1/8&quot; slicing.  If you don&apos;t know how to set it up, ask Chef or a 1st Cook.
3. Chop the ends off of jalapenos and place in compost bin. Do not remove seeds.  Set up 4&quot; full hotel pan under the chute to catch the sliced jalapenos.
4. On the slowest speed, carfully drop peppers into the feed chute.  Do not mash a whole bunch in there, or else the cuts won&apos;t come out even.
5.  Repeat until production is done for the day.  Label, date, refrigerate, or hold cold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46870" image="">Allergens:

none
Icons:

n/a

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.zest the most outer layer of the lemon using a fine microplane
2. Set aside zested lemon to be used first/ juiced 
3. Use zest as close to recipe execution as possible but any excess is to be Stored, labeled and rotated correctly with any older product diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49176" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:
1. Preheat oven to 425F

2. Dice to 3/4&quot; and toss diced sweet potato in oil &amp; seasoning.

3. Cook 10-12 minutes until tender.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Slice cucumber lenghtwise on a mandolin, do not use the core, as it is too soft and the cucumbers will break.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50784" image="">1. Slice avocado and take pit out.
2.Scoop avocado meat in a small cambro.
3. Add in lime juice, salt and pepper.
4. Smash it and save in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52042" image="">Method:

combine cornstarch and salt, set aside

remove tofu from packaging and strain any liquid away.

cube tofu and toss through seasoned cornstarch.

shake away excess cornstarch and put tofu cibes in a a deep fryer to make a golden brown, and delicious crust.

remove from fryer, drain fry basket for a moment and turn out onto absorbent paper towel to whisk away excess oil.

use is associated recipes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54202" image="">1. Place warm brown rice in bottom of bowl.

2. Working around the bowl place small piles of the remaining ingredients.

3. Add sauce then fried egg on top.

4. Garnish with bean sprouts, green onion and sesame seeds.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54204" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Whisk all ingredients together to combine.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54343" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Trim and cut in half or in quarters as needed. 

Steam in an perforated hotel pan. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Small dice jalapenos and tomatoes. Mince cilantro.

2. In a bowl combine all ingredents. Mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. Check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56540" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

THIS DISH IS SERVED COLD.

1. Working in small batches squeeze out as much water as possible and lay out on sheet pans to dry.

2. Heat up oil and sautee off garlic, and remove from heat

3. Mix dry spinach with remaning ingredients and combine well.

4. Serve, or cool and label/ rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56921" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. core the pepper composting craps
2. cool, store, label, wrap and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56923" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Remove timatillios hood and compost as trim
2. toss lightly in oil and salt + pepper
3. roast at 250 for 25 minutes
4. cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58715" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In a saute pan/ rondo over medium/ high heat add butter, garlic and salt/ pepper.

2. When garlic is soft and fragrant (1 minute) add chopped mushrooms and cook until they are soft strirring occasionally.

3. When 90% cooked add whipping cream and reduce until mushrooms bind together slightly.

4. Turn off heat, add lemon zest, parsley and chopped thyme. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58716" image="">1. Grill bread to warm and toast slightly. Brush with olive oil.

2. Warm mushrooms slightly, adjust seasoning and pile on top of grilled bread.

3. Garnish with parsley.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61699" image="">Method
- melt butter in large skillet over med low heat
- add shallots, diced chillies, garlic 7 ginger - saute for approx 12 min until ingredients are soft - stirring occationally
- add soy sauces, sugar - mix thoroughly
- add black pepper, stir to combine
hold mixture hot for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61747" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.
2. Adjust seasoning.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61748" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-64880" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Using mandoine slice cucmbers into 0.5 cm discs.
2. Toss in salt and pace over a drip pan for 2-3 hours.
3. Meanwhie simmer remaining ingredients and cool completely.
4. Transfer cucumbers to a cambro and pour enough pickling liquid to cover. Place parchment or plastic wrap on top.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64881" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Soak cashews in cold water overnight OR pour boiing water over and let sit 1 hour. Drain and rinse.
2. Cut and steam potatoes and carrots until very soft. Reserve.
3. Working in batches in large robot coupe puree mixture until smooth.
NOTE: You may have to add a bit of water to get it smooth but you don&apos;t want it to be runny.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-64882" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Dessed jalapenos.

2. Combine all ingredients in a wide rondo, bring to a boil and simmer stirring occasionally until thick.

NOTE: It wil get thicker once cooled so don&apos;t reduce too much. You can put a small amount on a plate and wait a couple minutes for it too cool to check it&apos;s consistency.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64883" image="">1) Lightly season patty with salt &amp; pepper.

2) Place on oiled flattop and press down fairly hard with metal spatula. Make sure burger doesn&apos;t flatten wider than the bun. After 1 minute or so carefully flip burger and press down again.

3) Meanwhile toast bun then spread vegan mayo on both sides. Place tomato jam on bottom of bun.

4) Place seared &amp; cooked burger on top of tomato jam, top with vegan cheese sauce, 4 slices of the pickles and a leaf of iceburg lettuce.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-65898" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Ensure capers are very dry.
2. Fry in 350 F deep fryer in baskets untl crispy.
3. Drain and cool on paper towel lined pan.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-66068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. In a large pot combine water and beans, bring to a boil, turn down to a simmer.

2. Simmer for 25 minutes, checking to see if you need to add more water.

3. If needed strain, and cool.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68211" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE***
Preps used in this Product recipe:
Method:
1. Brush sourdough with olive oil and grill until toasted.
2. Spread greek yogurt across the entire surface of the bread. 
3. Place tomatoes on top.
4. Garnish with blasamic then capers then chopped chives.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68212" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Heat saute pan over medium high heat.
2. Add oil and garlic and cook garlic until fragrent.
3. Add tomatoes and toss to combine.
4. Pushing down break down roughly half of the tomatoes (you want two different textures). 
5. Cook out for about 2 minutes and season with salt.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
