<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="R-37171" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice. Use the same dicing blade for the red onions.

2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Egg
Milk

Method:

1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.  

2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.  

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26056" image="">1. Cut tomatoes in half horizontally. Squeeze romano oil on tomato and season with salt &amp; pepper

2. Grill seed side down for 2-3 minutes or until grill marks are visible and tomato begins to soften.

3.  Hold for service or serve immidiately.

1 portion (ea) of grilled tomato is 2 halves

Allergens:

No known priority allergens.

Average Roma tomato = 90 g
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50795" image="">1. Thaw Corn. 
2. Saute onion. Add corn and spices. Salt if needed..</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26333" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fine chop parsley and thyme.  Combine with lemon &amp; lime juice, mayo and seasoning.  

2. Taste for seasoning and adjust if necessary.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26328" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In appropriate sized sauce pan, combine rice vinegar, salt, sugar, and simmer until salt and sugar are dissolved.  Add thai chilis and ginger, turn off heat and allow mixture to cool to room temperature.

2)  Meanwhile, add carrot and daikon radish to 4L cambro container.  Add room temp pickling solution, and wiegh down vegetables with parchment to keep them submerged.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.  Vegetables are best if left to pickle for at least 24 hours.

Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Dairy
Sulphites
Method:

1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26047" image="">1. Add eggs to appropriate cooking vessel
2. Cover with cold water by 1 inch
3. Bring to boil slowly over medium heat. Once boil is reached, remove from heat, cover and let sit for 12 minutes
4. Run eggs under cold water until cool
5. Place in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Alternatively, eggs can be made in rationale oven by steaming on 100% steam for 13 minutes.  Ensure to ice bath to bring down temperature and to stop the eggs from overcooking.

Allergens:

Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26127" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Tie bay leaf, thyme and rosemary with butchers string.

2. Combine beef stock, garlic cloves and herb bundle. Bring to a simmer. 

3. Simmer about 20 minutes. Strain stock and keep warm.

4. Add cornstarch slurry to stock while whisking until thickened.

5. Season to taste with salt, pepper and vinegar.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26063" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine half of blueberries and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the blueberries and heat until no longer frozen but still firm, about 5-8 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine soy sauce, thai chili&apos;s, sugar, cilantro, lime juice and garlic puree.  Whisk well until sugar is fully dissolved.  

2. Dice tofu into 1-1.25&quot; cubes and add to marinade.  Allow to marinate for at least 2 hours in appropriate vessel. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam rice.

2. Once rice is out of the steamer add all ingredients - oil, lime juice &amp; spice mix - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

3. When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1)  Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven.  Steam potatoes until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20 minutes.

2)  Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool.  Put on speed racks.  

3)  IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks.  Reserve for making classic potato salad.---- If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

4)  For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4 minutes.  Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


Allergens:

No known priority allergens.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279



1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
(2 step program)
1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

3)  Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully crack egg onto dish.  Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26065" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 

Mustard

Method:

1. Combine mayo, ketchup, mustard, relish, pureed shallot, salt &amp; pepper in a mixing bowl. Combine well.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat up oil in large sauce pot over medium low heat.  

2. Add garlic and and gently cook for 10 minutes.  That&apos;s right, 10 minutes.  Then add ginger puree and continue gently cooking for another 5-10 minutes. Stir it alot to make sure it doesn&apos;t burn, but really cook it out. 

3. Add kecap manis and rice vinegar.  Bring to a simmer for 10-15 minutes over medium heat.  Add corn starch slurry and simmer for another 5 minutes until thick.

4. Do not strain.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28249" image="">1)  Season and grill beef patty until well done (71*C).  

2)  While patty is grilling,toast on grill and add thunderbird sauce to both sides of bun and lettuce to the bottom portion of bun.

3)  Place cooked beef patty on top of lettuce and close.  Top with pickle and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28250" image="">1)  Follow same procedure as classic beef burger, but add cheese to the patty when it is 90% cooked.  Top with pickle spear and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28251" image="">1)  Season and grill chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked.

2)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and garnish with guacamole and lemon herb aioli.  Top cooked chicken breast with cheese until melted.

3) Add tomato, cooked bacon and citrus arugula.

4) Close bun and top with pickle skewer.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28254" image="">1)  Spread butter on outside of sourdough and put butter side down on griddle.  While still on the griddle, put cheeses on both sides of bread.  

2) Warm oven dried tomatoes and place them over entire surface area of sandwich.

3) Close sandwich when cheese begins to melt.  Continue grilling until bread is golden brown and cheese in completely melted.

4) Cut in half from corner to corner.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28280" image="">Using a #12 scoop, portion out 1 portion of eggs, one portion of potatoes and 2 halves of grilled tomato.  lightly dress arugula with cirus oil and a pinch of S+P.  Serve Immediately.

10 grams of bacon = 2 cooked slices

breakfast comes with choice of bacon (2pc) or sausage(1pc)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28281" image="">1)  Crack egg on flat top and grill.  Meanwhile, toast bun and spread evenly with mayo.  flip egg to cook over easy and place on bottom of bun.  Top with bacon, cheddar, and citrus arugula and close bun.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28285" image="">1)  Combine pancake mix and water throughly.  Reserve for service.

Allergens:  

Gluten
Wheat
Gluten
Soy 
Dairy
Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28286" image="">1)  Grab your #12 scoop.  Grab scrambled eggs from hot holding vessel.  Put on plate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28288" image="">1)  Cook sausage in 350*F oven until probe thermometer reaches 71*C.  Hold for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28293" image="">Allergens:
Gluten, Wheat, Mustard, Soy, Egg

Icons:
N/A


1)  Fry chicken strips according to package directions.  Double check that they are fully cooked by using a probe thermometer and taking the temperature.  Chicken strip should register at least 70*C to ensure it is well done.  Hold for service in food warmer.

2)  Serve with choice of sauce.

*Recipe assumes 2.0 oz avg. weight per chicken strip.  4 per order.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28301" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-30406" image="">- Pre-heat oven to 350
- bake 20-25 minutes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33911" image="">1)  Prepare and Ice bath

2)  Add green beans to perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for 2-3 minutes.  Immidiately put into ice bath.  Once cooled, drain well and store for service.

3)  Just prior to service quickly steam green beans and toss with s&amp;p mix.  Taste for seasoning and hold for service.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-34864" image="">
Combine salad greens with ranch dressing.  Plate on large square plate.

Top with sliced cherry tomato, cucumber, egg, avocado slices, cheese, bacon and turkey in seperate piles on top of greens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35714" image="">1)  Dredge chicken breast in cajun spice and grill until 50% cooked and starting to char and blacken.  Put in oven until cooked through.  

2)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill and dress bottom of bun with mayonnaise, lettuce, red onion, and tomato.  Put chicken back on grill and top with cheese. Place under steamer lid to reheat chicken and melt cheese, about 2 minutes.

3)  Place on top of bottom bun with toppings and close bun.  Garnish with dill pickle and serve immidiately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35772" image="">1) Produce as per prep recipe.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28291" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35270" image="">1)  Place beef patty on grill.  Ensure that it is cooked well done (above 71*C)

2)    Place sauted mushrooms on burger patty, then top with cheese.  Place steamer lid on top of patty and steam until cheese is melted and mushrooms are warm.

3)  Meanwhile, garnish bun with garlic mayo on both sides and lettuce on bottom half of burger.  

4)  Top beef patty with bacon and place lettuce on bottom half of bun.  Garnish with pickle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50692" image="">Toss diced tofu with seasoned cornstarch and fry until golden brown. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36075" image="">1)  Combine all well.  Allow to marinate for at least an hour, and up to 8.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Beef Vindaloo
Chickpea Vindaloo

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Over medium/ low heat in large rondeau, add oil, cinnamon and onions and cook till nearly carmalized and golden brown.

2)  Add ginger, garlic, seeded jalapenos and cook until peppers are soft.

3) Add tomato paste and cook, stirring often until it is a deep, dark brown.

4) Add ground dry spices and vindaloo paste and cook for 10 minutes, or until spice is cooked out. Taste to ensure that the spices are cooked out. 

5)  Add water, diced tomatoes and juice, salt, lemon juice and brown sugar.  Bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  

6)  Remove from heat, remove cinnamon sticks.  Puree with immersion blender. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35015" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-35014" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. cook fries crispy
2.season and toss in stainless boewl
3.place portiuon in bowl and serve
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35271" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.  

2. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50746" image="">1) Combine all ingredients in a pot, heat at medium until sugar dissolves. Then remove from heat.

2) Cool fully before using as marinade or if using later, store in appropriate sized vessel, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Cut lemons in quarters. Crush garlic and slice shallots.

2)  Combine all except chicken breast.  Stir well to combine.

3)  In a non-reactive container (plastic) add chicken.  Add marinade and JUST ENOUGH OIL to COAT not COVER the chicken breasts and mix well.  Allow to marinate for 8 hours or overnight.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37093" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Spaghetti.jpg">1)  Blanch cooked pasta in hot water until it is hot throughout.  Place hot pasta in serving bowl.

2)  Top with 5 meatballs and 6 fl. oz of tomato sauce.

3)  Garnish with parmesan cheese and parsley.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35517" image="">1)  Place all ingredients in mixing bowl and combine well.

Allergens:

Milk/Dairy
Egg
Soy
Gluten
Wheat</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35273" image="">1) Drain liquid from pickles.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36078" image="">1)  Stir fry marinated vindaloo beef until well done.  Add vindaloo sauce and combine well.  Bring to a simmer.  Add fried potatoes and hold for service.

2)  When an order is placed, put appropriate amount of basmati rice in serving bowl and top with vindaloo beef and potato mixture.  

3)  Top with yogurt, cilantro and crispy papadum.  Serve immediately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Take off stems of jalapenos.  Remove pits of avocado and scoop flesh from skin.  Place all ingredients except oil in 20 L cambro container.  

2)  Blend well with immersion blender until a smooth puree consistency is reached.  

3)  Slowly begin adding oil, a little at a time until all oil has been added.  Taste for seasonining.


-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58385" image="">1. Process veg: dice cucumber 
Julienne romaine. 
Slice green onions to bias.
Half grape tomatoes.

2.slice avocado.

3. Cook eggs, allow to cool and peel and cut into quarters

4. Toss romaine with dressing.

5. Put dressed romaine on a plate. In rows top with, hardboiled eggs, blue cheese, avocado and green onions.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29170" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Make apple cider dressing as per recipe.

2)  Shred cabbages in robot coupe food processor.

3) Pulse cleaned kale in robot coupe until broken down.

4)  Combine shredded cabbages, kale and chopped cilantro.  Mix well with dressing.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28759" image="">1) Place Turkey in 275F oven for approximately 4 hours. Internal temperature should be 165F.

2) Cool completely before slicing.

3) Slice on the meat slicer on a 2.5 setting</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26050" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine  dijon, herbs, shallots, garlic, sriracha, butter milk, salt and peppercorn in a 20L container, puree with a hand blander.

2. Combine greek yougurt &amp; sour cream . Mix thoroughly. Dressing should be thick but pourable.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-30041" image="">57 g = 2 strips of bacon. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-63018" image="">1. Dress top &amp; bottom of toasted bun with tahini dressing.

2. Place cooked burger in.

3. Top with amashed avocado, tomato &amp; citrus arugula.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50347" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Peel, core and dice the apple.
 
2)  In a big mixing bowl, add all the ingredients and whisk until all the ingredients incorporate. Reserve for service.

3) Transfer to aproppriate container, label, date and store in the fridge.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35713" image="">1)  Dredge Chicken Breast in house rub.  

2)  Placed dredged breast on parchment lined baking sheet.

3)  Repeat until production for the day is complete.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35272" image="">1) Remove and discard stem, cut letuce in quarters, then shave off thin strips.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.

Average weight of a head of Iceberg is 470g with 10% yield loss for core and outer leaves. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43746" image="">1) Add dressing to greens, cucumber, carrot, tomatoes, red pepper and mix well. Use just enough dressing to coat the salad.

2) Top with sunflower seeds and radish. Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50348" image="">1) In a flat top, add oil and 4oz for each pancake.

2) Cook about 2 minutes each side.

3) Served with apple compot and coconut whip.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50349" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.In a big mixing bowl, add all the DRY ingredients and whisk until everything is combined well. Add water and continue mix until the mixture incorporate well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.




2) Storage in appropriate container, label ,date and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50350" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Put bowl of stand mixer in freezer for about 5 minutes to ensure it&apos;s cool.

2. Add whipping cream to bowl of stand mixer with whisk attachment. Once cream begins to thicken, add icing sugar, vanilla and cinnamon. Continue to whip until stiff.

3. Can be held for 24 - 36 hours or until it begins to break.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50351" image="">1) In a flat top, add oil and 4oz for each pancake.

2) Cook about 2 minutes each side.

3) Served with maple syrup and cinnamon chantilly.





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50368" image="">1) Prepare egg.

2) Slice thick end of multigrain croissant open, spread mayo on bottom.

2) Toss arugula with citrus oil and salt and pepper, place in bun, top with egg, bacon and cheese, warm on flat top till cheese is melted.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50372" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1) Split pork loin in to quarters lengthwise. Should have 4 tube like pieces. In shallow pan or bag marinate pork for 24 hours making sure it&apos;s fully covered by the marinade.

2) Remove from marinade and place on a lined baking sheet on top of a wire rack. 

3) Roast pork at 425F atop a wire racks on a tin foil lined sheet pan until an internal temp of 144F is achieved. Reserve leftover maridande to recude until proper consistency to coat the cooked meat is reached.

3) Allow the meat to rest. Coat with reduction as needed 

4) Reserve excess marinade reduce in a pot until thick and syurupy. Cube up pork in to 1/4&quot; pieces and toss with reduced marinade to add flavour and moisture back in.

Portioning: 115g

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50504" image="">1) Place shaved beef on flat top and cook until starting to brown, add caramelized onion, and sauteed peppers.

2) On bottom piece of baguette, spread garlic mayo, place warmed up beef, onions and peppers. Break the cheddar, and provalone slices in half, and top filling with alternating halves of cheddar and provalone to cover top.

3) Place top of baguette on flat top, crust side down, until it&apos;s warm and starting to get crispy, but not hard.

4) Place place bottom piece with all fillings and cheese on parchment lined flash pan, put in deck oven for 2-3 minutes or until cheese is fully melted.

5) Combine top and bottom of sandwich, cut on a bias and serve.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50494" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto and half of the mozza cheese, then place zuchinni, and torn pieces of proscuitto evenly across flatbread.

2) Sprinkle remaining half of mozza cheese over top.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked place arugula then drizzle balsamic reduction over top.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

Slice Proscuitto using #2.5 slicer.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50501" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Shrimp Pasta.jpg">1. Slice drained sundried tomatoes into long thin strips about 1/4 lenghtwise.

2. Place pasta portion in basket in hot water pot to reheat pasta.  Drain well, removing any excess water from pasta, and place in mixing bowl. 

3. Add 4oz ladle of pesto, sundried tomatoes, shrimp, arugula and salt &amp; pepper to the spaghetti and mix well with tongs to coat all pasta with sauce. You may have to add a small splash of the pasta water to loosen.

4. Place high in serving bowl placing some of the ingredients on top of pasta and top with parmesan cheese.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50506" image="">1) Cut peppers in half, remove stem, seeds, and white rib/membrain. Slice peppers in to 1/8&quot; julien pieces.

2) In a large pan, heat oil on high, add peppers and season. Cook until tender and starting to brown.

3) Cool spread out on bakeing sheet. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50590" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread pesto, caramelized onion.

3. Spread crumbled goat cheese, half sliced cherry tomatoes.

4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until cherry tomatoes are fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

5. Take out of oven.

7. Spread arugula and drizzle with balsamic glaze.

8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50598" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Put bowl of stand mixer in freezer for about 5 minutes to ensure it&apos;s cool.

2. Add whipping cream to bowl of stand mixer with whisk attachment. Once cream begins to thicken, add icing sugar and lemon zest. Continue to whip until stiff. DO NOT OVERMIX.

3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

4. Can be held for 24 - 36 hours or until it begins to break.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46833" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50683" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix sugar, vinegar and chili in a pot and bring to a simmer until sugar dissolves.

2. Julienne carrots, place in a bowl and mix well with cold liquid.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50686" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Remove the cabbage core and shred cabbage finely.

2) Place water, vinegar, and sugar in a pot and warm until the sugar is dissolved, add salt, cool completely then pour over the cabbage.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50691" image="">Medium heat mixed well.

Ensure that the tofu has been fried as per preceeding sub recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50739" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine half of apples and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the apples and heat until about 8-10 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50894" image="">1) Add dressing to greens and mix well.

2) Top with cucumber, carrots, sunflower seeds, tomatoes, radish, red pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45231" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50700" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Teriyaki Tofu Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place rice in bowl and top with tofu/sauce mixture, zucchini.

2. Top with all vegetable ingredients in quadrants around the bowl. (Mushroom, cabbage, carrots, cucumber are served cold)

3. Garnish with sliced green onion.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:
sauce: 2oz ladel
rice: 1.5 white scoop
cabbage: yellow scoop
zucchini: yellow scoop
teriyaki: white scoop
mushroom: yellow scoop


Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-45255" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat

Icons:
N/A

Method:
 70 pcs average per case

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44601" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Toast and grind the cumin &amp; coriander.

2. Add remaining ingredients into large robot coupe with spatula attachement and puree to a smooth paste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


Prep:

- Process all ingredients into a size that will fit easily and not cause problems in the Vitamix. Also, find the PLUNGER for the Vitamix, as you will not be able to do this job without it.

- The Coconut Milk in this recipe will be used to loosen then process of Puree-ing the Green Curry Base Paste. Use Water only if necessary.

- Once processed ingredients and Coconut Milk are ready to go, Vitamix all of these ingredients into a paste. 

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

***This can be made in large batches, and frozen for future use if vac-packed. A Green Curry &quot;Base&quot; recipe only contains 4.62Kg of this base (HALF), to the rest of its ingredients.

Any questions? - Ask Chef...

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51828" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53081" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients into food processor or blender and puree on high speed until smooth creamy texture.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53084" image="">Portion burgers to 140g.

Dress bun top and bottom with tahini dressing.

Place cooked burger on bottom bun.

Top with smashed avocado &amp; tomato.

Top with citrus arugula.

Close bun, secure with pick.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54295" image="">1) Dry jalapenos well on a large tray with paper towel.

2) Combine corn starch and spices and mix evenly.

3) Coat jalapeno evenly in corn starch mixture.

4)  Fry in batches without baskets, until crispy.

5) Remove from oil, shake to drain oil and season immediately on a paper towel lines sheet pan. If you wait to long after they come out of the fryer the salt will not stick.

6) Do not overcrowd once they are out of the fryer or they will turn soggy.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55141" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Ensure corn is defrosted and all excess water removed.

2. In a mixing bowl combine corn, onion, oil, chili powder and salt and pepper and mix evenly.

3. In a 450*F oven cook until corn takes on some dark colour and is slightly caramalized.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55142" image="">1) Place greens, cabbage, beans, peppers, charred corn and tomatoes in mixing bowl.

2) Add dressing and GENTLY toss to combine ensuring all ingredients are coated in dressing.

3) Plate greens leaving some of the vegetables to garnish top of salad.

4) Finish top of salad with radish slices, tortilla strips, pumpkin seeds and feta.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56337" image="">1) Spread pesto evenly over entire area of flatbread.

2) Add artichokes, olives, sundried tomatoes then goat cheese.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Take it off from oven and evenly spread arugula on top and balsamic reduction.

5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54296" image="">1) Fully cook the seasoned burger patty.

2) Spread chipotle mayo on top and bottom of toasted bun add smashed avocado then iceburge lettuce on bottom.

3) Place burger patty on flat top, top with cheese and let it melt so it&apos;s a bit gooey and place on lettuce. 

4) Add sliced tomato then deep fried jalapenos place top bun on, skewer with bamboo toothpick and garnish with pickle spear. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56457" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1) Puree pickled jalapenos, lime juice and cilantro.

2) Mix well with mayonnaise.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56458" image="">1. Cod takes 10 minutes to deep fry from frozen.

2. Toast bun, spread mayo on both sides. 

3. Place cooked cod piece on bun, top with slaw and pickled red onions.

4. Close and add skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56490" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Mix all marinade ingredients ensuring sugar gets dissolved.

2) Add chicken thighs and marinade 12-24 hours.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56460" image="">1)  Grill beef patty to well done (70*C)

2)  Meanwhile, run bun through toaster and spread top and bottom with wasabi mayo.  When patty is nearly cooked through, brush with teriyaki sauce.

3) Place glazed burger on bottom bun, add pickled ginger and sprouts. Add top bun and skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56454" image="">1)  Grill seasoned chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked. 

2) Grill pineapple on both sides.

3) Brush chicken and pineapple on both sides with Teriyaki sauce and quickly glaze on grill. Do not leave on grill too long or sauce will burn. 

4) Place pineapple on chicken, then cheese and melt.

5)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and spread mayo on both sides.

6) Place lettuce, tomato and onion on bottom bun.

7) Place chicken and pineapple on top, close bun and skewer.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Preheat oven to 300F (low fan)

2) Cut roma tomatoes in half LENGTHWISE.

3) Gently toss with remaining ingredients.

4) Place cut side up on a wire rack over a baking sheet, place in oven for  2 hours 30 minutes.

5) Tomatoes should be dried but have some moisture remaining.

6) Do not store more than 2 high so tomatoes do not get crushed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Heat oil in sauce pot over medium heat. Add chopped shallot, garlic and lemongrass and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.  Add yellow curry paste and saute until fragrant, about 1 minute more.
   
2. Add coconut milk, lime leaves and sugar and bring to a simmer.  Allow to simmer for 10 minutes.  Strain through fine chinois. Add fish sauce and adjust seasoning. 
3. Thicken with corn starch.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56451" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Corn Flake French Toast.jpg">1. Preheat grill to 350*F. 

2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up.  Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg mixture then in corn flakes and put on griddle.  Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm throughout.

3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner.  Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.

4. NOTE: corn flakes need to be pulsed so they are small enough to stick evenly to the bread but retain some texture</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fill kettle with ROOM TEMPERATURE water. Do Not tutnr the kettle on.
2. Place the noodles into the water fully submerging the noodles. Mix the noodles around until they have loosened up and move freely and un-forzen
3. Noodles should be firm but not crispy.
4. Remove from kettle and let drain.
5. Lightly oil the noddles and store them labeled and rotated correctly.
6. Noodles are to be cook &quot;a-la-minute&quot; on the station as needed 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50803" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Assemble all the ingredients.

2. Char jalapenos on the grill until cooked.

3. Clean and de-seed the jalapenos.

4. Blitz jalapeno, lemon juice, salt/pepper in vitamix.

5. Mix honey, jalapeno mixture and mayo.

6. Taste and adjust as needed

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54583" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE


Grill the chicken breast with some of the BBQ rub spice and glaze with BBQ sauce when it is nearly done.

Toast the bun and sauce the top bun, put the caramelized onions on the bottom bun. 

Place the BBQ chicken breast on the bottom bun and top it with the lettuce and tomato. 

Place the lid on the bun and serve the pickle on the side.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50543" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut tomato in half
2.Toss in all the remaning ingredients
3.Drain the excess liquid

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: Muffaleta

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out all ingredients.

2. In a Robot Coupe add all ingredents and pulse until combined and coarse/slightly chunky.

3. DO NOT PUREE UNTILL SMOOTH this should be a slightly chunky spread with evident pieces of olive and such.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

2. Add red onions. 

3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50662" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
pickle|onion red

Allergens: 
Method:

1.  Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53848" image="">1. Combine Romaine and dressing in mixing bowl 

2. Garnish top with croutons and parm.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34843" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine soy sauce and brown sugar.  Simmer until liquid becomes syrupy (needs to thicken). 

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57191" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. discard unsavoury outer leaves

2.Remove core and discard

3. Cut and trim lettuce as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash Tomato in cold water
2.Cut in half Lenght wise
3.Container label fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
knife, cutting board, storage container
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix all ingredients together EXCEPT green onions.

2. Add sliced green onions last.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46864" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Be sure to make shred from other Iceberg lettuce preps
3. evenly slice lettuce 3 mm thick
4. Cover with wet brown paper towel to stop oxidization   

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and stirring.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26628" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix, heat to a boil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51217" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Prep all of the prep recipes in advance.

Layer all of  the ingredients in a tortilla wrap in the proportions indicated.

Wrap up tightly.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.Small dice jalapenos and tomatoes. Mince cilantro.

2. In a bowl combine all ingredents. Mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. Check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41574" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. PRE-SOAK Beans overnight!
   - 2 X 20L CAMBRO Containers
   - HALF of the Beans in Each
   - Filled with 12L of Water Each

2. Drain beans from their hydration liquid. Your cooking water should be different from your soaking water.

3. Using the small steam kettle, cook beans slowly in 20 extra liters of water. They should be good to start at 250F.

4. Cook the beans until they are soft, but not decomposing. During the cooking process it is important to skim off the foamy protein that will accumulate at the surface of the cooking beans&apos; water - this, if unchecked, will lead to a poor bitter taste and a lesser shelf life for the beans themselves.

5. While the beans are cooking, saute your onions in oil, until dark brown. Caramelize them as far as they will go, and then add cumin and garlic. Saute cumin and garlic for 5 minutes, and then take off heat.

6. Turn off steam kettle when the beans are cooked, and let beans sit. Take 4L of the cooking water, and set aside.

7. Drain beans, and then transfer them into a neutral container greater than 40L in volume. Get the large Immersion Blender.

8. Add the onion mixture with the garlic and cumin, as well as half of the salt, and half of the brown sugar. The remaining halves - set aside, and use to SEASON TO TASTE. 

9. With the Immersion Blender, blend about 4L of the bean mixture into a puree - and then add back into the rest of the beans, and mix. Add reserve liquid from the cooking, until you get - not a soup - beans with a puree of more beans.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44592" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather ingredients
2. Bake on tray 190C 375F 20 minutes or till done
3. Strain fat then crumble
4. Place in container once cold, label and fridge 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:Baking sheet collandier container 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44024" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place wrap on plate and put salad inside.

2. Add hot chorizo.

3. Eggs and sauce.

4. Wrap and serve.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34892" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Scale out ingredients.

2. In a sauce pot combine water and buuter and bring to a simmer, Add powder and stir for a minute.

3. Place in container and hold for service in a WARM place.
 
Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:scale pot whisk bowl container</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55155" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
2. Build sandwich to spec.

-store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51134" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients.
2. Put egg into a perforated pan.
3. Cook in steamer for 9-10 min.
4. Plunge eggs in a ice bath right away.
 

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: perfforated hotel pan, ice bath

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55419" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools.
2. Sweat garlic, shallot, lemon grass in oil.
3. Add curry paste and cook until encorperated.
4. Add coconut milk and simmer for 15 minutes.
5. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat well
3.Bake on sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46076" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51133" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients
2. Be sure that bacon bits are cut ahead of time, and eggs are half&apos;d ahead of time
3.  

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50301" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
Slanted bowl</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.HEAT FLAT TOP AND HAVE FLAT SPATULA AND RESTING TRAY READY
2.LIGHTLY OIL FLATOP
3.CRACK EGG ONTO FLAT TOP
4.SEASON
5.COOK UNTIL WHITES FULLY CONGEALED 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:1 egg

Utensils needed:

PROCESS:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Give a rough chop and keep the seeds

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44510" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine everything and mix thoroughly.
2. Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8202" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.mix together and label store with rest of spices

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Method:
1.Combine ingredents up to 3 days in advance.
-store, label and rotate

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7736" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1.Weigh quinoa into 4&quot; hotel pan
2.wash and drain
3.add water or veg stock
4. place in steamer and steam 20 mintues
5. once cooked fork wrap and place in warmer for service

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44499" image="">Allergen:

wheat, egg, gluten

Icon:

vegetarian</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56489" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Make pancakes.

2. Top w compote then chantilly.

3. Serve.


Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57405" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54875" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portion of crispy fries in bowl and top with cheese.

2. Pour portion of gravy over top of cheese and fries.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57461" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Mix well

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-40584" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:
Tacos
Bowls

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.slice shallot and dredge in potato starch mix
3.Shake off excess in a strainer
4.Fry once at 310 until bubbles stop and shallot float
5. remove from and let cool on a resting rack turning the fryer up to 350 when they are out
6. whenthey are cool, re-fry at 350 until golden brown
7.place on paper towel to absorb excess oil
8.place in container on a service towel, label and use for TWO DAYS ONLY 

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place all ingredients in a large pot.

2. Bring to a simmer and thicken with a corn starch slurry

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58270" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1) Place greens, cabbage, beans, peppers, charred corn and tomatoes in mixing bowl.

2) Add dressing and GENTLY toss to combine ensuring all ingredients are coated in dressing.

3) Plate greens leaving some of the vegetables to garnish top of salad.

4) Finish top of salad with radish slices, tortilla strips, pumpkin seeds and feta.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47541" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED
STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.blend together and use
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58362" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Smash black peppercorns slightly.  

2)  Combine water, crushed black pepeprcorns, bay leaf, sugar, garlic cloves, onion, rosemary, thyme, salt and lemon (make sure to give the lemons a good squeeze before throwing in the mix)

3)  Bring brine to a boil and stir to ensure that salt and sugar are dissolved.  Put mixture in blast chiller to cool.

4)  When brine has cooled COMPLETELY, add turkey breast.  Ensure breasts stay in brine by weighing them down with a tray from the servery.  

5)  Allow breast to brine for 6 hours.

6)  Roast in 325*F oven until browned and probe thermometer reaches 70*C (158*F).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.steam beets in steamer till soft
3.peel under water once cool enough
4.cut into pieces and toss with remaining ingredients
5. spread on roasting pan
6. Roast 200C/400F 15 minute or till done
7.Hot hold in insert for service covered
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g

Utensils needed:cutting board steamer pan roasting pan
serving dish

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56491" image="">1. Spread mayo on both sides of baguette.

2. Place cooked chicken, cucumber, pickled veg, sliced jalepenos then cilanrto (in that order).

PLEASE ENSURE JALAPENOS ARE VERY THINLY SLICED.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58450" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Take chicken out of marinade and lay it in a single layer on parchemnt lined baking sheets.

2. Place in a 375F oven and cook until internal temperature reaches 165F

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Slice strawberries when they are partially frozen(rough is fine) and place in suitable sized pot.

2. Add remaining ingredients except slurry. Bring to a boil.

3. Add slurry to thicken and remove from heat.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44506" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Halve the avocado and carefully remove the pit
3.  Slice into desired sizes
4. Toss in lemon juice to prevent oxydation

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 1 portion is 1/4 avocado

Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, bowl insert, mesuring cups
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52999" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU** Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.cut bacon into 4 cmx 2cm x 2cm strips
2. Heat pot to medium heat and add bacon
3. Stir to avoid burning while letting pieces fully render out 
4. Drain in chinoiseand cool reserving the fast
5. label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60387" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, lemongrass and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

2. Add mushrooms and rice, sautee 1 minute

3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

4. Sfter 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. 

5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-60537" image="">
Combine salad greens with ranch dressing.  Plate into small side salad bowl.

Top with sliced cherry tomato, cucumber, egg, avocado slices, cheese,(no bacon or ham!) on top of greens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47361" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients EXCEPT oil in a cambro.

2. Blend with immersion blender, then slowly drizzle in oil to form an emulsion.

3. Taste for seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56796" image="">PREP RECIPE

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.

label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61253" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place beets in a food processor, pulse 2-3 times.  DO NOT puree, there needs to be texture for the patties to hold together.

2. Fine dice onion.

3. Transfer beets to a large bowl, add other ingredients and stir to combine.  If texture is too mushy, add more bread crumbs until desired consistancy. NOTE the bread crumbs and quinoa will slowly absorb excess moisture over time.

4. Scale and shape burgers and place them on a parchment lined baking sheet. 

5. Bake patties in oven for 15 min, flip over and bake for a further 15 min. Hold for service OR

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:
patty portion weight 160 grams

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7444" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46545" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2. butterfly breasts if needed
3.lay out on baking sheet
4.Sprinkle cajun seasoning evenly
5.bake in oven 15 minutes or till done
6.cool and place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61685" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Place coconut oil in a rondo over medium heat.
2. Once warm add curry paste and sweat until fragrant, stirring so paste does not burn (3-4 minutes). You want to draw out as much flavour as possible in this step.
3. Add coconut milk, lime leaves (no stems) and bring to a simmer.
4. Simmer until desired consistency is reached.
5. Remove from heat, add fish sauce &amp; palm sugar and adjust seasoning. Remove lime leaves.
6. Curry should be spicy/ sweet/ salty &amp; slighty sour.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61687" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix well.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61742" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto.

2) Evenly lay shrimp, tomatoes and parmesan. Sprinkle chili flakes.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Cut into 4 even pieces, garnish with arugula, squeeze fresh lemon and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61779" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

2) Evenly lay cooked mushrooms over pesto.

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of flatbread is golden brown.

4) Once cooked take out from oven.

5) Lay arugula over.

7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-64945" image=""/>
</Recipes>
