<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-26136" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

Add  red onions. 

Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible

Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13683" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Dice peppers

Stirfry quickly in a very hot pan with oil: onions, celery and bell peppers

Chop parsley

Squeeze liquid from crab meat and check for shell fragments

Mix all ingredients together including the eggs, mayo and breadcrumbs

Shape into 2 oz (60g) cakes

Makes approximately 40 pieces

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47228" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-8196" image="">ALLERGEN: DAIRY

1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes. 

4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23950" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook and drain the bacon, and chop it. 

Caramelize the onions in a small amount of the bacon fat with the brown sugar. 

Once the onions are caramelized, add the chopped bacon, coffee, vinegar, rosemary and balck peppers and simmer to reduce to jam consistency.

Taste and add salt only if neccessary to balance the flavours. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Mince mint

2. Mix all ingredents thuroughly

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26628" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix, heat to a boil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10502" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26770" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in :Samosa

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:


1. Scale out all ingredents. Combine everything in a pot. 
Bring to a boil, reduce heat to a simmer. 

2. Cook out for 20-30 minutes or until sauce like consistency is reached and flavours have melded together.

3. Taste for seasoning and balance. Adjust if needed

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33559" image="">
METHOD:

Prep:

- This recipe should take 2 days - no more, no less, however, the curing process can be elongated, depending on time, to 3-4 days.

- TO CURE: Take Sesame Oil, Brown Sugar, and Salt - and rub the Pork Belly down thoroughly. Place in a Hotel Pan, SKIN SIDE DOWN, and let the sugar and salt begin drawing out moisture and breaking down the outside of the Belly. IMPORTANT: in the morning, when you come in for your shift the next day - TURN THE PORK BELLY OVER, SO THAT THE SKIN SIDE IS UP AND OPEN TO THE AIR. 

- Pre-Heat the Convection Oven to 325F/180C.

- Cover Pork Belly with remaining ingredients, and roast for 25 minutes. Then, turn the oven to 425F, and finish for and extra 10-15 minutes. 

- Once Pork Belly is cool, remove its skin layer and discard. Cut the meat, and prepare for next steps.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27300" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Bring a large pot of salted water to a hard boil. Gently place pergogies into boing water (perogies can be cooked from frozen). Cook for 3-5 minutes ( you will know they are done when they satrt floating to the top. Cautious not to over cook them as they will burst. Better to undercook slightly as they will be cooked again when they get fried!  Or use the steamer. Reserve for service.

2. Once ready for service; add a small amount of oil to a saute pan, heat pan over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add blanched(boiled) perogies to pan and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through.

3. PLATING; place the fried brussel sprouts in the centre of the plate, arange the perogies on top and around the sprouts; Each plate gets 240g of perogy (8pieces) 
4. Garnish with green onion. sauerkraut and sour cream are served on the side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37870" image="">ALLERGEN
SULPHITE

Method:

- In oil, sautee onion, garlic and mushrooms
- Add Cumin and chipotle. mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37871" image="">Allergen:

Method:

- Deep fry Tortilla, whole
- Layer it with the rest of ingredients</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41547" image="">Prep:
- Soak Tomatillos in Warm water for half an hour
   - Brush through them with your hand to loosen &quot;jackets&quot;. The more the better...
- Take off all of the Tomatillos outer jackets

Pre-Oven:
- Ready 2 Deep Hotel Pans for Ingredients
- Half all Tomatillos to ready them for roasting
- Cut Onions
- Add Garlic Whole
- Half Jalapenos and Serranos, Remove Stems
- Set Aside All Remaining Ingredients
- Oil and Salt Ingredients in Hotel Pans

Oven:
- Roast for up to 30-40 minutes at 375For until caramelized
- add water and cook for another 60-90 minutes
   - Stir Occasionally to circulate caramelized top!
- Remove and Cool!
   - Cooling this is key to its colour. If remaining ingredients are added (namely cilantro) to a warm sauce before blending, the green will turn to brown.

Post-Cooling:
- Add 6 of the 8 Bunches of the cilantro to the mixture, and blend with the Large Hand Blender / Immersion Blender. Take 3 Cups of the mixture, and add the remaining 2 bunches of cilantro to the Vitamix. Blend in the Vitamix until it is a uniform deep green mixture. Add to the remaining mixture. 
- Continuing with the Large Hand Blender / Immersion Blender, lime juice, and salt to taste.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41573" image="">Prep:

- Dissolve Tomato Paste in the &quot;Water For Recipes&quot; used to cook the Rice in the Combi Oven (this will result in the Rice turning Red.)

- Once Rice is out of the oven, add all ingredients - Oil, Rice Spice - into the rice in a big mixing bowl, and mix until incorporated.

- When adding the Rice Spice - you are SEASONING TO TASTE. The Rice Spice mixture has salt in it. Mix it in until you can taste the salt, and the spice will be perfect!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47422" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Saute the red peppers and onions to sweeten and soften them up

Assemble in the indicated proportions.

grill or bake the assembled quesdaillas 

Serve salsa and sour cream on the side</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53963" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Rehydrate the seaweed for 10 minutes as per the instructions on the packaging

Strain thoroughly and then toss with lemon juice and salt

Reserve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54300" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44483" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Add black pepper to gravy until the desired spiciness is achieved

***Please do not add it all at once</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51296" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients listed attractively on a plate in the proportions indicated
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41468" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings. 

Pour over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44422" image="">
Prep:

- In the skillet add oil, sautee onions until caramelized, and then toast Spices in the onions 
-  add Garlic and Ginger, cook out for 10 mins
- add the Tomatoes,and water to deglaze skillet and begin simmering for 30 mins

-  Add Butter, and Cream. Simmer further for 15mins

- Check seasoning, and then take off heat 

-Reserve what is needed for serve, or COOL AS FAST AS POSSIBLE what&apos;s not needed

  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26847" image="">Prep:

- Combine Butter Chicken Base sauce, and Chicken thighs in the quantities mentioned.

- Let simmer for 3 hours (if possible). This recipe should simmer for at least 3 hours - </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44542" image="">

Method:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44546" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the items in the indicated proportions attractively on a plate.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44550" image="">Allergens:
milk

Icons:
vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44552" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44603" image="">ALLERGENS: N/A

***Tajin Spice has been found in excess at Place Vanier, and will be used. This will be considered a back-up plan in case we run out of it.

Notes:

This mixture is meant to simulate the famous &quot;Tajin&quot; Spice Mix that exists in Mexico and other parts of Central and South America. The only thing this imposter spice is missing is lime-infused salt - Citric Acid has been employed to make sure that it isn&apos;t missed much. 

Bonus Points: to create lime-infused salt, simply zest 6 limes (for this recipe), and dehydrate overnight on a bed of Kosher Salt, and blitz up the next day in the Vitamix. If anyone actually does this - Chef will be impressed. 

Prep:

- Combine all ingredients. Mix up until uniformly dispersed.

- Label / Date / Store Appropriately...

Any questions? - Ask Chef...</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-39232" image="">
Prep:

-Cook Potatoes by steaming until tender enough to mash easily

-on low heat, simmer cream, garlic, salt, pepper and butter together 

- In the large Hobart Stand-Mixer near the dish area, combine all of the ingredients except the Cream mixture. Begin mixing when you’re ready, and add cream mixture to reach the consistency you want 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51222" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Trim ends off and peel. Discard

2. Cut and slice as needed for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44528" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing and portioning purposes only.

Make associated sub recipes as indicated in those particular recipes

The portion of sauce is 200ml or 6 fl. oz </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44527" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Clean, prepare and chop the herbs as needed. 

Use any combination (or even just a single herb) in a quanitity adding up to 8 grams total weight. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44533" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients in the proportions indicated</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46483" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Julienne all the ingredients and coat with lime juice to prevent oxidation.

Mix all the ingredients to form a slaw and keep cold online.

Toss with spice mix per serving.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47192" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-47208" image="">
PREP RECIPE

***To be converted over to product recipe

METHOD: 

Weigh each block of smoked tofu before cutting. they vary in weight so this is a helpful step to maintain consist protions

-then cut each piece into 50g 

-two pieces of smoked tofu per sandwich

Toast a baguette and add all of the ingredients listed in the proportions indicate</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45118" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47165" image="">


Cook out onions, garlic and ginger in chili oil.
Add the rest of the vegetables and continue to sautee.
Deglaze with cooking wine, soy sauce.
Add corn starch slurry to thicken mix.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47225" image="">Allergen:

Heat up veg stock on low heat.
Small dice onions. Sautee onions and garlic. when clea, add rice and toast for 5 mins or until transluent and slightly coloured. Ladle in veg stock slowly and stir continously so rice cooks and absorbs stock. When rice is cookes add cheese, butter, salt and herbs. 
check seasoning</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47196" image="">Allergen:

Peel Daikon, shred into matchsticks.
Heat up pickling liquid.
in two seperate containers, one for carrots one for daikon.
pour liquid to cover them.

label and reserve for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47195" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Peel and small dice lemongrass, shallots
Sautee shallots and garlice until translucent. Add coriander, lemongrass. cook for 10 mins. Add mushrooms, pepper, salt, soy sauce and coconut milk.

Add nutritional yeast. Blitz in a vitamix, check seasoning of paste.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47200" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47403" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50705" image="">Method:
- heat flat top or pan over med-high heat
- add oil, ensure to coat bottom of pan
- crack egg into hot pan
- season with salt &amp; pepper
- once egg has cooked 60%, flip over gently
- cook for 20 sec until white is fully cooked
- serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29179" image="">1) Add water to large pot, and bring to a boil, reduce heat slightly, add green lentils.

2) Simmer until lentils are fully cooked, drain water and cool lentils under cold running water. Drain and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50988" image="">1. Saute onion in oil until translucent. Add garlic cook for 5mins.
2. Add soy sauce, mirin, korean paste. Bring to a boil. Season. add sesame oil.
3. Put in Vitamix and blend.
4. Cool it down, Label and put away.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50991" image="">1. Cut tofu in Batonet. Deep fry (not too long, just to give color) and add to the sauce.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-27333" image="">
PREP PECIPE

Prepare veggies by cutting and roasting.

Make or fetch tomato sauce

TO BUILD

***This recipe make 4x 2inch hotel pans****

For the first layer, ensure that sauce is put into the bottom of the pan before the noodles go down.

Then layer in this order; noodle, sauce, veggie, cheese and repeat this 4 times, to get 4 layers. 

TO COOK

Steam the lasagnas to warm everything up to hot and cook out the interior, then top with the mozza and transfer to the oven to brown up and finish. 

***cottage cheese can be substituted for the ricotta in a pinch*** 

The finished Lasagnas get cut into 18 portions and 1 portion = 320 g
This recipe makes 4 hotel pans</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46641" image="">1 portion = 180g

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53248" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42364" image="">Combine and mix.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47424" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Saute the red peppers and onions to sweeten and soften them up

Assemble in the indicated proportions.

grill on flat top or bake the assembled quesdaillas 

cut into 4 equal pieces

Serve pico and sour cream on the side</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46638" image="">Allergens:
n/a

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan, made with out gluten

Method:
- rince rice until the water runs clear
- place rice, stock &amp; salt in a large pot
- bring to a boil, turn down to a simmer &amp; cover.
- cook for approx 45min or until some of the kernels begin to open
- remove from heat, strain, spread out onto a sheet pan and allow to cool
hold for service
 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46639" image="">Allergens:
n/a

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan, made with out gluten

Method:
- rince rice in a chinoise until water runs clear, let drain
- dice onions
- in skillet over med heat saute onion &amp; garlic until translucent but not colored
- add rice and saute for 3-5 min until rice begins to color
- add stock, bring to a boil, reduce to a simmer and cover
- cook over low heat until water has been absorbed
- remove from heat &amp; &quot;fluff&quot; with a fork or wooden spoon
- hold hot for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41914" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients. + A large bowl.
2. Mix and coat chicken thighs in oil and seasonings.
3. Either sear on the grill right away and mark the thighs depending on your need. Or leave them to marinate as long as you can.
4. Lable, date and refrigirate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50696" image="">Combine and mix.

Label, date and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-14480" image="">
ah huh whip it

whip it good

ah huh whip it

whip it real good</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50989" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-52913" image="">1. Disolve salt/sugar in the water/vinegar mixture.

2. Toast spices and add to brine base.

3. Mix in the sliced vegetables.

4. Let this mixture sit for a few days to marinate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52908" image="">1. Trip the bellies and ends of tuna.
2. Season with salt and pepper.
3. Sear Blue Rare.
4. Cool down.
5. Portion to 120g each.

Ghost Item = Albacore Tuna.  Added due to cost variance from item previously purchased vs item purchased from food mesh at lower price.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52910" image="">This is the base of the slaw garnish, keep it seperate from the dressing until the last moment during service.

1. Assemble all the ingredients, mix and set aside.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52909" image="">This sauce goes on top of the Seared Tuna

1. Assemble all ingredients.
2. Throw everything but the xanthan gum into a Vitamix and blend on high speed until smooth. 
3. Add xanthan gum and blend until combined fully.
4. Taste and adjust seasoning as needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52911" image="">1. Assemble ingredients together.
2. Place everything but the oil into the Vitamix and blend on high speed.
3. Slowly drizzle in the oil to emulsify the dressing.
4. Taste and adjust seasoning as needed.
5. Label, date and refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52960" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.
2. Sear the lamb first.
3. Add onions/garlic/ginger/leek and sautee a few more minutes.
4. Add in the spices and cook out for another 5-10 minutes or until the spices are fully developed and fragrant.
5. Add the tomatoes, potatoes, squash, water, yam and cook out until the yams are soft.
6. Season and add the mint/lemon juice.
7. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52914" image="">1. Toast and grind the fennel seeds.

2. Small dice lemon rinds.

3. Rough chop cilantro.

4. Mix all ingredients together.

5. Check seasoning.

Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52916" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Sautee onions, garlic and ginger.

3. Add Harissa Mix and sautee for another 5-10 minutes.

4. Add Apricots

5. Toss in the tomatoes, water, yam, chickpea, potatoes and okra and simmer until the potatoes are cooked.

6. Season and adjust seasoning.

7. Add parsley and lemon juice.


Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52915" image="">1. Toast all the spices seperately.

2. Grind all the seeds into powder.

2. Mix.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52907" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Small chop the dried fruit and lemon rinds - Not the raisins.

3. Mix all the dry ingredients - Cous Cous, fruit, lemon rinds.

4. Boil the water + oil - Season the water, taste the seasoning.

5. Pour over the dry ingredients/mix and let sit until the water is absorbed. Break up the cous cous and check seasoning.

6. Add lemon juice as needed and salt/pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-52965" image="">1. Place cous cous to the side.

2. On the other side put stew.

3. Garnish bowl with pickles, yogurt and cilantro and pumpkin seeds.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-52964" image="">1. Place cous cous to the side
2. On the other side put stew.
3. Garnish bowl with pickles, yogurt and cilantro and pumpkin seeds.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-52961" image="">1. Place cous cous down first on the bottom.
2. Place PTN of Tuna in the middle to the side.
3. Place tossed slaw to the side of the tuna.
4. Pour Cilantro Vin over the Tuna.
5. Put a ptn of pickles on the side.
6. Garnish with cilantro and Rst Pumpkin seeds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50703" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26759" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toss trimmed brussel sprouts in oil salt &amp; pepper

2. Place on parchment lined sheet trays in an even layer with space between

3. Roast in Oven @ 400F for approx 12-15 minutes untill roasted and lightly charring and cooked till tender inside.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50976" image="">
Simmer the lentils in the water until they are cooked, but still holding there shape- strain water away thoroughly and discard the water, reserving the lentils. 

Saute the onions, garlic, celery, carrot in some of the canola oil to soften and develop flavours. Reserve and cool down.

Saute off the mushrooms in the remainder of the canola oil and ensure that the water content in the mushrooms cooks out. Reserve and cool down.

Combine the cooked vegetabels and lentils in a big bowl and add the miso paste, rolled oats, walnuts, raisins, chili flakes, chopped thyme and mix thoroughly and season to taste with salt and pepper. 

Lightly oil 4 4inch deep 1/3 pans and tightly pack lentil loaf mixture into the improvised &quot;loaf pans&quot; to make the loaves. 

Bake these loaves for 30-60 minutes or until crispy on top and around edges and &quot;set&quot;.

Allow to cool for a few minutes before attemping to unmold. 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51290" image="">









***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Method:

- Deep fry Tortilla, whole
- Layer it with the rest of ingredients</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50990" image="">Allergen:


Method:

-in hot pickling liquid, add carrots and cucumbers
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53239" image="">Method
- peel pumpkin, remove seeds, cut into even sized chunks
- roast in 350f oven for 10 - 15 min or until tender and slightly dry looking
- remove from heat, keeping warm
- peel and boil the potato until fork tender.
- remove from heat, allow to vent off steam for a few minutes then hold warm for preparation.
- place flour on a work surface, make a well, pass the pumpkin through a ricer directly onto the flour, add salt, pepper, nutmeg
- work the warm ingredients together using a fork until combined ( mix as little as possible ). 
- wisk the egg in a separate bowl, make a well in the pumpkin mixture, incorporate the egg with as little mixing as possible
- once combined, form the dough into a large ball.
- cut off a piece of dough and roll out on a floured surface into a 1&quot; diameter &quot;snake&quot; 
- cut the dough into 1&quot; pieces.
- once all of the dough has been cut, place on a sheet pan with parchment ( keeping pieces separated so they dont stick together )
- place in freezer
- for service, blanch in salted boiling water until they float. 
- remove from boiling water
- place in non stick pan with sage butter, sear, 
- remove from pan, toss with roasted apples
- top with toasted hazelnuts, crisp sage leaves
- finish dish with shaved parmesan
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46572" image="">Allergens:

Dairy/Milk</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53241" image="">Method
- dice apple into 1 cm pcs, toss with lemon juice
- poach gnocchi in boiling salted water
- place sage butter in non stick pan over med high heat
- add apple &amp; gnocchi
- fry until gnocchi caramelizes
- remove from pan, add to plate
- top with crisp sage leaves, fresh parm, toasted hazelnut
serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26965" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

fine dice Jalapenos and set aside corn kernals

Mix wet ingredients

Mix dry ingredients

Combine wet and dry

Add the corn and jalapenos

Mix to combine again

Bake at 350F until cooked throughout and golden brown on top (aprox 15-20 minutes)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53250" image="">Method
- sear onions in hot oil until caramelized
- deglaze with sherry vinegar, stir 
- toss with salt &amp; pepper
- remove, cover, hold hot
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53251" image="">combine all ingredients except water in vitamix
pulse until combined
using medium speed, slowly add water until desired pourable consistancy 
hold for service </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50668" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Pre-drain the pickled jalapeno slices. 

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crisp and golden brown.

Take the two slices of bread for the sandwich add the well drained jalapeno peppers and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50709" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45966" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53906" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Get all veggies ready and set up an assembly line.

Briefly soak the rice paper, one at a time until pliable, turning frequently. 

Assemble the rice wraps by layering carrot julienne, the cellophane noodles, fresh herbs, cucumber julienne and the lettuce leaf. 

Tightly wrap like a burrito. 

Store on a tray lined with parchment, laid between damp towels and covered in plastic film. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50704" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Cook burger, toast bun, cook bacon. 

Assemble a buger with all of the listed toppings in the proportions indicated.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53923" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and blend. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53924" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Split the loin in half to make to pieces more managable. 

Take each half and quarter lengthwise to make long skinny strips. 

Rub and marinate the pork strips in jerk paste for 24 hours prior to cooking. 

To finish, Grill mark the pork loin strips and finish on trays in a 400F+ convection oven.

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32665" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Trim the root end of the green onions (do not chop them though) and toss in oil and salt and pepper. 

Grill them on the charbroiler turning them as needed to get them browned on both sides.

Set the green onions aside to cool

Once cool, chop them and reserve to add to the pineapple. 

Preheat oven to 450*F

Spread diced pineapple on baking sheet.  Roast @ 450*F, stirring to distribute product until pineapple begins to caramelize, about 15-20 minutes.  Allow to cool.

Using the robot coupe pulse the roasted pineapple a couple times to brek it down to a chunky salsa consistency

Combine roasted pineapple with grilled green onion 

Taste and adjust seasoning

Hold cold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53926" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

Combine and mix.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53927" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Grill and roast pork to well done and carve into 30g slices. 

Put slices on a slider bun with jerk ketchup on the bottom and roasted pineapple salsa on top</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53946" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Make veg stock by combining water and vegetable base. heat in a pot and reserve and set aside. 

Melt butter in a separate pot and saute onions until transluscent and then add garlic, stir garlic in and continue to cook for another minute or two.

Add arborio rice to pot and stir it through the onion and garlic and butter and toast the grains of rice in the butter for a minute or two.

Before the rice begins to catch and stick, deglaze with  white wine and stir the wine through the rice, cooking the wine away to nearly dry before adding stock. 

Now add stock, incrementally stirring frequently and thoroughly between additions. 

Add stock until the rice is very tender, in arancini, the risotto should be well past al dente. 

At the end of the cooking, mix through the parmesan and fresh chopped thyme. 

Taste and adjust seasoning. 

Lay out on a parchment lined sheet pan to cook thoroughly before balling

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53947" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Set up a 3 stage breading station

scoop 45g risotto balls with a portion scoop and run them through the breading process</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53955" image="">
PREP RECIPE

The crab cake mix rpe recipe yeilds approximately 40 crab cakes at 60g each. 

This recipe breads them. 

Set up a 3 stage breading station and run the cakes through: flour, eggwash, bread crumb.

Line up neatly on sheetpans

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53961" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Roast crab shells and mirepoix veg rubbed with oil and salt and pepper. 

Halfway through the roasting process smear some crushed tomato onto the collection of goodieas and continue to roast unitl golden brown

Once golden brown transfer the mixture to a pot, add garlic cloves, cinnamon stick, fennel seeds and fresh thyme, cover with water and simmer for 2-4 hours

Strain the stock into a clean pot and add rice, simmer the rice until very tender and then puree the rice to thicken

Strain through a fine strainer to remove any particle

Bring to a simmer and add cream, return to a simmer and add lemon juice, then adjust consistency and seasoning. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53964" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cut cherry tomatoes in half and lay out on a sheet pan

Sprinkle with olive oil, salt and pepper

Dehydrate at 300F for 30-90 minutes</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53965" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Boil potatoes until tender and drain thoroughly

Combine milk, cream and butter in a pot and bring to a simmer

Beat potatoes whip a whip on the stand mixer until they have broken apart

Now add the liquid and season to taste

No pepper is required, salt only

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53969" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Dust and pan sear rockfish

Char tiger prawns

Heat and hold bisque

Prepare and hold the mash

Prepare and hold the lemoned seaweed

Scrub and roast the carrots

Warm oven dried tomatoes

-Quenelle some mash in a bowl off center, stick a carrot vertical just outside the mash, top with the rockfish and ladle the bisque to fill the empty space, arrange on top of the bisque the seaweed, oven dried tomatoes and tiger prawns



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53970" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Taste and adjust seasoning as needed on roasted pumpkin

Scoop out 60g scoops

Do a 3 stage breading process

Reserve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53971" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Presoak white beans for 24 hours

Drain soaked white beans

Sautee onion and garlic in EVOO

Add beans and water and bring to a boil, reduce to a simmer

Simmer unitl falling apart tender and puree with a blender

Season with lemon juice, cayenne pepper, and salt to taste</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53972" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Quarter radishes nose to tail

Pour hot pickling liquid over radishes

Drain radishes previous to use 

Resrve pickling liquid for a second use</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53973" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Fry croquettes

Roast beets

Prepare potato crisps

Pickle and drain radishes

Confit and strain confit garlic

-To plate- put down some dots of bean puree (as glue) and place croquettes on top, arrange beet wedges interspersed with the croquettes, place some crisp potatoes and radish pickles, and arrange a beet green or two

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-29255" image="">Small dice apples 
In frying pan heat 40g of butter, add apples. Cook till softened.  Add 1/4 cup of sugar and caramelize. take off heat. 

Cube Bread 

in bowl mix milk, vanilla, egg, cinnamon and sugar. 

In another bowl mix cubed bread, raisins and apples

pour milk mixture over bread mixture and combine, let it soak up for 15 to 20 minutes. 

Line a hotel pan with parchment paper 

Pour bread mixture into hotel pan and push down

Melt the rest of the butter and pour over top of the bread

bake covered for 30 minutes at 350 then bake for 20 minutes uncovered. Till custard has set. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53979" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Heat the large steam kettle to just below simmering

Blanch the vegetables then the noodles in hot simmering water for no longer than 30 seconds to 1 minute. (leave the vegetables in when blanching the noodles)

Strain and cool.

Mix in the seasonings.

Tray and label.

Bake to heat for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until lightly browned and hot throughout. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53995" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss mushrooms with salt and pepper and oil. 

Roast on a parchment lined sheet pan in a hot oven until the water from the mushrooms cooks away and the mushrooms are browned and flavorful</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53996" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the onion with oil and salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned around the edges and hot throughout

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46824" image="">
PREP RECIPE

This recipe is for costing purposes only. 

Please make all of the associated sub recipes as indicated in those recipes. 

Any blend of the listed vegetables will suffice, or just one vegetable. 

The important part is that 180g/ 6oz (by weight) of vegetables are provided. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54079" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the exterior of the sandwich with garlic butter and lay slices of cheese and deli meat in the center portion. 

Grill on flattop until bread is goldwen brown and crispy and the cheese is melted. 

Cut in half once, corner to corner. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52968" image="">1. Toss Pumpkin Seeds with oil and seasonings

2, Roast until there is a little color.

3. Cool, downsize, label, Keep in dry spot.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54250" image="">1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Sautee/Brown the meat together first and season with all the salt. Drain off all the fat. - Salt amount is calculated for % of meat, please use the whole amount as stated. 450G.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add herbs and meat. 

4. Pour in the crushed tomatoes.

5. Pring to a simmer. 

6. Mix in the frozen vegetables ( peas and carrots ).

7. Check for seasoning.

8. Ladle into pans to cover with mash potatoes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47207" image="">
PREP RECIPE

***To be converted over to product recipe

Toast a baguette and all add of the ingredients listed in the proportions indicated</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50992" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Chop parsley, collect all ingredients, except the pork. 

Put the herbs and spices, oil, water and lemon juice in a bucket and buzz it with the handblender to make a fully pureed marinade.

Marinate the pork in this liquid, ideally for a day before cooking.

Roast the pork until fully cooked and golden brown and crispy on the exterior. 

***Please note the reduction in recipe yeild is reflective of the weight loss that occurs when the pork is cooked***</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51298" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Arrange the ingredients listed on a plate in an attractive manner. Garnish with fresh chopped italian parsley.

Use the proportions indicated. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51297" image="">
PREP RECIPE

****Soak white beans at least a day in advance, then drain the soaking water and discard.****

Chop vegetables and prepare herbs. 

Saute the mirepoix veg, garlic, and fennel seeds in oil until softened and fragrant. 

Add the tomato product to the pot and put some heat to it to develop flavours. 

Add the soaked, drained beans and enough water to cover and simmer for 1-2 hours or until beans are completely soft. 

Top up water as needed. 

Add the herbs at the end and adjust seasoning as needed. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47418" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47206" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Serve 1 roll with 45ml of sauce</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50706" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Grill the burger on the charbroiler, melting the cheese on it when it is close to done.

Toast the bun. 

Fry the overeasy egg on the flattop

To build the burger, put the feast signature sauce on the top bun and the bacon jam on the bottom bun. 

Place the patty on the bottom bun and top with the egg, add the lettuce and tomato slices and put the lid on the burger. 

Secure with a skewer and serve with the pickel spear on the side. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54768" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50497" image="">***If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher.  You will regret life if you do not do this step.  Trust me.

1) Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a boil.

2) Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.

3) Once pasta is cool drain water and stir in lots of ice and cold water, stir constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled drain the water.

4) Store cooled pasta in container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51534" image="">Method

-Peel skin off Jicama
- julienne sized pieces, can use a mandolin 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55427" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem and seeds.

3. cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50565" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61118" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-9733" image="">1. Cut with sharp knife on the bias
2. Refreshing cut onions in ice water water, drain and let dry off beofre storing
3. Label and store correctly</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56113" image="">1. Thick cut the cabbage and apples.

2. Sautee the onions and garlic first, add the cabbage and apples. Cook out for 20 minutes, add vinegar, salt and pepper and taste.

Serve hot.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56631" image="">Method:

- use a vitamix to make this sauce. It is essential that you use a blender strong enough to puree the cashews in the sauce so it is not grainy.  If you do not have a vitamix, pre soak the cashews in hot water for a minimum of 1 hr before making the sauce. 
- place all ingredients in the vitamix, puree until smooth
- adjust consistency with water until desired consistencty is reached
- adjust seasoning - acid (tamarind), heat(sambal), sweet(sugar), salt(veg fish sauce) to desired taste
- label, date, hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56766" image="">METHOD:

1. slice tomatoes in half

2. toss in bowl with olive oil and salt and pepper

3. on parchment lined tray place tomatoes cut side up.

4. put in oven at 400 degrees for 6-10 minutes (may need longer) 

5: check for doneness; most liquid should have evaporated and tomatoes should be slightly dried around edges but not leathery or burnt.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56768" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Heat a large pot over medium heat. Once hot, add oil, onion, cumin, and one-third of the salt.(Adjust if altering batch size).

2. Add garlic, ginger, cilantro, and green chilies to Robot coupe to pulse into a paste. Then, add to the pan with the onions.

3. Next add ground coriander, chili powder, and turmeric and stir to coat. Add a little more oil at this point if the pan is looking dry.

4. Next add pureed tomatoes and chickpeas and remaining salt. If the mixture looks a little too thick, add up to 1 cup (250 ml) water. You’re looking for a semi-thick soup consistency at this point, as it will cook down into more of a stew.

5. Increase heat to medium high until it reaches a rolling simmer, then reduce heat to low or medium-low and maintain a simmer (uncovered) for 15-20 minutes, or until thick and stew-like. Stir occasionally.

6. When the chana masala is thickened and bubbly, taste and adjust seasonings as needed, add more salt if needed.

7. Remove from heat and add lemon juice and garam masala. Stir to mix.

Hot hold/serve immediately

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44790" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Grab can 
2.open
3.Drain and rinse
4.place in container label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56915" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-57038" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Carved Turkey Dinner

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a roasting pan rub the turkey down with oil, season liberally all over with salt and pepper and garlic.

2. in the bottom of the roasting pan add Stock, thyme, rosemary and bay leaf

3. Cover with tin foil and place in 325F oven for an hour

4. Uncover and finish turkey uncovered. Check temp every 30 minutes till centre of trukey reaches an internal temp of 160F.

5. Reserve pan drippings for gravy.

HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57040" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Carved Turkey dinner

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Strain pan drippings through a fine-mesh sieve; discard solids and reserve 2 1/2 cups pan drippings; set aside.

2  Melt butter in a medium saucepan over medium heat. Whisk in flour and thyme until lightly browned, about 1 minute.

3. Gradually whisk in reserved pan drippings. Bring to a boil; reduce heat and simmer, whisking constantly, until thickened, about 5-10 minutes. Stir in parsley; season with salt and pepper, to taste. Adjust seasoning as needed.

  HOT HOLD/SERVE

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57147" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. remove stem and seeds, discard

3. cut peppers into apropriate size/shape for use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41407" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Trim ends/tips of chives and discard any blemished chives.

2.Using a sharp chef knife mince chives. use a rocking/slicing motion to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate sized container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1. Gather All Ingredients

2. Slice onions with food prossecer slicing blade

3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion

4. cool down and store in cambros

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50679" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove rosemary needles from the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. Using a sharp knife, pile the rosemary in a bundle and rough chop. Continue this until rosemary is a course or fine as needed for recipe.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55167" image="">RATIO</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56114" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam in the steamer for for 3-5 minutes. Cautious not to over cook them as they will burst. Better to undercook slightly as they will be cooked again when they get fried! Reserve for service.

2. Once ready for service; add a small amount of oil to a saute pan / flat top, heat pan over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add steamed perogies to pan and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through. HOT HOLD / SERVE

3. PLATING; Arange the perogies  around the plate in a circle, top with caramelized onions; Each plate gets 240g of perogy (8pieces) slice the smokie into bite size slices (bias cut) arange around the perogies alternating around the plate.
4. Garnish with green onion. Sauerkraut and sour cream are served on the side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51527" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Place all your rice noodles in a deep mixing bowl, (trying to snap as few of them as possible as you remove them from the package). Bring a good amount of water to boil. Pour the boiling water over the rice noodles until they are completely submerged. 

2.  Stir constantly to prevent clumping/sticking. When they are completely limp, give them a taste to see if they’re cooked through. The thread-like vermicelli noodles  will cook through in just a few minutes. The flat rice noodles might take upwards of ten minutes depending on thickness. Pay attention and test the noodles frequently because they’ll become mushy if they overcook.

3. Once the noodles are tender, drain them and run them under cool water to stop the cooking. Toss them with a small bit of sesame oil to keep the noodles from sticking to each other if you’re not going to use them right away. 

4. The noodles will be used in a stir-fry dish like pad thai, you definitely want to under-cook them a little bit. They will absorb more moisture and cook the rest of the way through once in the stir fry. If your noodles are perfectly cooked to start, they will turn to mush in the stir fry. 

NOTE: Even with a bit of sesame oil, the noodles still tend to clump up after you drain them. They will loosen again once you mix the noodles into your dish

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51536" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Pick leaves from thick parts of stem. Discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife lightly roll leaves together and using a slicing motion run knife thru the oregano until desired texture achived (course or fine)

3. Always use a slicing motion when chopping soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in aproptiate insert/cambro with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-6888" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Pulse jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

*Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61104" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19208" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut to size
3.place in container, label and refridgerate 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32656" image="">1)  Bring water up to a boil.  Add concentrate.  Stir throughly to combine.  Use immidiately or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56115" image="">**COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam in the steamer for for 3-5 minutes. Cautious not to over cook them as they will burst. Better to undercook slightly as they will be cooked again when they get fried! Reserve for service.

2. Once ready for service; add a small amount of oil to a saute pan / flat top, heat pan over medium high heat, once the oil begins to shimmer, add steamed perogies to pan and allow to crisp slightly around the exterior, ensuring the inside is thuroughly heated through. HOT HOLD / SERVE

3. PLATING; Arange the perogies  around the plate in a circle, top with caramelized onions; Each plate gets 240g of perogy (8pieces) 

4. Garnish with green onion. Sauerkraut and sour cream are served on the side.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7093" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Steam potatoes in Rational.

2. Warm remaining ingredients in a pot. DO NOT BOIL.

3. Using paddle attachment in large mixer break up potatoes while adding remaining ingredients.

4. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62275" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.
2.
3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46637" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.gently clean mushroom stems

2.cut down portions to approx the same size

3.Saute shallots, garlic,  in oil until translucent

4. Fold in thyme leaves and saute 1 min

5. Saute until mushrooms have expressed most of their liquid

6. Remove from heat, toss with fresh squeezed lemon juice, chopped parsley

7. Season with salt &amp; pepper

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, rondeau pot, insert, rubber spatula
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50601" image="">For stocks - save all your parsley, leek, green onion and cilantro ends!!!!!!

1. Sautee onion, garlic and leek. Cook out for 5 minuts untill soft. 

2. Add carrot, celery and the spices and sautee for a few more minutes.

3. Add water and bring to a boil, turn down to a low simmer and let it ride for 45 minutes. 

4. Turn off the burner and throw in the parsley and leek ends and let the stock sit for another 30 minutes with the heat off.

5. Strain, downsize and cool down.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53993" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss diced Zucchini with oil and salt and pepper and roast on a parchment lined sheet pan until browned and hot throughout.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26947" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Side

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Preheat the oven to 400 degrees F.

2. Cut the potatoes into quarters and place in a bowl with the olive oil, salt, pepper, garlic and rosemary; toss until the potatoes are evenly coated.

3. Dump the potatoes on a baking sheet and spread out into 1 layer(no crowding, leave space between); roast in the oven for at least 1 hour, or until browned and crisp. Flip twice with a spatula during cooking to ensure even browning.
 4. Remove the potatoes from the oven, season to taste with salt and pepper as needed and serve.

 *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58362" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Smash black peppercorns slightly.  

2)  Combine water, crushed black pepeprcorns, bay leaf, sugar, garlic cloves, onion, rosemary, thyme, salt and lemon (make sure to give the lemons a good squeeze before throwing in the mix)

3)  Bring brine to a boil and stir to ensure that salt and sugar are dissolved.  Put mixture in blast chiller to cool.

4)  When brine has cooled COMPLETELY, add turkey breast.  Ensure breasts stay in brine by weighing them down with a tray from the servery.  

5)  Allow breast to brine for 6 hours.

6)  Roast in 325*F oven until browned and probe thermometer reaches 70*C (158*F).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57231" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41572" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine and mix thouroughly

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
