<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23950" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook and drain the bacon, and chop it. 

Caramelize the onions in a small amount of the bacon fat with the brown sugar. 

Once the onions are caramelized, add the chopped bacon, coffee, vinegar, rosemary and balck peppers and simmer to reduce to jam consistency.

Taste and add salt only if neccessary to balance the flavours. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32665" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Trim the root end of the green onions (do not chop them though) and toss in oil and salt and pepper. 

Grill them on the charbroiler turning them as needed to get them browned on both sides.

Set the green onions aside to cool

Once cool, chop them and reserve to add to the pineapple. 

Preheat oven to 450*F

Spread diced pineapple on baking sheet.  Roast @ 450*F, stirring to distribute product until pineapple begins to caramelize, about 15-20 minutes.  Allow to cool.

Using the robot coupe pulse the roasted pineapple a couple times to brek it down to a chunky salsa consistency

Combine roasted pineapple with grilled green onion 

Taste and adjust seasoning

Hold cold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50668" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Pre-drain the pickled jalapeno slices. 

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crisp and golden brown.

Take the two slices of bread for the sandwich add the well drained jalapeno peppers and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50696" image="">Combine and mix.

Label, date and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50703" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50704" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Cook burger, toast bun, cook bacon. 

Assemble a buger with all of the listed toppings in the proportions indicated.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50705" image="">Method:
- heat flat top or pan over med-high heat
- add oil, ensure to coat bottom of pan
- crack egg into hot pan
- season with salt &amp; pepper
- once egg has cooked 60%, flip over gently
- cook for 20 sec until white is fully cooked
- serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50706" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Grill the burger on the charbroiler, melting the cheese on it when it is close to done.

Toast the bun. 

Fry the overeasy egg on the flattop

To build the burger, put the feast signature sauce on the top bun and the bacon jam on the bottom bun. 

Place the patty on the bottom bun and top with the egg, add the lettuce and tomato slices and put the lid on the burger. 

Secure with a skewer and serve with the pickel spear on the side. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50709" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-53923" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and blend. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53924" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Split the loin in half to make to pieces more managable. 

Take each half and quarter lengthwise to make long skinny strips. 

Rub and marinate the pork strips in jerk paste for 24 hours prior to cooking. 

To finish, Grill mark the pork loin strips and finish on trays in a 400F+ convection oven.

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53926" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

Combine and mix.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53927" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Grill and roast pork to well done and carve into 30g slices. 

Put slices on a slider bun with jerk ketchup on the bottom and roasted pineapple salsa on top</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54079" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the exterior of the sandwich with garlic butter and lay slices of cheese and deli meat in the center portion. 

Grill on flattop until bread is goldwen brown and crispy and the cheese is melted. 

Cut in half once, corner to corner. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
</Recipes>
