<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat well
3.Bake on sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water from the pan runs clear

2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26053" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine tahini, garlic, lemon juice, water and salt in large mixing vessel.  

2. Combine well with immersion blender.

3.  Add chopped parsley.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine everything and mix thoroughly.
2. Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and salt, and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil.

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and continue to cook onions for 40 minutes. In a cycle of letting them brown, and scraping and stirring with a wooden spoon, until onions are a dark golden brown. Add a splash of water cold if the bottom browning is sticking too much.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26328" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  In appropriate sized sauce pan, combine rice vinegar, salt, sugar, and simmer until salt and sugar are dissolved.  Add thai chilis and ginger, turn off heat and allow mixture to cool to room temperature.

2)  Meanwhile, add carrot and daikon radish to 4L cambro container.  Add room temp pickling solution, and wiegh down vegetables with parchment to keep them submerged.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate.  Vegetables are best if left to pickle for at least 24 hours.

Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26331" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine soy sauce, thai chili&apos;s, sugar, cilantro, lime juice and garlic puree.  Whisk well until sugar is fully dissolved.  

2. Dice tofu into 1-1.25&quot; cubes and add to marinade.  Allow to marinate for at least 2 hours in appropriate vessel. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1)  Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

2)  Remove baskets from deep fryer.  Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

3)  Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil.  Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

4)  Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil.  Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

5)  Place in appropriate container once cooled.  Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
soy (from tortilla)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27383" image="">1)  In mixing bowl, combine cooked quinoa and 30 ml of lemon tahini dressing.  Place in serving bowl.

2)  Combine shredded beets, edamame, matchstick carrots, spinach and roasted yam with remaining dressing.  Combine well and place on top of quinoa.  Garnish with roasted sesame seeds and lemon wedge.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31111" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1)  Add water to steam kettle, add konbu and bring to a simmer for 15 minutes. Remove konbu. 

2) Turn off heat, whisk in miso.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-31948" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35227" image="">THE RECIPE IS A PREP,  an in house made ingredient recipe
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Mix to smooth consistencey 
2. Send it
3.
cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35271" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:
NOTE: 1 litre of mayo = 1 kilogram.

1. Combine all well.  

2. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35313" image="">1) Toss romaine lettuce and croutons together in bowl with dressing.  Place greens on plate. 

2) Top with parmesan cheese, croutons and lemomn wedge.  Serve immidiately.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35801" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  In large mixing bowl, combine oil, yams, and salt and pepper.  Mix well.

2)  Put seasoned yams on parchment lined roasting pan, and roast yams until well caramalized and tender, about 15 minutes.  Make sure to rotate pan and mix product half way through cooking to ensure even roasting.

3)  Make sure to not smash up yams.  We need them to be nice and unsmashed.

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Take off stems of jalapenos.  Remove pits of avocado and scoop flesh from skin.  Place all ingredients except oil in 20 L cambro container.  

2)  Blend well with immersion blender until a smooth puree consistency is reached.  

3)  Slowly begin adding oil, a little at a time until all oil has been added.  Taste for seasonining.


-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43677" image="">1)  Place appropriate amount of salad greens in bowl.  Add Santa Fe Salad portion and 30 ml ladle of vinaigrette.  Combine well.

2)  Garnish salad with crispy tortilla strips and lime wedge.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43746" image="">1) Add dressing to greens, cucumber, carrot, tomatoes, red pepper and mix well. Use just enough dressing to coat the salad.

2) Top with sunflower seeds and radish. Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45255" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat

Icons:
N/A

Method:
 70 pcs average per case

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49660" image="">clean &amp; scrub beets 
place in water and boil until fork tender ( keep colors separate
in separate pot, bring the remaining ingredients to a boil
once beets are fork tender, remove from heat, discard cooking liquid
peel, slice into 1 cm slices
in 2 separate pots, add peeled sliced beets and pickling liquid together, simmer for 5 min
remove from heat and allow to cool in cooking liquid
refridgerate and hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49662" image="">Method:
wash zucchini
trim ends 
cut into 1&quot; thick rounds ( if zucchini is over 2&quot; in diameter, cut in half lenghtwise
toss with oil, salt, pepper
grill over high heat until marked
remove from heat, allow to cool 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50504" image="">1) Place shaved beef on flat top and cook until starting to brown, add caramelized onion, and sauteed peppers.

2) On bottom piece of baguette, spread garlic mayo, place warmed up beef, onions and peppers. Break the cheddar, and provalone slices in half, and top filling with alternating halves of cheddar and provalone to cover top.

3) Place top of baguette on flat top, crust side down, until it&apos;s warm and starting to get crispy, but not hard.

4) Place place bottom piece with all fillings and cheese on parchment lined flash pan, put in deck oven for 2-3 minutes or until cheese is fully melted.

5) Combine top and bottom of sandwich, cut on a bias and serve.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50506" image="">1) Cut peppers in half, remove stem, seeds, and white rib/membrain. Slice peppers in to 1/8&quot; julien pieces.

2) In a large pan, heat oil on high, add peppers and season. Cook until tender and starting to brown.

3) Cool spread out on bakeing sheet. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50509" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50690" image="">1. Pre heat oven 375F.
2. In a baking sheet, lay flat cashew.
3. Roast it for about 8-10minutes or until golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50781" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems 

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the Basil together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until basil desired size/texture. *Always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until lightly browned and hot throughout. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55083" image="">1. Peel and diced parsnip.
2. Combine the rest of ingredient in mixing bowl.
3. Roast.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56490" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Mix all marinade ingredients ensuring sugar gets dissolved.

2) Add chicken thighs and marinade 12-24 hours.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56491" image="">1. Spread mayo on both sides of baguette.

2. Place cooked chicken, cucumber, pickled veg, sliced jalepenos then cilanrto (in that order).

PLEASE ENSURE JALAPENOS ARE VERY THINLY SLICED.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56849" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Soak papaya in cold water overnight (this will keep it crispy).

2. Bruise papaya.

3. Add carrot, green beans.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Soak papaya in cold water overnight 9this will keep it crispy).

2. Bruise papaya.

3. Add prepped papaya, carrot &amp; bean mixture with tomatoes (cut in half) to mixing bowl.

4. Add dressing and toss to combine.

5. Plate, ensuring you leave some tomato and beans to place on top of salad.

6. Garnish with toasted cashews.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Put all ingredients EXCEPT oil in robot coupe.

2. Puree then slowly add oil in a steady stream until cheese is light and fluffy.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-58430" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-58450" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Take chicken out of marinade and lay it in a single layer on parchemnt lined baking sheets.

2. Place in a 375F oven and cook until internal temperature reaches 165F

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61660" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method: 
1. Peel beets.
2. Using mandoline, julienne beets.
3. Rinse in cold water until water runs clear so beets don&apos;t bleed into other foods.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61788" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-61789" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cut veg into long slices 1-2 cm thick.
2. Grill on both sides to get some grill marks and smokey flavour.
3. Remove from grill and toss together with olive oil and salt &amp; pepper.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67823" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE
Final product handed to the customer

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE***
Preps used in this Product recipe:
Method:
1. Dress arugula and root veg.

2. Place in bowl and garnish with feta then pumpkin seeds.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-67824" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Toss each vegetable SEPERATELY in olive oil, caraway seeds and seasoning.
2. Roast at 425F on seperate full sized baking sheets until just cooked and slightly coloured.
3. Once cooled mix together, label and store.

Rotate this item with older product.
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
