<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7139" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients.
        2. Mix the remaining ingredients.


        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: DAIRY
        Method:

        1. Assemble all ingredients.

        2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

        3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes.

        4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

        5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

        6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

        22.7 kg = 50 lbs
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size required
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients and tools
        2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9767" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-13933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

        2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients
        2. Slice onions with food prossecer slicing blade
        3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion
        4. cool down and store in cambros

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

        2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

        3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice.
        Mix well.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

        2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

        3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

        4) Season with salt &amp; pepper.

        -Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

        PREP RECIPE

        1. Over medium heat, heat oil

        2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

        3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions
        begin to soften

        4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and
        distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

        5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

        2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse
        for 10 minutes

        3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

        4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop
        and water is cooked out.

        5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

        6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding
        more milk.

        7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula
        (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20 minutes.

        8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, havarti and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

        9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil. Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4
        minutes.

        2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar. Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is
        dissolved and well incorporated.

        2. Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

        2. Add red onions.

        3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1) In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high
        heat. Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot. Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not
        overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown. Taste for seasoning.

        2) Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find
        it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

        2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the
        water to a FULL boil.

        3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not
        stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
        APPROX 7 MINUTES

        4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure
        to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir

        5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1) In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil. When oil is warm, add garlic and fry
        until garlic is golden brown. Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste. Add chili flakes and
        fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

        2) Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer. Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more. Take off heat.

        3) Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth. Label, date,
        refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26229" image="">1) In large pot, bring water and salt to a boil

        2) bring water down to a simmer and gently cook lasagna noodles, being careful not to rip or tear.

        3) Strain noodles, allow to cool slightly and add oil to ensure that noodles will not stick together.

        4) reserve for lasagna, or store in appropriate vessel and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26328" image="">1) In appropriate sized sauce pan, combine rice vinegar, salt, sugar, and simmer until
        salt and sugar are dissolved. Add thai chilis and ginger, turn off heat and allow mixture to cool to room
        temperature.

        2) Meanwhile, add carrot and daikon radish to 4L cambro container. Add room temp pickling solution, and wiegh
        down vegetable swith parchment to keep them submerged.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate. Vegetables are best if left to pickle for at least 24 hours.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26460" image="">1) In medium sauce pan, combine lentils and water

        2) Spread out on a baking tray and allow to cool. Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-29170" image="">1) Make apple cider dressing as per recipe.

        2) Shred cabbages in robot coupe food processor.

        3) Pulse cleaned kale in robot coupe until broken down.

        4) Combine shredded cabbages, kale and chopped cilantro. Mix well with dressing.

        Allergens:

        Soy
        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1) Bring water to a boil in large stock pot. Add veg stock concentrate and stir well
        to combine. Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33519" image="">1) Combine milk, onion and bay leaf in large steam kettle. Bring to a simmer. Lower
        heat and allow onion and bay leaf to steep in liquid for 20 minutes.

        2) Bring milk back up to a simmer and add corn starch slurry as per recipe.

        3) Strain thickened liquid and label, date, refrigerate.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-33520" image="">1) Combine white sauce, salt and pepper and garlic. Bring to a simmer and allow
        flavours to infuse, about 5 minutes.

        2) Add parmesan cheese and taste for seasoning.

        3) Hold for service, or label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Milk/Dairy
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-34121" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-35132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Cut lemons in quarters. Crush garlic and slice shallots.

        2) Combine all except chicken breast. Stir well to combine.

        3) In a non-reactive container (plastic) add chicken. Add marinade and JUST ENOUGH OIL to COAT not COVER the
        chicken breasts and mix well. Allow to marinate for 8 hours or overnight.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35272" image="">1) Remove and discard stem, cut letuce in quarters, then shave off thin strips.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.

        Average weight of a head of Iceberg is 470g with 10% yield loss for core and outer leaves.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-37780" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Preheat the oven to 450F.

        2. Toss the cauliflower with the lemon oil, salt &amp; pepper until evenly coated.

        3. On a parchment lined baking sheet place cauliflower in even layer with space betwee eac piece (don&apos;t
        crowd pan or veg will steam rather than roast) roast until golden and tender; Aprox. 20 minutes. Transfer to a
        hotel pan for service.

        HOT HOLD/SERVE

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        pickle|onion red

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings.

        2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42012" image="">1) Roasted Serrano peppers on grill until deeply charred. Reserve for making sour
        cream

        2) Combine sour cream, roasted serrano peppers, lime juice, cilantro and salt in container for vita mix. Process
        on medium until well combined.

        3) Taste for seasoning and label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Milk/Dairy
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1) Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment. If you don&apos;t know
        how, ask chef or a 1st cook.

        2) Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

        Allergens:

        No known prioirity allergens.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44510" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44652" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingedients
        2.pick leaves
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1) Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along
        the stem to remove leaves.

        2) Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45011" image="">1) Put strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.
        If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

        2) In large kettle, bring water to a boil.

        3) Add egg noodles and turn heat down by half. Simmer egg noodles for 3-5 minutes or until al dente.

        4) Drain water. When water is completely drained, add cold water back into pot along with 3 grey lugs of ice.
        Until pasta is completely covered. mix gently.

        5) Drain water and repeat step 4. It&apos;s very important to stir the pasta gently to ensure that it is cooled
        throughout, especially when making large batches.

        6) Strain water again and add cooked pasta to appropriate vesself for storage. Add a small amount of oil and
        stir into noodles to avoid having them stick.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingedients
        2.wash and trim
        3.place in container, label and place in fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:

        Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46507" image="">1) Cut cherry tomatoes in half, toss with oil and salt and pepper mix, roast in a hot
        oven 450F briefly 10 min or so, just to soften up and brown lightly
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Method:

        1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
        2. Save tops for soup/sauce
        3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
        4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens

        Method:

        1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
        2.
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-47324" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


        Related Products this prep gets used in: Meatball sub

        Method:

        1. Begin by sauteing onion until soft and staring to brown then add garlic and cook it out till it becomes
        fragrant. Reserve.

        2. Cook lentils until soft and mash before adding into the mixture. DRAIN THOROUGHLY. Allow to steam out.

        3. Make sure both cooked components are completely chilled down prior to adding to meat mixture.

        4. Mix thoroughly, Cook a small piece and taste for seasoning, adjust as necassary.

        5. Form into meatballs and chill thoroughly.

        MEATBALL PORTION SIZE SHOULD BE 55g RAW- USE THE BLACK HANDLED PORTION SCOOP. CHECK WEIGHTS!

        -Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        n/a

        Method:

        Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn
        heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

        Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

        ***Note***

        This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a
        *free* by-product.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

        Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done.

        Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-49002" image="">Allergens:

        Icons:
        made with out gluten

        Method:
        - slice pancetta rounds2-3mm thick
        - lay flat on parchment lined sheet pan
        - cover with another piece of parchment
        - top with another flat sheetpan
        - bake in 375 oven for 7-10 min or until crisp &amp; fat is rendered
        - hold for service
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50464" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        Mac &amp; cheese

        Method:

        1) Set milk out to warm up while doing other steps.

        2) In pot melt the butter over medium heat

        3) Add the flour through fine mesh chinois while whisking melted butter to insure that no lumps are formed.

        4) Stir until the mixture is smooth and with out lumps, this is the time to be more careful. Cook for 1 minute
        so the flour becomes tastier and absorbs the fats. The roux should be a nice golden colour.

        5) Add warm milk to roux in a steady stream, whisking continuously. Simmer on low heat until it starts to
        thicken, but insure it does not come to a boil. Whisk in the salt and pepper mix, and nutmeg, taste for
        seasoning and adjust if needed. Set aside for recipe.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50485" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1) Roughly chop onion in to bit size pieces, add to robocoupe and puree.

        2) Add all other ingredients to a bowl and mix well with whisk, and season to taste with salt.

        cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50488" image="">1) Unwrap smoked brisket, place on meat slicer, and cut to 1/8&quot; slices.

        2) Place in an appropriate sized container, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50489" image="">1. Preheat oven to 275F
        2. Combine achiote paste, orange and pineapple juice into a thick spreadable paste.
        3. Season pork with salt and pepper. Make sure to get in all the cracks.
        4. Place pork in braising dish with onions and jalapenos. cover with achiote marinade and add water until it
        comes halfway up the shoulder. Bring to simmer.
        5. Cover pork and braise in oven for about 7-8 hours, or until pork pulls easily apart
        6. Remove meat and pull apart or shred with forks. Reduce remaining braising liquid and add half if necessary.
        Add back in pork to keep moist
        7. Allow to cool. Store in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50491" image="">1) Butter one side on each piece of rye, and place on the flattop.

        2) Put smoked meat on the flattop, drizzle 1-2 tbsp water over the meat to create steam, heat it through.

        3) Place saurkraut on flat top and drizzle with 1-2 tbsp of water to create steam, heath through

        4) Apply Russian dressing to both sides of the bread while on the flattop, place swiss chesse on 1 side of
        bread, top with hot smoked meat. top with Saurkraut.

        5) place other slice of bread on top of saurkraut &amp; toast until golden on both sides

        6) Once the bread is crispy and brown, move to cutting board. Slice diagonally, corner to corner. Place on the
        plate and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50494" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto and half of the mozza cheese, then
        place shredded kale, zuchinni, and torn pieces of proscuitto evenly across flatbread.

        2) Sprinkle remaining half of mozza cheese over top.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top
        cheese starts to melt and brown.

        4) Once cooked, cut and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.

        5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

        Slice Proscuitto using #2.5 slicer.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50562" image="">1. Spread pesto across entire surface area of flatbread.

        2. Add capicollo, sundried tomatoes then mozzarella.

        3. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Take it off from oven and finish with balsamic glaze.

        5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50590" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

        2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread pesto, caramelized onion.

        3. Spread crumbled goat cheese, half sliced cherry tomatoes.

        4. Bake 4-5 minutes or until cherry tomatoes are fully cooked and side of flatbread is golden brown.

        5. Take out of oven.

        7. Spread arugula and drizzle with balsamic glaze.

        8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

        2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme
        is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50788" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

        2) Evenly lay sliced Bocconcinni over pesto.

        3) Add sliced tomatoes.

        4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        5) Once cooked take out from oven.

        6) Spread out whole basil and drizzle balsamic glaze.

        7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50789" image="">1.Drain and slice boconccinni.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
        2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
        3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
        4. Take it off from oven.
        5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
        6. Store in a dry place until needed.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
        2.Store in fridge until needed.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50824" image="">1. Pre-heat oven to 400F
        2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet,
        3. Spread half of the cheese, pulled pork, corn, julienne peppers and lastly sprinkle the rest of the cheese
        4. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.
        5. Take off fom oven and add pico de gallo.
        7. Drizzle the sour cream.
        8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50858" image="">1.Sautee peppers &amp; onions until slightly soft and fragrent.

        2. Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with mashed confit garlic.

        3. Evenly spread spinach then sauteed peppers &amp; onions.

        4. Lay down sliced tomatoes.

        5. Sprinkle feta cheese and olives.

        6. Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50859" image="">1) Spread pesto on the bottom of the flatbread, drain excess liquid off bruschetta mix
        and place evenly over the top of the flatbread.

        2) Add mozzarella cheese.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        3) Take it off from oven and drizzle with balsamic reduction.

        4) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50860" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Dice tomatoes.

        2) Combine all ingredients, and place in a container, pour over liquid to coat tomatoes. Let marinate at least
        24 hours.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50896" image="">1) Prebake flatbread first in deck oven for 4-5 minutes until bottom is crispy and
        edges of flatbread are golden brown before putting any toppings on.

        2) After baking &amp; cooling lightly coat bottom of flatbread with cream cheese, smoked salmon, capers and
        sliced white onion.

        3) When you get an order warm flatbread in deck oven for 1 minute.

        4) Take it off from oven and garnish with fresh dill.

        5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
        2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Wash Tomato in cold water
        2.Cut in half Lenght wise
        3.Container label fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
        knife, cutting board, storage container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-51303" image="">Method:
        ladel 90 ml portion of sauce onto plate
        top with portion of baked pasta
        garnish with fresh parsley sprig and sprinkle of shredded parm
        serve

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53126" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Warm bechamel over medium heat, stirring often to ensure sauce doesn&apos;t scald on the bottom of the pot.

        2. Have shredded cheese ready and add off the heat while stirring to melt.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54664" image="C:\Users\okbrianb\Pictures\Pasta 16 pieces.bmp">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE
        ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cook off, and break up chorizo, sautee until fully cooked and browned. Remove cooked meat with slotted spoon
        and set asidet.

        2. In the fat left by the chorizo, saute onions and peppers until fragrant. Add mushrooms until soft and most of
        the moisture has been cooked off.

        3. Combine evenly with penne and tomato sauce.

        4. Place into 2&quot; hotel pan and top with the cheeses.

        5. Cover with plastic wrap and a metal lid, steam with the thermometer in until internal temperature reachs
        160F.

        6. Place in oven at 400F until cheese is golden brown. Cut in to 16 even pieces (2 x 8).

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54666" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Warm up sauce.

        2. Blanch broccoli.

        3. Cook chicken.

        4. Toss cooked pasta with sauce, broccoli, chicken and portion into a hotel pans.

        5. Cover with plastic wrap and a metal lid, steam with the thermometer in until internal temperature reachs
        160F.

        6. Place in oven at 400F until cheese is golden brown. Cut in to 16 even pieces (2 x 8).

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55083" image="">1. Peel and diced parsnip.
        2. Combine the rest of ingredient in mixing bowl.
        3. Roast.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55084" image="">1. Diced carrot and place in a mixing bowl with the rest of ingredients and roast.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55127" image="">1) In Robot Coupe slice onion and zucchini.

        2) In Robot Coupe shred carrots.

        3) Drain roasted peppers and slice.

        4) In rondo over medium heat add olive oil and seasoning. Add onion, garlic and carrot and sweat until softened
        and fragrant.

        5) Add zucchini and peppers and cook until just warmed through (3-4 minutes).

        6) Check for seasoning.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55515" image="">IT IS VERY IMPORTANT SPINACH IS TOTALLY DEFROSTED AND AS MUCH LIQUID HAS BEEN SQUEEZED
        OUT.

        1) In a large pan add oil over medium heat and sweat onion until soft.

        2) Add garlic and sweat 1-2 minutes until fragrant.

        3) Add mushrooms and cook until most of their liquid has been released.

        4) Add spinach and stir to combine ensuring most of liquid in spinach has been released.

        5) Season to taste.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55516" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Spread a small amount of cheese sauce on bottom of 2&quot; hotel pans.

        2) Spread lasagna noodles evenly.

        3) Add mushroom/ spinach mixture then ricotta.

        4) Add another layer of noodles.

        5) Add sauce and more vegetable mixture.

        6) Add noodles/ sauce.

        7) Top with mozzarella and parmesan.

        8) Bake uncovered in a 300 F oven for 45 mins. Ensure noodles are cooked and internal temperature is between
        160-165 F.

        (Builds one pan, bottom to top)
        Parmesan 100g
        Mozzarella 500g
        3-cheese sauce 750ml
        Noodles 8
        Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
        3-cheese sauce 750ml
        Noodles 8
        Ricotta 500g
        Mushroom/ Spinach mix 800g
        Noodles 8
        3-cheese sauce 750ml

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56337" image="">1) Spread pesto evenly over entire area of flatbread.

        2) Add artichokes, olives, sundried tomatoes then goat cheese.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Take it off from oven and evenly spread arugula on top and balsamic reduction.

        5) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56433" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Peel and clean Celery root, cut into manageable size pieces.

        2. Using Mandoline slice into matchstick sized pieces(Julienne) mince green onions and parsley. Set aside.

        3. Using cheesecloth gently squeeze exess moisture from shrimp (don&apos;t squeeze to hard the shrimp will break
        and look unappatizing)

        4. In a bowl mix together mayo, dijon, seasonings, lemon zest and juice.

        5. Fold reserved celery root, green onions, parsley and shrimp together. taste for seasoning and adjust as
        needed. Use immediately or store in a container with a drip shelf (moisture will develop as it sits)

        6. When using mix try to strain off any exess developed moisture as we dont want to make soggy sandwiches!

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56454" image="">1) Grill seasoned chicken to well done. Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent
        flare ups. To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken. If it
        reaches 70*C, it is cooked.

        2) Grill pineapple on both sides.

        3) Brush chicken and pineapple on both sides with Teriyaki sauce and quickly glaze on grill. Do not leave on
        grill too long or sauce will burn.

        4) Place pineapple on chicken, then cheese and melt.

        5) While chicken is cooking, toast bun and spread mayo on both sides.

        6) Place lettuce, tomato and onion on bottom bun.

        7) Place chicken and pineapple on top, close bun and skewer.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56455" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Mix well.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56456" image="">1. Spread grainy mustard mayo on one side of each piece of bread.

        2. Quickly dip both slices of bread in liquid egg, making sure bread doesnt get too soaked.

        3. Place on flattop, add ham, turkey &amp; swiss cheese.

        4. Cook until egg is golden brown and cheese is melted.

        5. Cut in half (corner to corner) and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56457" image="">1) Puree pickled jalapenos, lime juice and cilantro.

        2) Mix well with mayonnaise.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56458" image="">1. Cod takes 10 minutes to deep fry from frozen.

        2. Toast bun, spread mayo on both sides.

        3. Place cooked cod piece on bun, top with slaw and pickled red onions.

        4. Close and add skewer.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

        2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56490" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Mix all marinade ingredients ensuring sugar gets dissolved.

        2) Add chicken thighs and marinade 12-24 hours.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56491" image="">1. Spread mayo on both sides of baguette.

        2. Place cooked chicken, cucumber, pickled veg, sliced jalepenos then cilanrto (in that order).

        PLEASE ENSURE JALAPENOS ARE VERY THINLY SLICED.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56492" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Ensure tuna is well drained.

        2. Combine all ingredients.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56493" image="">1. Warm tuna mixture slightly to take off any chill.

        2. Toast bread.

        3. Place warm tuna mixture on bread, add tomato slices then cheese.

        4. Melt cheese and garnish with green onions.

        5. Cut in half and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56500" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Cook pasta to al dente. This is very important as the pasta will soak up the sauce and get very soft/ mushy
        if it is over cooked.

        2. Drain pasta well and mix with sauce.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        4. Top with mozzarella and parmesan and bake in a 350F oven for ??? minutes ensuring top is golden brown and
        pasta is hot..

        5. Makes 16 portions (2 x 8).

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56502" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Toss cooked pasta, shrimp &amp; grape tomatoes (cut in half) in cream sauce.

        2. Put into hotel pans, top with mozzarella then parmesan.

        3. Bake in 350F oven until hot through and cheese has browned.

        4. Portion into 16 even portions. (2 x 8)

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56506" image="">1- Whisk together all marinade ingredients and coat pork loin. Let marinade for 12-24
        hours, turning loin when possible to provide even coverage.

        2- Remove pork from marinade, season with salt &amp; pepper and roast in a 400 F oven until internal temperature
        of pork reaches 160 F.

        3- Let pork rest before slicing.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56508" image="">1. Spread mustard on both sides of bun.

        2. Layer sl;iced pork, ham, cheese and pickle.

        3. Close bun and press in panini until crispy and cheese is melted.

        4. Cut in half on a slight bias.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56924" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: shell fish, egg, gluten
        Method:

        1. Lightly toast the bread.

        2. Place the lettuce on the bottom of the bun.

        3.Using apropriate sized portion scoop (GREY SCOOP) place 145g of the shrimp remoulade salad mix on top of the
        greens (make sure exess moisture/water has been drained off before placing on sandwich (no one likes a soggy
        bun!)
        close with top bun and serve.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57150" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1. Gather ingredents

        2. Pick Dill fronds off the larger thick stems. Discard stems

        3. Rough chop dill, Using caution not to bruise a delicate herb (use a slicing motion rather than pressing down)

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58450" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Take chicken out of marinade and lay it in a single layer on parchemnt lined baking sheets.

        2. Place in a 375F oven and cook until internal temperature reaches 165F

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61498" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with tomato sauce.

        2) Evenly lay ham, then mozzarella and diced mango.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-61658" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep is used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Ensure roasted cauliflower is broken down into small pieces.

        2. Mix all ingredients (including some of the mozzarella) together in a large mixing bowl reserving a bit of
        mozza for the top. Check for seasoning.

        3. Top with mozza and parmesan.

        Rotate this item with older product.
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61742" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread with pesto.

        2) Evenly lay shrimp, tomatoes and mozzarella. Sprinkle chili flakes.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Cut into 4 even pieces, garnish with arugula, squeeze fresh lemon and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61755" image="">1.Pre-heat oven to 400F or grill

        2. Lay flatbread in a cookie sheet, spread tomato sauce then roasted root veg.

        3. Top w/ crumbled goat cheese.

        4. Bake 4-5 minutes and side of flatbread is golden brown.

        5. Take out of oven.

        7. Spread arugula and toasted pumpkin seeds.

        8. Cut into 4 even pieces and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-61756" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep is used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. All veg should be cut in the same size (3/4&quot; dice)

        2. Roast each veg seperate tossed in olive oil, caraway and s&amp;p in a 425F oven until tender and slightly
        caramalized.

        Cool, label and store.
        Rotate this item with older product.
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-61757" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep is used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. In a large mixing bowl add cooked pasta, drained tuna, cooked mushrooms, peas, parsley &amp; aged cheddar
        cheese.
        2. Mix well and transfer to shallow hotel pans.
        3. Top with bread crumbs.

        Cool, label and store.
        Rotate this item with older product.
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61778" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in olive oil.

        2) Mix all cheeses together.

        3) Spread cheese evenly over flatbread.

        4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        5) Once cooked take out from oven.

        6) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61779" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto.

        2) Evenly lay cooked mushrooms over pesto.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Once cooked take out from oven.

        5) Lay arugula over.

        7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61780" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in cheese.

        2) Evenly lay sliced apple &amp; cooked pancetta over.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Once cooked take out from oven.

        6) Spread out arugula.

        7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61781" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in alfredo sauce.

        2) Evenly lay spinach, cooked chicken, diced artichokes, red peppers.

        3) Add both cheeses.

        4) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        5) Once cooked take out from oven.

        6) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61782" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in garlic confit puree.

        2) Evenly lay cooked mushrooms, chili flakes &amp; mozza cheese.

        3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 4-5 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and edges of
        flatbread is golden brown.

        4) Once cooked take out from oven.

        6) Spread out arugula.

        7) Cut into 4 even pieces and serve
    </Recipe>
</Recipes>
