<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well
3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26047" image="">1. Add eggs to appropriate cooking vessel
2. Cover with cold water by 1 inch
3. Bring to boil slowly over medium heat. Once boil is reached, remove from heat, cover and let sit for 12 minutes
4. Run eggs under cold water until cool
5. Place in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Alternatively, eggs can be made in rationale oven by steaming on 100% steam for 13 minutes.  Ensure to ice bath to bring down temperature and to stop the eggs from overcooking.

Allergens:

Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26050" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Combine  dijon, herbs, shallots, garlic, sriracha, butter milk, salt and peppercorn in a 20L container, puree with a hand blander.

2. Combine greek yougurt &amp; sour cream . Mix thoroughly. Dressing should be thick but pourable.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

4.  Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and the rest with romano oil.  Shake it.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26065" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 

Mustard

Method:

1. Combine mayo, ketchup, mustard, relish, pureed shallot, salt &amp; pepper in a mixing bowl. Combine well.

2. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26086" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In sauce pan over medium heat, add oil.  Once warm, add garlic and ginger, saute until fragrant, about 4 minutes.  

2. Add soy sauce, water, brown sugar and white sugar.  Bring to a simmer for 5 to 10 minutes until sugar is dissolved and well incorporated. 

2.  Add slurry and simmer until sauce is thickend to desired consistency.   

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26333" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Fine chop parsley and thyme.  Combine with lemon &amp; lime juice, mayo and seasoning.  

2. Taste for seasoning and adjust if necessary.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1)  Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

2)  Remove baskets from deep fryer.  Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

3)  Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil.  Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

4)  Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil.  Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

5)  Place in appropriate container once cooled.  Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
soy (from tortilla)</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28249" image="">1)  Season and grill beef patty until well done (71*C).  

2)  While patty is grilling,toast on grill and add thunderbird sauce to both sides of bun and lettuce to the bottom portion of bun.

3)  Place cooked beef patty on top of lettuce and close.  Top with pickle and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28250" image="">1)  Follow same procedure as classic beef burger, but add cheese to the patty when it is 90% cooked.  Top with pickle spear and serve immidiately.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28251" image="">1)  Season and grill chicken to well done.  Ensure to pat product dry to help prevent flare ups.  To make sure that it is cooked through, insert probe thermometer into thickest part of chicken.  If it reaches 70*C, it is cooked.

2)  While chicken is cooking, toast bun and garnish with guacamole and lemon herb aioli.  Top cooked chicken breast with cheese until melted.

3) Add tomato, cooked bacon and citrus arugula.

4) Close bun and top with pickle skewer.


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28252" image="">1)  Grill beef patty to well done (70*C)

2)  Meanwhile, run bun through toaster and spread top side with mayo.  When patty is nearly cooked through, brush with BBQ sauce, add sauted onion and top onions with cheese.  Top cheese with Bacon.  Top bacon with lettuce and onion rings and close sandwich with top half of bun.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28254" image="">1)  Spread butter on outside of sourdough and put butter side down on griddle.  While still on the griddle, put cheeses on both sides of bread.  

2) Warm oven dried tomatoes and place them over entire surface area of sandwich.

3) Close sandwich when cheese begins to melt.  Continue grilling until bread is golden brown and cheese in completely melted.

4) Cut in half from corner to corner.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28759" image="">1) Place Turkey in perferated hotel pans and Steam the turkey @ 240 in the bag till internal temp. reach 165F (2-3 hr defrosted).

2) Slice on the meat slicer on a 2.5 setting</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-34864" image="">
Combine salad greens with ranch dressing.  Plate on large square plate.

Top with sliced cherry tomato, cucumber, egg, avocado slices, cheese, bacon and turkey in seperate piles on top of greens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35014" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. cook fries crispy
2.season and toss in stainless boewl
3.place portiuon in bowl and serve
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35015" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-35132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Cut lemons in quarters. Crush garlic and slice shallots.

2)  Combine all except chicken breast.  Stir well to combine.

3)  In a non-reactive container (plastic) add chicken.  Add marinade and JUST ENOUGH OIL to COAT not COVER the chicken breasts and mix well.  Allow to marinate for 8 hours or overnight.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35258" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Using the robocoupe attachement to slice 1/8&quot;
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: insert, robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35270" image="">1)  Place beef patty on grill.  Ensure that it is cooked well done (above 71*C)

2)    Place sauted mushrooms on burger patty, then top with cheese.  Place steamer lid on top of patty and steam until cheese is melted and mushrooms are warm.

3)  Meanwhile, garnish bun with garlic mayo on both sides and lettuce on bottom half of burger.  

4)  Top beef patty with bacon and place lettuce on bottom half of bun.  Garnish with pickle.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35271" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.  

2. Taste for seasoning.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35272" image="">1) Remove and discard stem, cut letuce in quarters, then shave off thin strips.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.

Average weight of a head of Iceberg is 470g with 10% yield loss for core and outer leaves. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35273" image="">1) Drain liquid from pickles.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35305" image="">1)  Combine mustards, anchovies, garlic, capers, red wine vinegar, water and seasoning in appropriate sized vessel, or in bowl of blender.  Blend well to combine.

2)  With blender or motor of immersion blender running, slowly begin incorporating oil.  Continue slowly adding until all oil have been incorporated.  Taste for seasoning.

3)  Store in appropriate sized vessel and lable, date, refrigerate.   

***  This dressing should be more of a vinniagrette than a traditional thick caesar dressing.  Do not add a crap ton more oil to thicken.

Allergens:

mustard
sulphites
fish/shellfish
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35313" image="">1) Toss romaine lettuce and croutons together in bowl with dressing.  Place greens on plate. 

2) Top with parmesan cheese, croutons and lemomn wedge.  Serve immidiately.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35713" image="">1)  Dredge Chicken Breast in house rub.  

2)  Placed dredged breast on parchment lined baking sheet.

3)  Repeat until production for the day is complete.  

4)  Label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35714" image="">1)  Dredge chicken breast in cajun spice and grill until 50% cooked and starting to char and blacken.  Put in oven until cooked through.  

2)  Meanwhile, toast bun on grill and dress bottom of bun with mayonnaise, lettuce, red onion, and tomato.  Put chicken back on grill and top with cheese. Place under steamer lid to reheat chicken and melt cheese, about 2 minutes.

3)  Place on top of bottom bun with toppings and close bun.  Garnish with dill pickle and serve immidiately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: robocoupe
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43641" image="">1)  Cut butter into equal size chunks.  Reserve.

2)  In medium sauce pot, add maple syrup, cinnamon and salt.  Bring maple syrup to 115*C (240*F).

3)  Take maple syrup off heat, add butter carefully a few chunks at a time while stirring.  When all butter is added, place in stand mixer with a whisk attachment.  Starting on slowest speed, and moving up to high speed, whip butter and maple syrup until its full incorporated.  Mixture may look somewhat runny still.

4)  Place in appropriate container and allow to cool.  Label, date, refrigerate after it&apos;s cool, lid tightly.  Should last about 2 weeks.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Take off stems of jalapenos.  Remove pits of avocado and scoop flesh from skin.  Place all ingredients except oil in 20 L cambro container.  

2)  Blend well with immersion blender until a smooth puree consistency is reached.  

3)  Slowly begin adding oil, a little at a time until all oil has been added.  Taste for seasonining.


-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43677" image="">1)  Place appropriate amount of salad greens in bowl.  Add Santa Fe Salad portion and 30 ml ladle of vinaigrette.  Combine well.

2)  Garnish salad with crispy tortilla strips and lime wedge.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43746" image="">1) Add dressing to greens, cucumber, carrot, tomatoes, red pepper and mix well. Use just enough dressing to coat the salad.

2) Top with sunflower seeds and radish. Serve immediately.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45231" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46833" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46864" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Be sure to make shred from other Iceberg lettuce preps
3. evenly slice lettuce 3 mm thick
4. Cover with wet brown paper towel to stop oxidization   

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46865" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47322" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Combine well.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-47390" image="">1) Cut Baguette in to 1/4 lengths, and make trough like indent on bottom piece.

2) Ladle warm tomato sauce in the trough, place a meatball on top of the sauce, top with two slices of havarti.

3) Place bottom half with sauce and meatballs on parchment lined pie pan. Bake in deck oven for 1 minutes to melt cheese a little bit.

4) While baking warm top half of baguette on flattop, crust side down. Should get slightly crispy, but not hard.

5) Remove bottom half from oven when cheese is melted and meatballs are hot, top with arugula and top bun. Cut on bias. Serve.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50323" image="">1) Fully cook the meat patty

2) Spread garlic mayo on top and bottom of bun, and iceburge lettuce on bottom

3) Place burger patty on flat top, top with blue cheese crumble, and let it melt so it&apos;s a bit gooey, and top with caramelized onion and place on lettuce. Place top bun on top skewer with bamboo toothpick and garnish with pickle spear. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50415" image="">1) Spread the butter to the bread.

2) Put the bread to the flat top, add cheese and mushrooms, cook for 3 minutes or until the bread is golden brown.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50436" image="">1. Finely chop parsely.
2. Combine all ingredients


Note: Ranch Dressing can also be a subtitute to this dressing on the salad.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50462" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all ingredient well. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50465" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Wipe chick breasts clean of lemon and herb mix.
2. Toss in oil and hot sauce.
3. Cook to internal temperature of 165F.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50466" image="">Grill up the marinated chicken. 

Brush the cooked chicken with Franks Hot Sauce. 

Toast up the bun.

Put together the sandwich with the blue cheese dressing, the glazed chicken, and the lettuce.

Serve with the pickle spear on the side.   </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50485" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1) Roughly chop onion in to bit size pieces, add to robocoupe and puree.

2) Add all other ingredients to a bowl and mix well with whisk, and season to taste with salt.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50488" image="">1) Unwrap smoked brisket, place on meat slicer, and cut to 1/8&quot; slices.

2) Place in an appropriate sized container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50491" image="">1) Butter one side on each piece of rye, and place on the flattop.

2) Put smoked meat on the flattop, drizzle 1-2 tbsp water over the meat to create steam, heat it through.

3) Place saurkraut on flat top and drizzle with 1-2 tbsp of water to create steam, heath through

4) Apply Russian dressing to both sides of the bread while on the flattop, place swiss chesse on 1 side of bread, top with hot smoked meat. top with Saurkraut.

5) place other slice of bread on top of saurkraut &amp; toast until golden on both sides

6) Once the bread is crispy and brown, move to cutting board. Slice diagonally, corner to corner. Place on the plate and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50496" image="">1. Toss romaine with dressing.
2. Arrange the lettuce on a plate
3. Slice the eggs into sections
4. Cut lemon and tomatoes into wedges
5. Place shrimp on the lettuce then garnish with tomato wedges, hardboiled eggs olives and lemon wedges.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50504" image="">1) Place shaved beef on flat top and cook until starting to brown, add caramelized onion, and sauteed peppers.

2) On bottom piece of baguette, spread garlic mayo, place warmed up beef, onions and peppers. Break the cheddar, and provalone slices in half, and top filling with alternating halves of cheddar and provalone to cover top.

3) Place top of baguette on flat top, crust side down, until it&apos;s warm and starting to get crispy, but not hard.

4) Place place bottom piece with all fillings and cheese on parchment lined flash pan, put in deck oven for 2-3 minutes or until cheese is fully melted.

5) Combine top and bottom of sandwich, cut on a bias and serve.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50506" image="">1) Cut peppers in half, remove stem, seeds, and white rib/membrain. Slice peppers in to 1/8&quot; julien pieces.

2) In a large pan, heat oil on high, add peppers and season. Cook until tender and starting to brown.

3) Cool spread out on bakeing sheet. Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50546" image="">1) Butter one side of 2 slices of the sourdough bread, place on flattop butter side down.

2) Spread the spiced jelly over both sides, and place two slices of cheese on both sides.

3) Cook on flat top till bread is browning and starting to be crispy, and cheese is melted.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50574" image="C:\TracRite\Cobb Salad.jpg">1. Process veg: dice cucumber 
Julienne romaine. 
Slice green onions to bias.
Half grape tomatoes.

2.Cook bacon. Set aside to cool and crumble or cut into small pieces.Dice avocado.

3. Cook eggs, allow to cool and peel and cut into quarters

4. Toss lettuce with dressing.

5. Put dressed romaine on a plate. In rows top with the bacon,sliced chicken, hardboiled eggs, blue cheese, avocado and green onions.



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50739" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Combine half of apples and all of the water, sugar, lemon juice, and vanilla extract. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the apples and heat until about 8-10 minutes.  Thicken with corn starch slurry.

cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50798" image="">1) Spread maple butter on each side of the bread.

2) Lay it on pre-heated flat top.

3) Lay 3 sliced swiss cheese and spread apple compote.

4) Once cheese is melted, put top bread, make sure bread has toasted and turned golden brown.

5) Slice into bias and serve.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50822" image="">1) Grill 2 small pieces of butterflied and separated chicken breast.

2) Spred mayo on bun, add lettuce and caramelized onion ,stack chicken,cheese, pineapple, ham, bacon, cheese and chicken in that order.

3) put in quick oven for melting cheese</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50889" image="">1)  Grill beef patty to well done (70*C)

2)  Meanwhile, run bun through toaster and spread top side with mayo.  When patty is nearly cooked through, brush with BBQ sauce, top with cheese melt fully, add bacon. close sandwich with top half of bun garnish with pickle spear.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50894" image="">1) Add dressing to greens and mix well.

2) Top with cucumber, carrots, sunflower seeds, tomatoes, radish, red pepper.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55118" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Preheat oven to 300F (low fan)

2) Cut roma tomatoes in half LENGTHWISE.

3) Gently toss with remaining ingredients.

4) Place cut side up on a baking sheet, place in oven for 90 minutes.

5) Tomatoes should be dried but have some moisture remaining.

6) Do not store more than 2 high so tomatoes do not get crushed.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56459" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Add all ingredients, except oil in a cambro.

2. Using immersion blender blend all ingredients well. Slowly add oil in a steady stream while blending.

3. Adjust seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57370" image="">1. Slice shallots lengthwise into long strips using a knife or mandoline.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-58362" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Smash black peppercorns slightly.  

2)  Combine water, crushed black pepeprcorns, bay leaf, sugar, garlic cloves, onion, rosemary, thyme, salt and lemon (make sure to give the lemons a good squeeze before throwing in the mix)

3)  Bring brine to a boil and stir to ensure that salt and sugar are dissolved.  Put mixture in blast chiller to cool.

4)  When brine has cooled COMPLETELY, add turkey breast.  Ensure breasts stay in brine by weighing them down with a tray from the servery.  

5)  Allow breast to brine for 6 hours.

6)  Roast in 325*F oven until browned and probe thermometer reaches 70*C (158*F).

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
</Recipes>
