<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9741" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.gather and clean ingredients.
2.Slice
3.Lable and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:NA

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size required
3.place in container, label and store in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes
2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well
3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26076" image="">1. Combine onion, bay leaf and cloves in cheese cloth, tie up tight.

2. Place milk and cheese cloth bundle in large sauce pot. Bring to a simmer, then turn off heat. Allow to infuse for 10 minutes

3. Remove cheese cloth bundle. Keep warm

4. Add butter to clean sauce rondeau. Melt butter until it starts generating bubbles, cook until bubbles stop and water is cooked out.

5. Take butter off heat and add flour, a little at a time until smooth and white roux forms.

6. Add milk while still off heat a little at a time being sure to incorporate, well, with whisk before adding more milk.

7. Add bechamel back into medium low heat until it simmers. Allow to simmer, stirring frequently with spatula (ensure to scrape bottom, the flour loves to stick to the bottom of the pan!) for 15-20  minutes.

8. Add salt &amp; pepper mix, parm, havarti and mozzarella. Stir well until evenly incorporated.

9. Allow to cool in appropriate vessel. Label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26077" image="">1. Combine softened butter, garlic, parsley, lemon juice and salt &amp; pepper mix in bowl of mixer with paddle attachement on medium low, stir to combine
2. Add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

Allergens:

No known priority allergens</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26170" image="">1. Pre heat grill to medium high
2. Place naan bread portion over grill. Get grill marks, then flip about 2 minutes. Brush with garlic butter and serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26196" image="">1. Combine lemon juice, lime juice, vinegar, dijon, shallot, garlic, sugar, and salt and pepper mix in blender. Combine on medium speed
2. Slowly incorporate oil to create an emulsification. Add chopped parsley.  Check for seasoning
3. Transfer to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26216" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1.place a strainer in the kettle. If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone. If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher. You will regret life if you do not do this step. Trust me.

2. Fill large pot or steam kettle with water at least 6x water to pasta ratio, turn heat to high and bring the water to a FULL boil.

3. Once water is boiling reduce heat and add pasta. Stir stir every few minutes to make sure pasta does not stick. Cook until pasta is al dente, soft but with a bit of a bite.
APPROX 7 MINUTES

4. Drain water and stir in lots of ice, stirring constantly to fully cool all pasta. Once fully cooled be sure to drain any excess water. Then add oil and stir 

5.Store the now cooled pasta: labeling and rotating this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26226" image="">1)  In large rondeau over medium-lowheat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and fry until garlic is golden brown.  Ensure to cook garlic until it is no longer bitter to taste.  Add chili flakes and fry for about 30 seconds - 1 minute more.

2)  Add crushed tomatoes and bring to a simmer.  Add seasoning and simmer 5 minutes more.  Take off heat.

3)  Add tomato sauce to appropriate vessel and puree with immersion blender until smooth.  Label, date, refrigerate. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26229" image="">1)  In large pot, bring water and salt to a boil

2)  bring water down to a simmer and gently cook lasagna noodles, being careful not to rip or tear.

3)  Strain noodles, allow to cool slightly and add oil to ensure that noodles will not stick together.

4)  reserve for lasagna, or store in appropriate vessel and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26231" image="">1)  Chop thyme and rosemary finely.  Combine w/ butter, roasted garlic puree, lemon juice, chili flakes, s&amp;p mix.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Dairy
Sulphite
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26234" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Preheat oven to 375*F.  Pull out garlic butter to soften,  or heat slightly in steamer, covered with plastic wrap until it is spreadable.

2. Slice bread in half horizontally.

3. Spread bread generously w/ roasted garlic butter.  Top both sides with parm cheese and bake on baking sheet for 15-20 minutes or until bread is crusty on the outside and soft in the middle and cheese is melted.

4. Yield should be 16 pieces (cut down the middle lengthwise. Then cut those pieces into 4).

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26307" image="">1)  Remove outside flat from packaging and blot dry with paper towl.

2)  Combine oil, S&amp;P, herbs to make a paste.  Rub meat generously at least one day before if possible.

3)  Preheat oven to 450*F

4)  Put beef in roasting pan and roast for 10-15 minutes.  Turn down heat to 225*F and roast until a probe thermometer inserted into the middle of meat registers 50*C.  Reserve juices.  

5)  Allow beef to rest for at least 20 minutes and serve.  If using for sandwiches, put in cooler on drain rack and slice as needed.    

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26308" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 375*F

2)  Place bones on roasting pan or baking sheet and place in oven to roast until golden brown, about 2 hours.  Ensure to move bones around and rotate pan to ensure bones are evenly browned.

3) Once roasted, place bones in large stock pot or steam kettle.  Cover bones with water until just a small amount of bones are sticking out of water.  Bring to a simmer.

4)  Once a simmer is achieved, skim any impurities that rise to the top.  Continue skimming and simmering for at least four hours.  

5)  Add rough chopped onion, celery, and carrot and bay leaf to stock.  Allow to simmer for another 4-8 hours (or overnight).

6)  Remove stock from heat.  Remove bones with tongs and reserve.  Using a pitcher and fine chinous, strain stock into appropriate vessel.  Bones can be covered again with water to make remoulage.   </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26309" image="">1)  Using the roasting pan from the roast beef, put pan on stove top burner over medium heat.  Allow juices to caramelize.  Discard beef fat that seperates from juices.  Add onion to pan and begin scraping and allow onion to deglaze pan.  

2)  When onions are soft, add stock, thyme, rosemary, and allow mixture to reduce by half.

3)  Add seasoning and taste.  Adjust seasoning if necessary.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26384" image="">1)  Soak navy beans in cold water overnight in fridge, ensuring to cover beans by at least 2-3 inches of water.

2)  The next day, drain soaked beans and add to large pot.  Add water, rough chopped carrot, celery and onion.  DO NOT SEASON!

3)  Bring to a gentle simmer, skimming any impurities that comes to the top.  Simmer until beans are cooked through, about 15-20 minutes.  

4)  Carefully drain, trying not to squish beans.  Pick out vegetables and bay leaf and discard.

5)  Cool on baking tray.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26436" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F

2)  In large mixing bowl, combine butternut squash, canola oil and seasoning.  Mix well to distribute.

3)  Spread evenly on baking sheet(s) and roast in oven until sugars begin to caramalize and squash softens, about 25 minutes.  Ensure to rotate pans a stir product to evenly roast.

4)  Reserve for service or further recipe.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26453" image="">1)  In a sauce pot, heat oil to 70*F

2)  Put basil in jug of vitamix and carefully pour warm oil into vitamix with it running on med-low setting.

3)  Once oil is safely added, puree on med. high.

4)  Filter through fine chinoise.  Label, date, refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26454" image="">1)  In large rondeau or tilt kettle over medium high heat, add chili flakes and oil.  Allow to infuse for 1 minute.

2)  Add diced red onion and saute until soft, 5-8 minutes.  Add garlic and saute 1 minute more.  Add roasted butternut squash, zucchini and tomatoes and saute until warm.  Turn off heat and add chard, spinach and stir until wilted.  Add basil oil, basil and stir to incorporate.

3)  Add to serving vessel and serve warm.  Top w/ parm if guest requests it.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26459" image="">1)  Spread some tomato sauce on the bottom of a 2&quot; hotel pan. 
-Add oven ready lasagna noodles to cover.

-Add vegetable mixture to cover.

-Add layer of noodles then more tomato sauce.  

-Add noodles then cheese sauce.

-Repeat until hotel pan is nearly full.

2)  Top off layers with mozza.  Wrap tightly.  

3) Bake in a 375*F oven for 30-45 minutes.  

Uncover and bake until sauce is bubbling and cheese is melted and brown.   minutes or so.

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28314" image="">1)  In tilt kettle over medium high heat, add oil.  Once oil is hot add onions and saute until beginning to soften and  caramalize.  Add seasoning and hold for service, or put in shallow hotel pan and chill in cooler.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28362" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28393" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-28396" image="">serve in the indicated proportions 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28989" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in: SAUCE|Mayo|Vegan

Method:

1) Drain chick peas through strainer. Retain chick peas fir recipe or use.

2) This will yeild 1L of aquafaba to keep for recipes if needed, if not discard.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32656" image="">1)  Bring water up to a boil.  Add concentrate.  Stir throughly to combine.  Use immidiately or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33557" image="">1)  Combine all well.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33858" image="">1)  In large rondeau or on flat top grill over medium heat, add oil and butter.  When butter is melted, add chopped shallot and infuse in oil and butter for about 2 minutes.

2)  Add sliced mushrooms and increase heat to high.  Brown mushrooms and season with salt and pepper.  DO NOT CROWD MUSHROOMS OR ELSE THEY WILL NOT BROWN.  YOU MAY HAVE TO WORK IN BATCHES.

3)  Once all mushrooms are browned, add all back to rondeau.  Add red wine and simmer until wine has reduced.  Add warm veg stock.  allow to simmer an additional 10 minutes.  

4)  Turn heat to low and incorporate cream.  Stir well to incorporate.  Season to taste with S+P.  It may be necessary to thicken gravy w/ corn starch slurry.  Add at your descretion.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33887" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 425*F

2)  In a large mixing bowl, add beets, oil and S+P.  Combine well and put on parchment lined baking trays.

3)  Cover with aluminium foil and put in oven.  Roast for 45 minutes to 1 hour or until beets are fork tender, but not mushy.  

4)  Slips peels off of beets and chop into bite size chunks.  Toss with honey and tarragon and season to taste.  Hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-33889" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-33891" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35305" image="">1)  Combine mustards, anchovies, garlic, capers, red wine vinegar, water and seasoning in appropriate sized vessel, or in bowl of blender.  Blend well to combine.

2)  With blender or motor of immersion blender running, slowly begin incorporating oil.  Continue slowly adding until all oil have been incorporated.  Taste for seasoning.

3)  Store in appropriate sized vessel and lable, date, refrigerate.   

***  This dressing should be more of a vinniagrette than a traditional thick caesar dressing.  Do not add a crap ton more oil to thicken.

Allergens:

mustard
sulphites
fish/shellfish
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35337" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: Milk
Dairy

Method:

1)  Preheat oven to 300*F

2)  In appropriate sized pot, combine water, garlic, shallot and thyme bring to a simmer, then take off heat and allow to infuse for about 20 minutes.  Strain out aromatics and add cream. Reserve warm.

3)  Combine cornmeal and salt.  Pour cornmeal mixture into stock and cream while whisking constantly

4)  Add mixture to hotel pans, and put in oven.  bake for 45 minutes, stirring every 15 minutes.

5)  Add butter and parmesan cheese.  Taste for seasoning and reserve for service, or 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35798" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Heat oil in rondeau.  Once oil is hot, add onions and paprika.  Saute for about 5 mintues until onions begin to soften.

2. Add garlic and saute for 1 minute more.  Add tomato.  Add spinach a handful at a time, ensuring that it wilts before adding another handful.

3. Reduce heat to medium. Add drained chickpeas and oregano.  Allow to simmer, stirring occassionally, for about 30 minutes.

4. Season to taste.  Hold for service, or

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35799" image="">Allergens:

Sulphites
Soy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36050" image="">1)  Smash black peppercorns slightly.  

2)  Combine water, crushed black pepeprcorns, bay leaf, sugar, garlic cloves, onion, rosemary, thyme, salt and lemon (make sure to give the lemons a good squeeze before throwing in the mix)

3)  Bring brine to a boil and stir to ensure that salt and sugar are dissolved.  Put mixture in blast chiller to cool.

4)  When brine has cooled, add chicken breast.  Ensure breasts stay in brine by weighing them down with a tray from the servery.  

5)  Allow breast to brine for 2-4 hours.

6)  Roast chicken breast in 450*F oven until browned and probe thermometer reaches 70*C (158*F).
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36058" image="">1)  Make chicken stock as per recipe.

2)  In an appropriate sized sauce pot over medium heat, add oil.  When oil is warm, add garlic and gently saute with crushed chilis for about 1 minute.  

3)  Add stock, cream, lemon juice and dijon.  Bring to a simmer, then add butter.  

4)  Taste for seasoning.  Thicken lightly with corn starch slurry if necessary.  Hold for service, or label, date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36061" image="">1)  Put cous-cous in hotel pan.

2)  Bring water to a simmer.  Put over cous-cous and cover until cous-cous has absorbed all the water (5-10 minutes).  Fluff with a fork until tghere are no lumps and put on baking sheet to cool.

3)  When cous-cous is cool, combine with green onion, parsley, green and red pepper and viniagrette.  Taste for seasoning.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36074" image="">1)  Roast Spaghetti Squash as per recipe.

2)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onion and saute until translucent, about 2-3 minutes.  Turn heat down to medium, add chili flakes and curry powder and continue sauteing for another 5 minutes, ensuring to cook out the spices.  Add garlic puree and saute 1 minute more.

3)  Add peeled roasted spaghetti squash, coconut milk and salt and bring to a simmer.  Add spinach a handful at a time until fully incorporated.  

4)  Hold for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37057" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-37058" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-37083" image="">Caesar salad portion size is 70g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-37084" image="">Caesar salad portion size is 70g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38517" image="">1)  Brine and cook chicken breast as per recipe.

2)  Hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38518" image="">1)  Make cous-cous as per recipe.  Scoop appropriate amount of cous-cous and SERVE IT FORTH!

2)  Give yourself a hi-5</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38633" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41047" image="">1)  Peel yam with teeth.  Give yourself hi-5.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42292" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients well until full incorporated.

2)  Reserve in appropriate container for Tandori Chicken.  Label, Date, Refrigerate.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42293" image="">1)  Drain chicken legs well and put into apprpriate container.  Pour tandoori marinade over chicken legs, ensuring to get in there with your hands to disperse the marinade.  Label, date, refrigerate.

2)  Allow chicken to marinate overnight.  

3)  Be a friend to your GWH&apos;s.  Line baking pans with aluminum foil.

4)  Place perforated screens on top of baking trays in arrange chicken legs to fit.  Do not over crowd.  Discard excess marinade.

5)  Preheat oven to 180*C (350*F).  Bake for about 30 minutes, or until a probe thermomoeter inserted into the largest thigh reaches 65*C (149*F).

6)  Wheel out rack from Rationale oven and crank heat to 500*F.

7)  When oven is hot, put chicken back in.  Allow skin to blacken slightly.  Ensure that chicken legs reach internal temperature of 71*C (160*F).  

8)  Hold hot for service. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42317" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 375*F.

2)  Cut spaghetti squash in half and scoop out the seeds.

3)  Rub flesh of squash with oil and season with salt and pepper.  Place flesh side down on parchemnt lined baking tray and put in oven.  

4)  Roast for 25-30 minutes, or until squash flesh is tender and peel comes off easily.  Scoop out roasted squash and discard peel.  Reserve for recipe, or label date, refrigerate.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-42351" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:Dairy, Wheat/gluten, egg
Method:

1. Combine cornbread mix and water.  Incorporate thawed corn, diced jalapeno and shredded cheddar cheese and incorporate into batter.  Reserve for making corn bread.

2. In a parchment lined 2&quot; hotel pan spread out cornbread batter to fill 1/4 way up the pan, pressout till even and in all the corners 

3. Bake in a 325F oven for 35-40 minutes, use a tooth pick to c&quot;cake test&quot; bread to ensure doneness, may require another 5-10 minutes

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43704" image="">1)  Pull off stems of chilis and shake out seeds as best you can.  Place in frying pan over medium heat and toss until fragrant, about 4-5 minutes.  Add stock, raisins and orange juice and simmer until chilis rehydrate, about 15 minutes.

2)  Drain chili mixture, ensuring to save liquid.  

3)  Transfer chilis mixture to vitamix, add chipotles and puree.  Scrape out contents with spatula and reserve.

4)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onions.  Saute until beginning to softenthen add diced poblano&apos;s and yam.  Saute 2 minutes more.  Add cumin, oregano and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.

5)  Add pureed chilis and soy sauce and continue to saute for about 2 minutes.  Add reserved chili hydrating liquid, tomatos, drained kidney beans, drained black beans, and drained hominy.  Stir well and add salt and pepper.

6)  Bring to a simmer, reduce to low, cover and cook, stirring occassionally until yams are tender, about 1 hour.  Continue checking chili and adding water if it looks like it&apos;s getting dry.

7)  If possible, make one day ahead to allow flavors to develop.  

8)  Reheat chili to at least 60*C.  Top with chunks of cornbread batter and bake @350*F until cornbread is cooked through.  Serve with serrano sour cream and green onion.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43710" image="">1)  Using the slicer machine, set dial to #17 and slice tofu lengthwise into chunks.

2)  Cover with seasoned flour, then egg wash, then panko.

3)  Fry @ 350*F for about 2 minutes or until warm throughout and golden brown.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43911" image="">1)  Cook Spaetzle accoring to package directions.  Reserve for service.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44728" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Products related to this Prep recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.gather igredients
2.chop leaves 
3.wash and dry
4.label and fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44962" image="">1)  Add oil to flat top and wait until it reaches smoke point.

2)  Add spaetzle to flat top and sear until browned. Add salt and pepper and dijon mustard.  Mix well.

3)   Add to hot holding vessel and hold for service.  Just before service add fresh chopped parsley.

Allergens:

Wheat 
Gluten
Mustard


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44963" image="">1)  Use a #6/white handled scoop, and use two scoops for a portion.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44968" image="">Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat 
Soy 
Egg
Dairy/Milk
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45136" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45164" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-48489" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

Combine oil and garlic in a pot. Bring the garlic and oil to a boil over medium high heat and immediately turn heat off. Allow product to cool in oil.

Once cool strain and reserve garlic oil and confit garlic separately.

***Note***

This recipe only costs out the confit garlic portion of the recipe with the garlic flavoured oil becoming a *free* by-product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they do not last very long.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50517" image="">1) Remove softer fronds of the dill from the harder stems. Chop well for garnish.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50522" image="">1) In a large bowl, toss carrots in oil, dill, maple syrup, vinegar, salt and pepper.

2) On a parchment lined baking tray, roast carrots at 400f until starting to brown, and cooked through.

3) Sprinkle parsley and toasted pumpkin seeds over carrots and put in vessel to hold hot for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50689" image="">Saute zucchini and season.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51285" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-51467" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
PREP RECIPE

There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55127" image="">1) In Robot Coupe slice onion and zucchini.

2) In Robot Coupe shred carrots.

3) Drain roasted peppers and slice.

4) In rondo over medium heat add olive oil and seasoning. Add onion, garlic and carrot and sweat until softened and fragrant.

5) Add zucchini and peppers and cook until just warmed through (3-4 minutes).

6) Check for seasoning.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
</Recipes>
