<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9765" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut into small dice, approx 1/4 inch
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.wash and cut to size wanted
3.place in container, label and store

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26112" image="">1. Preheat grill to high. Pre heat oven to 350F

2. Brush sausage with oil. Put sausage on grill to sear. Once crisp and has grill lines, remove from grill and put in oven until hot throughout, about 10 - 15 minutes

2. Cut to appropriate serving size and put in serving vessel.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

2)  Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes.  Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and store in appropriate vessel.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26713" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-28314" image="">1)  In tilt kettle over medium high heat, add oil.  Once oil is hot add onions and saute until beginning to soften and  caramalize.  Add seasoning and hold for service, or put in shallow hotel pan and chill in cooler.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35773" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41913" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Measure all and get your ingredients together.

2. Place everything into a medium pot and turn your burner on to medium low.

3. Bring to a low simmer and turn down a tad so it barely bubbles. Simmer for about 40 minutes.

4. After 40 minutes, turn off and let the oil sit and cool down.

5. Grab a cointainer, chinoise(china cap) and grease filter and filter the oil from the other ingredients. The oil should be a nice flourescent red color.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42504" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43583" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

*NOTE THE GHOST OIL IN THIS RECIPE IS FOR NUTRITION EVALUATION PURPOSES, THIS IS THE FRYER OIL, WE ARE NOT ADDING OIL TO THE FINISHED PRODUCT*

Allergens: 
Method:

1. -THIS RECIPE IS A TOUGHT ONE; CRISPY SHALLOTS ARE AN ART FORM. PLEASE FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS CAREFULLY, AND GET CHEF TO DO THIS WITH YOU ONCE BEFORE TRYING IT ON YOUR OWN.

2. Mandoline Shallots into thin rings - Approx. 2mm.

3. Created a Salt/Water Brine at 10% salt (100g Salt: 1000ml Water). Soak mandolined Shallots in Brine for 10 minutes. Rinse once with clean water, and let rest for 20 minutes.

4. At 325-350F, fry Shallots until golden. Shallots will continue cooking once you take them out - and set them on a tray lined with paper towel. IMPORTANT: as soon as you take the Shallots out of the fryer, and onto their blotting surface of paper towel, you will need to move them around so that they don&apos;t clump up and form balls or nests (which, once dried, will not come apart easy). THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT TO GETTING A GOOD PRODUCT.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43729" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1)  Combine lemon juice, orange juice, soy sauce, brown sugar, ginger and garlic puree&apos;s.  Mix very well.  Add chicken thighs and marinate for 4-6 hours.

2)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  Add chicken thighs skin side up to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up chicken thighs.  Do not cover skin.  Roast chicken thighs until biggest thigh registers 150*F on an instant read thermometer.

3)  Remove thighs and add to hot holding vessels.  Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining marinade and pour over chicken.
Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44916" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED
STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredient
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45150" image="">Average raw weight of a bone in chicken thigh is 170g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49662" image="">Method:
wash zucchini
trim ends 
cut into 1&quot; thick rounds ( if zucchini is over 2&quot; in diameter, cut in half lenghtwise
toss with oil, salt, pepper
grill over high heat until marked
remove from heat, allow to cool 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50424" image="">1) Coat mushrooms in oil and seasoning. Preheat oven to 375f.

2) Place mushrooms on parchment lined baking sheets evenly, only single layer, use multiple pans if needed, place whole rosemary and thyme sprigs over mushrooms. 

3) Roast in oven about 15 mintues, carefully drain excess mushroom juices from the pan,  and respread out mushrooms if needed. Return to oven and continue roasting an other 30 minutes, or until mushrooms are brown and tender.

4) Toss with chopped parsley and move to hot holding vessel. Hold hot for service.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50473" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:
-Short Rib Papperdelle
-Boneless Beef Shortrib

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Season beef with salt and pepper.  Preheat oven to 225*F.

2)  In rondo or tilt skillet over high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add beef and sear well on all sides, and place in hotel pan.

3) In same rondo or skillet sweat onion, garlic and carrot stirring often until fragrant.

4) Add tomato paste and stir 1-2 minutes.

5) Add red wine vinegar and beef stock and bring to a boil.

6)  Place warm liquid over beef until it comes about half way up side of beef.  Place parchment paper on top and cover with lid.  Place in preheated oven and braise overnight or until very tender.

7)  Remove from oven and let cool down in liquid.  Strain braising liquid and reduce until thick and almost syrupy, about 2/3&apos;s.  Reserve.  Taste for seasoning.  

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50677" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Warm vinegar, sugar and chili in a pot until sugar is dissolved. Cool completely.

2) Cut cucumber into 3 equal pieces. Slice cucumber using mandoline turning on all 4 sides so you get ribbons of cucumber but no seeds.

3) Mix cucumbers and cold pickling liquid.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53994" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Toss the peppers with canola, salt and pepper and roast in a hot oven on a parchment lined sheet pan until lightly browned and hot throughout. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54743" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Peel and dice the russet potatoes. Use in recipes.

Store in a pail of water to prevent oxidation/browning. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56955" image="">THIS IS A PRODUCT RECIPE, final product handed to the customer..

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Scoop chowder into appropriate container 
2. Garnish with dill

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57145" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather ingredents

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate size/shape for recipe use

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57146" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather inredents.

2. Remove stem/core/seeds. discard

3. Cut into apropriate shape/size for recipe use


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60385" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large pot heat oil, add garlic, and ginger, sautee 1 minute until fragrent.

2. Add rice, sautee 1 minute

3. pour in veg stock and water season with salt and umami dust, Stir and bring to a boil uncovered. Once boil is reached turn heat down to low, cover and simmer 1 hour, stirring occasionally.

4. After 1 hour, check for consistancy and seasoning, Adjust as needed. Add the shrimp and chopped kimchii at the end.

5. Crispy shallots, fresh green onion and chili oil are for garnish.

HOT HOLD/SERVE


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-60546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Dice potatoes, Carrots, Celery, Onion into 1/4 inch cubes. Thinly slice fennel (reserve some of the fronds for garnish) Set aside. cut rock fish into large dice (1/2 inch) Break smoke salmon chunks up slightly. Gather and scale all ingredients.

2. In a large rondeau/Pot add a small amout of oil to sautee off the Mire poix (celery,carrot,onion),fennel No Colour just till slightly soft.

3. add butter to pan and let melt, add in flour to make a light roux and whisk in fish stock. Allow to simmer 5-6 minutes while gently whisking to prevent lumps and allowing to slightly thicken.

4. Add thyme bundle and bay leaf


5. Add fish in and alow the rock fish to cook out in the broth. Reduce to a low flame and let simmer so the flovours come together (20-30 minutes)

6. Add heavy cream just before removing from heat.

7. Add 3g of kale to the bottom of the bowl and Top with hot soup for service (if put into the batch of soup the soup will turn grey and is very unappatizing) Garnish with a few strands of fennel fronds.

Hot hold/serve imediately.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61306" image="">1) Cut tofu in to 150g, steak style portions. (long flat rectangles)

2) Season with salt, pepper and oil. Grill to add grill marks.

3) Cool and keep for service time. Service time, heat to 74c and keep for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61788" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-61789" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Cut veg into long slices 1-2 cm thick.
2. Grill on both sides to get some grill marks and smokey flavour.
3. Remove from grill and toss together with olive oil and salt &amp; pepper.

Cool, label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62501" image="">PREP RECIPE
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep is used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. All veg should be 1/4&quot; dice (except jalapenos which can be minced).

2. Adjust seasoning and keep cool.

Label and store.
Rotate this item with older product.
Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
