<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="R-8355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Stretch dough to 16&quot;

2. Spread tomato sauce evenly across dough leaving a half inch boarder for the crust.

3. top with mozza cheese evenly covering the base of the dough.

4. place slices of boccancini across the base of the dough on top of the mozza.

5. Using a lightly floured peel transfer the raw pizza into the forno to bake (aprox 3-4 minutes) crust should be baked through and golden on the edges.

6. Again using the peel remove the fully baked pizza from the forno oven. On the cutting board using the pizza knife cut into 8 equal slices, carnish with fresh basil and serve imediately.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-8357" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Stretch dough

Spread cheese(s)

Apply toppings

Bake until the bottom is a mottled golden brown and cheese is bubbly and melted. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Pulse jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well.  

3. Adjust seasoning.

*Store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26068" image="">

PREP RECIPE

1. Over medium heat, heat oil

2. Add onions and stir to evenly incorporate in the oil

3. Allow onions to continue to cook over medium-high heat until natural sugars begin to caramelize and onions begin to soften

4. Turn heat to medium low and granulated sugar. Continue to cook onions for 40 minutes while scraping and distributing caramelized sugar over the onions

5. Season with salt &amp; pepper. Cool and add to appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34541" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

*** for yeilding purposes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34666" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. on a parchment lined sheet pan place sausage in a even layer

2. cook at 350F untill cooked through

3. Cool and reserve for service

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42012" image="">1)  Roasted Serrano peppers on grill until deeply charred.  Reserve for making sour cream

2)  Combine sour cream, roasted serrano peppers, lime juice, cilantro and salt in container for vita mix.  Process on medium until well combined.

3)  Taste for seasoning and label, date, refrigerate.

Allergens:

Milk/Dairy</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42160" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix. 

Use a blender if you like, it is easier. A whisk will work too. 

***Please make sure to mix tahini before you use it as it settles and separates. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42354" image="">

- Once your Pork Butts are ready to prepare, score their tops (THE FATTY PART) with cross-hashed cuts up to 1CM deep, OK?!

- At this point, rub the Pork &quot;Butts&quot; with the dry spices (Cumin, Cinnamon, Cayenne +), salt, and achiote. The Achiote paste can also be mixed into a little bit of orange juice or pineapple juice to make it easier to rub in.

- In Deep Hotel Pans, place all of the butts in there with the Onions, Garlic, and wet ingredients (Water, Pineapple Juice, Orange Juice) - THEN - pre-heat your oven to 275-300 Degrees (F). 

The level of the wet ingredients should come halfway up pork, add more water if need be. Wrap with foi

Cook for 4.5-7 hours.  At 4 hours, you can check to see how this process is going. 


Label/Date/Store!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46419" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Prepare all ingredients in advance.

Parsley is to be coarsely chopped and used quite abundantly, as though it were a green and not particularly a herb. 

Quarter sundried tomatoes.

 top flatbread with both cheeses, sundried tomatoes, and chickpeas. 

Bake until the crust is crispy and mottled golden brown underneath and cheese is melted.

Top the finished flatbread with the tahini drizzle and the coarsely chopped parsley. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Stretch out the dough to 16&quot;

2. Spread the pesto evenly across the base of the dough leaving a half inch border for the crust.

3. Evenly spread the mozza across the dough covering the pesto. 

4. On top of the mozza spread out the artichokes, sauteed mushrooms, and chicken, try not to overlap the ingredents too much so all aspects are visual to the guest.

5. With a lightly floured peel, scoot the raw pizza into the forno oven and bake for 3-4 minutes (longer if needed) Crust should be cooked through and golden.

6. Again using the peel remove coocked pizza from the forno placing it on the cutting board, using the pizza knife cut into 8 even slices.

&amp;. Serve imediately and with kindness.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50533" image="">1) Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto and mozzarella cheese, then place artichoke heart pieces and caramelized onion evenly across flatbread.

2) Evenly place halved grape tomatoes around flatbread, 

3) Place on parchment lined flash pan and bake in deck oven for 3-4 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4) Once cooked, cut, sprinkle arugula and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50562" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Spread the pesto. 

Arrange toppings

Sprinkle cheese

Bake until bread and toppings are hot and cheese is melted. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50802" image="">1. Drain water and put in a container.
2.Store in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50858" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

On a prebaked flatbread, spread pesto and sprinkle veggies and olives

Bake until toppings and bread are hot and cheese is slightly melted. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53744" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Combine everything in a pail and blend with giant handblender </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54387" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE



Apply toppings in the indicated proportions

Bake until bottom of crust is mottled golden brown, cheese is melted and crust is crisping around edges. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56762" image="">Method:
- drain and rinse artichoke allow all excess moisture to drain off
- toss artichokes with olive oil, oregano &amp; basil
- hold for service
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
