<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
    <Recipe id="P-7635" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny Bravo

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Open can
        2.Drain in strainer and wash throughly
        3.Place drained beans in insert label and place in fridge
        4. Heat in steam required amount

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:90G Blue scoop

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9742" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Clean and cut leeks
        2. Toss in oil and salt + pepper
        3. Charr leeks on grill
        4. Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9756" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size required
        3.place in container, label and store in fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Products related to this Prep recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-9863" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Tip/tail the leeks save the green tips for other preps
        2. Soak in cold water to rinse off dirt
        3. cut to desired shape
        4. store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

        2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-18746" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny,

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.wash and cut to size wanted
        3.place in container, label and store

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

        n/a

        Icon:

        vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

        Method:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-25893" image="">1) Add potatoes to perforated hotel pans and put in rationale oven. Steam potatoes
        until about 85% done and a knife can be easily inserted into the potatoe with little resistance, about 15-20
        minutes.

        2) Carefully spread potatoes out on sheet pan to cool. Put on speed racks.

        3) IF APPLICABLE---When cool, tear apart by hand in rough chunks. Reserve for making classic potato salad.----
        If NOT FOR POTATO SALAD, THERE IS NO NEED TO TEAR THEM UP

        4) For service, fry potatoe chunks in 350* fryer until crispy on the outside and cooked throughout, about 4
        minutes. Alternatively, roast in 450*F oven until crispy, about 15-20 minutes.


        Allergens:

        No known priority allergens.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

        2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
        2. Mix in garlic
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26021" image="">1) Rinse quinoa in hotel pan under cold water while agitating quinoa until the water
        from the pan runs clear

        2) Place rinsed quinoa to hotel pan, with appropriate amount of water and steam until cooked, around 40 minutes.

        4) Spread out on baking tray, carve gridlines to allow quinoa to cool more quickly. Cool in fridge, store in
        appropriate vessel. Label, date, refrigerate
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26055" image="">1. Put liquid egg in hotel pan and put in rationale oven on 100% steam for 10-15
        minutes, or until the egg have cooked, but are still slightly creamy.

        2. Add to vessel. Add fresh herbs, seasoning and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26057" image="">1. Pre heaet grill to 350F/medium heaet

        2. Spread oil on grill and allow to get hot

        3. Crack egg on oil, allow whites and yolk to set. Season with salt &amp; pepper for sunny side up egg

        4. Gently flip over and cook for 15 - 30 seconds for over easy egg
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26058" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine lemon juice, salt and pepper in jug of vitamix

        2. Slowly pour in canola oil to emulsify

        3. Put in appropriate container, label, date and refrigerate

        4. Alternatively, fill up a squeeze bottle 1/3rd of the way with lemon juice, a pinch of salt and pepper, and
        the rest with romano oil. Shake it.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

        2. Puree jalapenos in robot coupe until finely minced.

        3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice.
        Mix well.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26069" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In mixing bowl, combine arugula, citrus dressing, salt &amp; pepper mix.

        2. Mix to lightly dress arugula.

        3. ONLY MIX WHAT YOU NEED. THIS DOES NOT HOLD WELL.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26136" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Prepare pickling liquid as per recipe

        2. Add red onions.

        3. Allow to pickle 24 hours if possible.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

        2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

        3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

        4. Hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

        2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

        3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1) In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high
        heat. Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot. Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not
        overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown. Taste for seasoning.

        2) Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26311" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In a large stock pot, add water and vegetables.

        2) Bring to a simmer and allow to simmer for 30-40 minutes. Carefully strain stock through fine chinoise and
        store in appropriate vessel.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26378" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. With 1/4 inch dice attachment on the robocope dice shallots and then tomatoes (so the shallots don&apos;t get
        stuck/lost make sure they are processed first), place in perferated hotel pan and let drain excess liquid out
        for 10-15 minutes.

        2. Add diced tomato and shallot and mix with puree garlic, chiffonade basil, olive oil, balsamic vinegar and S&amp;P
        in mixing bowl and mix throughly. Taste for seasoning.

        3. Check quality after 24 hours.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26380" image="">1) Preheat oven to 300F.

        2) Put almonds in oven, toast for 10 minutes. Rotate pan and stiralmonds and toast for another 5 minutes or
        until golden brown. Allow to cool.


        Allergens:

        Nuts/Treenuts
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26381" image="">1) Preheat oven to 200*F

        2) Combine all in large sauce pot. Bring to a very gentle simmer (just until you can see small bubbles forming
        rapidly)

        3) Put pot in oven for 3 hours. Strain, reserving garlic. Transfer to appropriate storing vessel and allow to
        cool.

        4) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26382" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:
        PLEASE NOTE CUT SIZE ON SWEET POTATOES IS 1/4&quot;

        1. Preheat oven to 425*F

        2. In a mixing bowl add yam, zucchini, red peppers, garlic, jalepenos, red onion, corn, chili oil and UBC house
        rub. Mix well.

        3. Put hash on baking tray or roasting pan in an even layer (DO NOT OVERCROWD PAN OR YOU WILL STEAM THE VEG
        RATHER THAN ROAST).

        4. Roast for 15-20 minutes, or until sweet potato is caramelized and cooked through. Remove from oven and let
        cool.

        5. Once cooled add hash to a large mixing bowl and combine with drained black beans, cilantro and mix well.

        6. Check seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26383" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine lime juice, mustard, garlic, cumin, and S&amp;P in jug of vitamix. Blend well.

        2. Slowly pour in oil over medium speed to create an emulsification.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26385" image="">1) Combine olive oil, lemon juice, crushed red pepper and crushed garlic and
        seasoning. Combine well with a whisk.

        2) Pour marinade over torn kale leaves. Toss to coat and refrigerate overnight in an appropriate container.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26390" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine water and salt in a large pot. Bring to a boil.

        2. Add buskwheat soba to boiling water, then turn heat down to medium and simmer noodles until tender but not
        overcooked, about 2 mins. TASTE FOR AL DENTE

        3. *Drain noodles well and ensure to rinse very, very well under cold running water, gently agitating by hand.
        This will ensure that the noodles will not overcook, and will not be sticky when stored.

        4. Mix well with sesame oil once cooled and hold for service.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26393" image="">1) Preheat deep fryer to 350*F

        2) Remove baskets from deep fryer. Ensur to have a mixing bowl and tray lined with papertowels, and a spider.

        3) Place two large handfuls of julienned tortilla strips in hot oil. Deep fry for 45s - 1 minute, or until
        tortillas are cooked through and very crispy.

        4) Retrieve with spider and drain excess oil. Season with salt in mixing bowl and place on papertowel lined pan.

        5) Place in appropriate container once cooled. Label, date, and store in a cool dry place.

        Allergens:

        Gluten
        Wheat
        soy (from tortilla)
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26476" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Egg
        milk

        Method:

        1. Pour whole liquid egg into mixing bowl.

        2. Combine cinnamon, vanilla extract, and icing sugar with egg mixture well with whisk.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26481" image="">The below looks like old info to me that req&apos;s a rework- to revisit. 3496279


        1) Put eggs in perforated hotel pan and steam in rationale oven for predetermined time.
        (2 step program)
        1 - 100% steam 147*F Preheat
        2 - 100% Steam 147*F 45 minutes. Turn on alarm notification.

        2) Load eggs and cook for program cycle.

        3) Upon receiving order from customer, simply add egg to hot water for 1 minute to reheat egg and carefully
        crack egg onto dish. Serve immediately.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Cut stem off
        3. Pick leaves off

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-26527" image="">1) Place beets in perforated tray. Steam beets until tender enough that a paring knife
        can be easily inserted into beet with little resistance. Allow to cool. When cool enough to handle, slip off
        skins and cut into bite sized portions.

        2) Season with salt and pepper and store in appropriate vessel.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-27273" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Avocado Taost.jpg">1) Grill or toast
        ciabatta until crisp and warm.

        2) Spread evenly with guacamole, than top with bruscetta mix, arugula then pickled onions.

        3) Garnish with hemp hearts.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-27275" image="C:\Users\afdaos\Desktop\Black Bean Bowl.jpg">1) Combine Quinoa with half of cumin lime
        dressing, place in bowl.

        2) In a saute pan over medium heat, add oil. Once hot, add potato hash and dressing and sauce until warm
        throughout, about 1 minute. Drop poached egg into warm water.

        3) Add chopped cilantro to hash and plate on top of warm quinoa. Place avocado on top of hash, make a well for
        the egg and put egg in. Garnish with more cilantro and serve.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-32459" image="">Allergens:

        Sulphite
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1) Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours. Ensure to store upside down.

        2) Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

        3) Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

        4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

        5) Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment. Add vanilla and whisk some more to
        incorporate.

        6) Store in appropriate container. Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-32747" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. ***This is a neutral base for any number of quiche flavourings.

        2. Whisk together the eggs, milk, cream, and salt until frothy

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35255" image="">1) Cut cucumber in quarters lenght wise, cut out seads.

        2) Cut remaining pieces in to 1.5 inch lenght pieces and cut in to 1/16th inch sticks.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35337" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: Milk
        Dairy

        Method:

        1) Preheat oven to 300*F

        2) In appropriate sized pot, combine water, garlic, shallot and thyme bring to a simmer, then take off heat and
        allow to infuse for about 20 minutes. Strain out aromatics and add cream. Reserve warm.

        3) Combine cornmeal and salt. Pour cornmeal mixture into stock and cream while whisking constantly

        4) Add mixture to hotel pans, and put in oven. bake for 45 minutes, stirring every 15 minutes.

        5) Add butter and parmesan cheese. Taste for seasoning and reserve for service, or

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35338" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) In bowl of food processor, combine half of the oil, vinegar, basil, parsely, arugula, garlic puree and
        seasoning. Process until smooth. Do not strain.

        2) Add remianing oil and STIR with a spoon or spatula to combine.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-35341" image="">1) Place warm polenta in bottom of bowl. Top with marinated kale and radish, then egg,
        and garnish with salsa verde.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-35733" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1) Toast nori by waving it over grill until it crisps up on both sides. Allow to cool.

        2) Combine half of the sesame seeds, sugar and salt in jug of vitamix blender. Blend well until combined into a
        paste. Do not over process or you will be making sesame paste, and that isn&apos;t very good.

        3) Crumble up nori very finely in vitamix. Combine ground sesame mixture, crumbled nori, and remaining sesame
        seeds and korean chili flakes.

        cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-36666" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\5 Alarm Bowl.jpg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ
        THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Preps used in this Product recipe:

        Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Start building this bowl with the beans and rice hot in the bottom of the serving vessel.

        2. Add remaining ingredients topping with poached egg and avocado fan.

        3. Drizzle with cumin lime dressing and habanero sauce..

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-38515" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 3/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice celery to 3/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure
        how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-41468" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:
        pickle|onion red

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine and boil to dissolve sugar and bring flavours out of spices and seasonings.

        2. Strain liquid before pouring over ingredient to be pickled and allow time to work its magic.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42353" image="">
        Prep:

        - Quarter Corn Tortillas. 2.5 Packages of Corn Tortillas will yield 2 Deep Hotel pans full of Corn Chips.

        - Using Paper Towel, create a large pan or bowl for draining the excess oil off of the Tortilla Chips, after
        they&apos;ve come out of the Deep Fryer.

        - At 350 Degrees (F) in the Deep Fryer, fry NO MORE THAN HALF OF A STACK OF CORN TORTILLAS (QUARTERED) at a
        time.

        - Using a Spider, or Long Tongs - KEEP TORTILLAS MOVING AT ALL TIMES.

        - Depending on how dark the Deep Fryer oil is, fry the Tortilla Chips until they are brown (keeping in mind that
        they will cook for a little while longer once they&apos;ve been taken out of the fryer.

        - As soon as the chips are out drying, salt lightly using the Windsor coarse grain salt. The salt will only
        stick during this stage of production - be sure to catch it!

        Label/Date/Store

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-42425" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Slice cucumber to 1/8 thinkness
        3.

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed: robocoupe
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how
        to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

        2) Label, date, refrigerate.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43719" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine all well. Put in fridge overnight to allow oats to soak up liquid. Combine with other
        fruits/garnishes as indicated in recipes.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43737" image="">1) Bring water to a rapid boil in an appropriate sized pot. Gently lower eggs into
        boiling water with a slotted spoon.

        2) Cover pot with aluminum foil and turn heat off completely. Allow eggs to sit in hot water for 8-9 minutes.

        3) Strain eggs, and shock in ice bath to stop eggs from cooking further and to make them easier to peel.

        4) When eggs are completly cool, peel them.

        5) Egg whites should be fully cooked, and yolk should be slightly runny.

        6) Store in appropriate contianer. Label, date, refrigerate.

        Allergens:

        Egg

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-43738" image="">1) Prep soba noodles as per recipe, and portion.

        2) Prepare Dobanjiang Sauce as per recipe.

        3) Place chilled soba noodles in mixing bowl and mix well with dobanjiang sauce. Place noodles in serving bowl
        and garnish with remaining vegetables. Zigzag a squirt of sauce on top of vegetables, then garnish with sesame
        and nori and soft boiled egg. Cut the egg in half and present the cut side.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-43918" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        ***This recipe does not need to be heated, put all of the ingredients in a bowl and whisk well.***

        1. Combine all well.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44392" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1.Gather ingredients
        2.in non reactive pot place everything except eggs
        3.bring to a simmer
        4. Crack egg into simmering water and cook soft
        5. pull from water and put in ice bath to cool rappedly
        6. place in container place enough cold water in container to keep eggs loose so they do not break
        7. Label and fridge

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:NA

        Utensils needed:Pot slotted spoon containers
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44429" image="">1) Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment. If you don&apos;t know
        how, ask chef or a 1st cook.

        2) Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

        3) Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

        Allergens:

        No known prioirity allergens.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44506" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:
        1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
        2. Halve the avocado and carefully remove the pit
        3. Slice into desired sizes
        4. Toss in lemon juice to prevent oxydation

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning: 1 portion is 1/4 avocado

        Utensils needed: cutting board, knife, bowl insert, mesuring cups
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Method:
        1. Gather ingredients.
        2. Put frozen corn in mixing bowl.
        3. Add other ingredients and mix.
        4. Spead out on roasting pan and bake 190C 375F for 15 minutes or till roasted (lightly coloured).
        5. Place in insert label, cover and place in warmer for service.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:30G

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Gather all ingredients.

        2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

        3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as
        chunky as possile

        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1) Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along
        the stem to remove leaves.

        2) Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
        TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. Drain the cheese
        2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
        3.
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-46842" image="">1) Rinse rice well under running water, until the water begins to run clear.

        2) Pour coconut milk and over rinsed rice and mix well.

        3) Steam for 20-25 minutes or until rice is tender.

        4) Spread out on a baking sheet to cool, or add to appropriate vessel and hold warm for service.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-48487" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Combine tomatoes, chile de arbol, garlic cloves. Add water until vegetables are just covered.

        2) Bring to boil, turn down to a simmer and continue simmering until tomatoes are soft, about 10-15 minutes.

        3) Remove vegetables by straining into a large bowl. ENSURE TO RESERVE WATER!

        4) Add vegetables to a vita mix, or puree with hand blender in an appropriatly sized vessle. Puree until smooth,
        but do not strain. Add some reserved water if you are having difficulties pureeing, or if puree is too thick.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-48488" image="">
        1) Warm tortilla shell on the flat-top grill with a small amount of oil. Grill until warm and slightly crispy.

        2) Meawhile add more oil to the grill and fry the egg.

        3) Spread refried beans on tortilla shell and place fried egg on top of beans.

        4) Top with warm Rancheros Salsa, and add mozzarella cheese, and top with chopped cilantro. Serve immediately.


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-49176" image="">makes topping for 9 portions
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-49663" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Steam beets until fork tender.

        2. Peel and chop into cubes.

        3. Combine all ingredients in food processor.

        4. Pulse until combined and smooth texture.

        5. Remove from mixer, adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:

        1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

        2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue
        this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent
        bruising.

        3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

        *Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently


    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50500" image="">1) Remove all leaves from thick stem.

        2) Stack and line stem to tip, up 10-20 leaves largest at the bottom, smallest on top. Roll the stack in to a
        tight a tube as possible. Starting at the tip of the tube, holding stem, cut super thin ribbons of leaf.

        3) Final product should be thin strips that can be used for garnish. Cut only what you need for the day, as they
        do not last very long.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50513" image="">1. Combine 3/4 frozen peaches, sugar, lemon juice. Bring to simmer at medium heat.

        2. Once liquid begins to thicken, add the rest of the peaches and heat until about 8-10 minutes. Thicken with
        corn starch slurry. (Add the cornstarch slurry incrementally, allowing the compote time to thicken between
        additions, once the desired consistency achieved, stop adding) finish with vanilla extract.

        3. Allow to cool, label, date and refrigerate or if using immediately, add to hot holding vessel.

    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50526" image="">1. Preheat grill to 350*F.

        2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up. Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg
        mixture and put on griddle. Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm
        throughout.

        3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner. Top with compote, whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing
        sugar.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50555" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Omelet.jpg">1. Preheat flat top 350*F.

        2. In one side of the flat top. Add oil, vegetables and salt Cook about 2 minutes.

        3. In the other side of the flat top. Pour the liquid egg. Once egg starts to set add the sauteed vegetables and
        cheese and folder over.

        4. Garnish with chopped parsly and serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Amanda

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Gather all ingredients and tools

        2. core out stem

        3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

        4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

        *Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50734" image="">1. Cut butternut squash to meduim dice.
        2. Fine dice sage.
        3. Mix all ingredients.
        4. Roast in 375F oven until soft for about 20minutes.
        5. Put in baine marie until service.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-50800" image="">1. Toast bread
        2. Spread ricotta
        3. Place butternut squash dice on
        4. Sprinkle pumpkin seeds
        5. Serve
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
        2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
        3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
        4. Take it off from oven.
        5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
        6. Store in a dry place until needed.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-50966" image="">Template to Cut + Paste into OC Preps:

        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.Wash Tomato in cold water
        2.Cut in half Lenght wise
        3.Container label fridge
        -cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
        knife, cutting board, storage container
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        johnny

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1. make a tasty vegetable stock
        2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53339" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Warm veg stock.

        2. Mix spices well and mix into dry couscous.

        3. Pour hot stock over couscous and cover with cling film. Wait 10 minutes.

        4. Remove film, add, diced peppers, oil &amp; lemon juice and using a fork stir well to break apart all the
        grains of cous cous.

        5. Add herbs and stir.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-53341" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Place all ingredients EXCEPT oil into Cambro/ Vitamix.

        2. Blend and slowly add oil in a steady stream.

        3. Adjust seasoning.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-53342" image="">1. Warm pita on flattop and cut into 3 equal pieces..

        2. Spread hummus onto the side of the large bowl.

        3. Place couscous in bottom of bowl.

        4. Dress spinach, cucumbers and tomatoes in dressing and place in one side of bowl.

        5. Place falafel next to vegetables, then cut pita with points facing up and top with hemp seeds and lemon wedge
        (no seeds).
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-54697" image="">
        PREP RECIPE

        There are approx. 4 lemons per pound. a lemon is cut into 8 wedges, this recipe represents this.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55098" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Gluten
        Wheat
        Soy

        Method:

        1. Make overnight oats as per recipe.

        2. Combine remaining ingredients (EXCEPT OATS) in a large cambro container and blend well with immersion
        blender. Mix well into overnight oats and let stand in the fridge overnight.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55115" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. In a large rondo over medium heat add oil and onion and cook until fragrant (2-3 minutes).

        2. Add garlic, jalepeno and all spices and continue to cook, stirring occasionally for 2-3 more minutes.

        3. Add canned tomatoes, bring to a simmer and cook stirring occasionally for 20-30 minutes.

        4. Add salt and pepper and adjust seasoning.

        5. Blits with imersion blender to smooth texture

        6.Transfer to a container, label, cool, document cooling log, and store.


        Portioning:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-55116" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Chilaquiles.jpg">1) Warm tomato sauce
        in a saute pan.

        2) Cook egg on flattop.

        3) When egg is almost cooked add tortilla chips into pan with sauce and gently fold so all chips get coated in
        sauce without breaking too many chips.

        4) Transfer to plate, add cooked egg on top.

        5) Garnish with crumbled feta, brunoise red onion &amp; cilantro.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-55117" image="">1) Place oats in bowl.

        2) Top with sliced banana, coconut cream &amp; toasted almonds.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-55548" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Cut corn tortillas in thin strips.

        2. Fry WITHOUT baskets, and use spider to drain well from oil.

        3. Season as soon as tortillas come out of oil as salt will NOT stick once they are cool.

        -store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56398" image="">
        BEFORE COMMITING TO COOKING THIS RECIPE; GATHER ALL INGREDIENTS, UTENSILS REQUIRED AND READ METHOD THOROGHULY!

        1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

        2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

        3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with serano wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac
        as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

        LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56451" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Corn Flake French Toast.jpg">1.
        Preheat grill to 350*F.

        2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up. Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in egg
        mixture then in corn flakes and put on griddle. Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden
        brown and warm throughout.

        3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner. Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.

        4. NOTE: corn flakes need to be pulsed so they are small enough to stick evenly to the bread but retain some
        texture
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56509" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Breakfast Quesadilla.jpg">1. Place
        tortilla on flattop, spread cheese evenly on both sides (this will be the glue to hold the whole thing together.

        2. Add remaining ingredients evenly over the entire surface so each bite gives you all the ingredients..

        3. Fold in half and cook on both sides until golden brown and crispy.

        4. Cut into 4 even pieces. Place crispy tortilla strips on plate and place quesadilla on top to prevent bottom
        from getting soggy.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56510" image="">1) Grill or toast ciabatta until crisp and warm.

        2) Sread evenly with guacamole, than top with salsa.

        3) Garnish with Tajin and tortilla strips.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56511" image="">1) Grill or toast ciabatta until crisp and warm.

        2) Spread evenly with guacamole, than top with roasted squash and goat cheese.

        3) Garnish with dukkah.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56637" image="">1. Preheat grill to 350*F.

        2. When an order is placed, put oil on griddle to heat up. Meanwhile, put two pieces of sliced bread in eggnog
        mixture and put on griddle. Allow toast to cook for 2-3 minutes per side, or until golden brown and warm
        throughout.

        3. Cut bread in half from corner to corner. Top with whipped coconut cream, maple syrup and icing sugar.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56687" image="">1) Puree pear tomatoes and half of the roasted peppers in a blender until smooth.

        2) In a saute pan heat olive oil over medium heat. Add garlic and cook until fragrant but not brown.

        3) Add spices &amp; tomato paste and cook 1-2 minutes.

        4) Add pureed tomato mix, kale and remaining roasted red peppers (cut into strips).

        5) Simmer for 10-15 minutes.

        6) Adjust seasoning.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56688" image="S:\Open Kitchen\Chefs - all star team\Food Photos\Shakshuka.jpg">1) Pre poach eggs to
        70% done.

        2) Warm sauce in saurte pan and finsih cooking egg in sauce.

        3) Garnish with diced avocado, feta cheese &amp; Italian parsley.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56695" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Mix well.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56696" image="">1. On flattop make omelet.

        2. Warm mushrooms and at the last minute mix w/ pesto.

        3. Place mushrooms in the middle of omelet, sprinkle cheese and fold shut.

        4. Serve.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56797" image="">1) Place shallots in food processor, making sure not to over fill.

        2) Puree until desired consistency is achieved.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56874" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Westcoast Avocado Toast

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1. Toast all nuts and whole spices seperately to bring out the flavours. (Nuts on sheet pans in a 300F oven and
        spices in a dry pan over very low heat).

        2. Obviously you do NOT want to burn anything or it will become bitter.

        3. PULSE everything in a food processor until you get a course texture, not a paste.

        -store in a dry container with a lid, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-56958" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

        Method:

        1) Spread dry oats on a sheet pan and bake in a 300F oven for 10-15 minutes. This toasting will improve the
        flavour of the oats.

        2) Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.

        3) In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, cinnamon, salt and vanilla.

        4) Simmer mixture for 7-10 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still
        just a little chewy.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56959" image="">1) Pour oats into bowl, place dollop of yogurt in the middle.

        2) Garnish with black pepper and strawberry compote.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-56966" image="">1) Pour oats into bowl, place dollop of yogurt in the middle.

        2) Garnish with maple syrup and thawed diced apples.
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-57344" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1) Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.

        2) In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, squash puree, brown sugar, cinnamon, nutmeg,
        salt and vanilla.

        3) Simmer mixture for 25-30 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still
        just a little chewy.

        4) Hold hot for service, or if preparing in advance, chill in blast chiller and label, date, refrigerate.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="P-58949" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A
        RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens:
        Method:

        1. Slice strawberries when they are partially frozen(rough is fine) and place in suitable sized pot.

        2. Add remaining ingredients except slurry. Bring to a boil.

        3. Add slurry to thicken and remove from heat.

        -cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61110" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="P-61308" image="">PREP RECIPE
        ***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY
        PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

        Related Products this prep gets used in:

        Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
        Method:
        1.
        2.
        3.
        cool product, label it and store it, rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently
        Portioning:

        Utensils needed:
    </Recipe>
    <Recipe id="R-61732" image=""/>
    <Recipe id="R-61733" image=""/>
</Recipes>
