<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-7341" image="">1: Add Meat sauce With vegetables.
2: Cook Penne 10 MIN
3: Place 6 oz pasta in sourghdouh bread bowl.
6: top with cheese.
7:bake 375 F untill golden .</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-7438" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Boil 20L of water seasoned 100 grams of salt
2. When water is at a rolling boil pour pasta in and stirr to stop from clumping
3. Vook pasta for 7 minutes to have &quot;al dante&quot; and 8.5 minutes to be fully cooked
4.Strain pasta out in collander and pour drained pasta onto sheet pan with olive oil\
5. Cool, store in firdge, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-8196" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: DAIRY
Method:

1. Assemble all ingredients.

2. Throw the milk into the steamer.

3. Sautee onions and garlic until soft. Add in spices and cook out for a few minutes. 

4. Add milk and keep heat on medium as to not burn.

5. Mix in the slury until a good saucy consistency.

6. Add cheese and check seasoning.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43699" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. slice taro on correct slicer #

3. cook in deep fryer until crisp and golden

4. season with salt &amp; pepper

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: 
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
