<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="P-9745" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-18318" image="">1) Thinly slice up green onion.

2) Place in apropriate sized conatianer, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26090" image="">1. Add rice to hotel pan using a small lid, prop the hotel pan up on an angle in sink. Rinse rice in cold water agitating rice by hand and letting water drain off naturally. Rinse until water runs clear

2) cook rice in rationale oven by putting in appropriate amount of water and rice and rinsed as above. Put rice and water into hotel pan, cover and cook at 220*F with 100% steam. Around 50 minutes.

3) Spread cooked rice out on baking sheat to cool, once cooled down, store in approriate container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26112" image="">1. Preheat grill to high. Pre heat oven to 350F

2. Brush sausage with oil. Put sausage on grill to sear. Once crisp and has grill lines, remove from grill and put in oven until hot throughout, about 10 - 15 minutes

2. Cut to appropriate serving size and put in serving vessel.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26114" image="">1. Steam or boil perogies as per package directions
2. heat flat top at tilt kettle to medium high heat. Arrange perogies flat side down and sear. Once crispy, season with salt &amp; pepper and butter. Remove to serving vessel and repeat as necessary.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. In medium depth hotel pan, rinse rice under cold water until it runs clear while agitating by hand.

2. Put in steamer for 40 minutes.

3. Stir with a spoon to loosen grains.

4. Hold for service.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26164" image="">1) Crush fennel seeds and mustard seeds coarsely.

2) Combine all, mixing very thoroughly.

3) Transfer to appropriate vessel, label and date and store in dry storage area.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26225" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 400*F.

2)  In mixing bowl, add oil to potatoes, turnips, butternut squash and carrots.  Add seasoning.  Distribute among baking sheets and put in oven to roast.

3)  Add beets to same mixing bowl and season in left over oil, salt and pepper.  Put on seperate baking sheet and cover in tinfoil.

4)  When vegetables are 50% done, stir and rotate pan.  Add thyme, rosemary and garlic and continue to roast until vegetables are caramalized and tender.

5)  Serve immediately, or put in approproate vessel and hold for service.

Allergens:

No known priority allergens

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26310" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Steam potatoes in rationale oven for about 30 minutes or until fall apart tender.

2. Once cooked, remove potatoes from the steamer and put in big bowl of hobart mixer.  On lowest setting using a paddle attachment, let mixer mash up potatoes.  Continue mixing until there is very little steam coming out of potatoes.

3. Meanwhile, gently heat up cream, butter and thyme together in a sauce pot. Let simmer for 2-3 minutes, then pass through fine strainer to remove thyme.

4) Add cream mixture to potatoes with salt and pepper and continue mixing until well incorporated.  

5. Taste for seasoning. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26384" image="">1)  Soak navy beans in cold water overnight in fridge, ensuring to cover beans by at least 2-3 inches of water.

2)  The next day, drain soaked beans and add to large pot.  Add water, rough chopped carrot, celery and onion.  DO NOT SEASON!

3)  Bring to a gentle simmer, skimming any impurities that comes to the top.  Simmer until beans are cooked through, about 15-20 minutes.  

4)  Carefully drain, trying not to squish beans.  Pick out vegetables and bay leaf and discard.

5)  Cool on baking tray.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26442" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Preheat oven to 325*F.  

2) Trim cauliflowers on 2 sides. trim leaves and stem, but leave stem in tack to keep wedges together. Reserve trim for other uses. 

3)  Rub cauliflower heads evenly with oil and house rub. A pastry brush is a good way to get marinade in all parts of the cauliflower.

4)  Spread out cauliflower heads evenly on baking sheets and roast until golden brown and crispy on the edges, about 25-30 minutes. Ensure core is cooked through by piercing with a pairing knife and checking for resistance.
.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Cut and place on roasting tray acorn squash wedges12 Pieces per Acorn
3.sprinkle with other ingredients
4. Roast 190C/375F 25 Minutes or till done
5. put in serving dish for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:130g 

Utensils needed:tongs or spoon
ALLERGEN
-NONE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28313" image="">1)  Steam or simmer perogies according to package directions until soft.  Add to grill and sear until golden brown and slightly crunchy on the exterior, and hot throughout.  

2) Combine with grilled onions and hold for service.  </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28314" image="">1)  In tilt kettle over medium high heat, add oil.  Once oil is hot add onions and saute until beginning to soften and  caramalize.  Add seasoning and hold for service, or put in shallow hotel pan and chill in cooler.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28318" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-31957" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32661" image="">1)  Bring water to a boil in large stock pot.  Add veg stock concentrate and stir well to combine.  Use immidiatly, or cool in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32673" image="">1)  In large stock pot, bring water to a boil.  Add concentrate and stir throughly.  Use immediately, or store in appropriate container and label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34293" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-38556" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-40743" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-41047" image="">1)  Peel yam with teeth.  Give yourself hi-5.

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41094" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice carrots to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41095" image="">1) Either by hand or using the Robocoupe 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machine please ask for assistance) dice celery to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43440" image="">1) Ether by hand or using the Robocope 1/4&quot; dice attachment (if your not sure how to set up or properly use this machien please ask for assistance) dice onion to 1/4&quot; size.

2) Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***


Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:Dairy, Wheat/gluten, egg
Method:

1. Combine cornbread mix and water.  Incorporate thawed corn, diced jalapeno and shredded cheddar cheese and incorporate into batter.  Reserve for making corn bread.

2. In a parchment lined 2&quot; hotel pan spread out cornbread batter to fill 1/4 way up the pan, pressout till even and in all the corners 

3. Bake in a 325F oven for 35-40 minutes, use a tooth pick to c&quot;cake test&quot; bread to ensure doneness, may require another 5-10 minutes

-Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43702" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43704" image="">1)  Pull off stems of chilis and shake out seeds as best you can.  Place in frying pan over medium heat and toss until fragrant, about 4-5 minutes.  Add stock, raisins and orange juice and simmer until chilis rehydrate, about 15 minutes.

2)  Drain chili mixture, ensuring to save liquid.  

3)  Transfer chilis mixture to vitamix, add chipotles and puree.  Scrape out contents with spatula and reserve.

4)  In large rondeau over medium high heat, add oil.  When oil is hot, add onions.  Saute until beginning to softenthen add diced poblano&apos;s and yam.  Saute 2 minutes more.  Add cumin, oregano and saute until fragrant, about 2-3 minutes.

5)  Add pureed chilis and soy sauce and continue to saute for about 2 minutes.  Add reserved chili hydrating liquid, tomatos, drained kidney beans, drained black beans, and drained hominy.  Stir well and add salt and pepper.

6)  Bring to a simmer, reduce to low, cover and cook, stirring occassionally until yams are tender, about 1 hour.  Continue checking chili and adding water if it looks like it&apos;s getting dry.

7)  If possible, make one day ahead to allow flavors to develop.  

8)  Reheat chili to at least 60*C.  Top with chunks of cornbread batter and bake @350*F until cornbread is cooked through.  Serve with serrano sour cream and green onion.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43715" image="">1)  Season beef.  Add oil to tilt kettle @ 400*F, then brown beef.  When beef is browned, remove from tilt kettle and place in perforated insert to drain.

2)  Add onion to tilt kettle and saute while stirring and scraping up the fond from the beef.  When onions are soft, add garlic and ginger puree and saute for 1 minute more.  Add tomato paste and red wine and ensure that bottom of skillet is deglazed.  

3)  Add fish sauce and stock.  While waiting for stock to simmer, add lemon grass, kaffir lime, star anise and thai chili to cheese cloth, and tie off to make a bundle.  Add flavour bundle to stew along with browned beef, diced carrots and sweet potatoes and close lid.  Allow beef to braise for about 30 minutes on low heat (225*F).  

4)  Remove from heat when beef is tender and vegetables are cooked through and place in 3 or 4 hotel pans.  Put in blast chiller to chill, or if serving immediately, add to hot holding.

 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43716" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1)  Dissolve palm sugar in a small amount of water, or grate it on a box grater.  Add to remaining ingredients and stir well to combine.  

2) You can warm palm sugar in veg stock JUSt until it dissolves then add remaining ingredients.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43717" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Blanch brocolli.

2)  Preheat flat top to 400&quot;F.  Add oil and saute vegetables starting with cabbage, then green peppers and carrots, then brocolli and smoked tofu.

3)  Add cooked rice vermicelli noodles and vegan pad thai sauce.  Saute together to ensure everything is well combined.  

Do NOT over cook as noodles will fall apart.

Hold for service.


-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43718" image="">***If using put strainer in the kettle.  If you don&apos;t know what it looks like, ask someone.  If you can&apos;t find it, ask a dishwasher.  You will regret life if you do not do this step.  Trust me.

1) Fill large pot or steam kettle with hot tap water at least 6x water to pasta ratio.

2) Add noodles. Stir stir to make sure noodles do not stick.Soak rice noodles checking for texture. They should be soft enough to bite through but not falling apart on their own weight.

3) When they get cooked they will absorb the sauce and get softer so it is very important you slightly UNDERCOOK the noodles.
If they are fully cooked when prepping they will fall apart when heating and become a mess.

4) Drain the water.

5) Store cooled noodles in container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43729" image="">1)  Combine lemon juice, orange juice, soy sauce, brown sugar, ginger and garlic puree&apos;s.  Mix very well.  Add chicken thighs and marinate for 4-6 hours.

2)  Preheat oven to 400*F.  Add chicken thighs skin side up to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up chicken thighs.  Do not cover skin.  Roast chicken thighs until biggest thigh registers 150*F on an instant read thermometer.

3)  Remove thighs and add to hot holding vessels.  Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining marinade and pour over chicken.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43730" image="">1)  Combine all well and reserve for salad.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43731" image="">1)  Combine brown sugar, S+P mix, soy, lime, and oil.  Mix well.  Add pineapple and allow to marinate for 30 minutes.

2)  Preheat oven to 400*F, add pineapple to parchment lined tray and roast until charred and tender, approx. 15 minutes.

3)  Reserve for salad.  Can be made the day before.

Allergens:

Soy
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43732" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU**

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.  Remove kale from stems and cut into bite sized chunks.
2.  Combine with remaining ingredients and hold cold for service.
 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:




</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44350" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44585" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny\

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry limes
2.Slice into 8 wedges end to end each slive weighting approc 20-25 grams
3.Place in insert lable and place in fridge for service
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:1 piece per order

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44901" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.pick leaves
3.place in container, label and store in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

n/a

Method:

remove rosemary from stems/stalks and chop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45019" image="">1)  Using an 8 fl. oz. scoop for portioning, use 1.5 scoops to ladle stew into bowl.  Serve immidiately.

Allergens:

Fish/Shellfish
Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45150" image="">Average raw weight of a bone in chicken thigh is 170g</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45151" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-45153" image="">
***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Start with rice

2. Sides

3. Chicken x 2 thighs

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45201" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-47340" image="">serve in the indicated proportions </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49252" image="">Heat up honey in a water water bath to make it more runny and make working with it easier.

Puree chipotles in blender, add honey.

Flush the honey bottle with 200ml of hot water and add this hot water to the blender.

Puree to a smooth sauce.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50386" image="">1)  Combine all ingredients. Store in appropriate container, lable date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50389" image="">1) Cut tofu into 150g  slices.

2) Place tofu in container with Shoyu Marinade, let sit for 2-3 hours.

3)  Preheat oven to 425*F.  Add marinaded tofu to hotel pans and add marinade until it comes half way up the tofu slices. Roast tofu for 20 minutes, or until tofu temprature reads 65c on thermometer.

3)  Remove tofu and add to hot holding vessels.  Add sriracha, sesame seeds and chopped green onion to remaining marinade and pour over tofu.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50676" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove leaves from the thickest parts of the stems. discard stems.

2. Using a sharp knife, lightly roll the thyme together in a pile and slice through; continue this until thyme is finely chopped. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50721" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.cut and deseed into 12 wedges
3.Place into container,label and refidgerate

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51201" image="">Rub spices and oil on beef, mark on the grill, finish in the oven, baste and glaze with chipotle glaze.

Cook skewers to medium as much as possible.

A hot oven of 450F or hotter will be most effective for achieving a crispy crust of the edges and still having a medium cooked beef with lots of moisture on the inside. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51285" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51568" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1.

2.

3.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53277" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. make a tasty vegetable stock
2.cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56849" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Soak papaya in cold water overnight (this will keep it crispy).

2. Bruise papaya.

3. Add carrot, green beans.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
