<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Recipes>
	<Recipe id="R-8355" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Spread tomato sauce evenly across dough leaving a half inch boarder for the crust.

2. Top with mozza cheese evenly covering the base of the dough.

4. place slices of bocconcini across the base of the dough on top of the mozza.

5. Using a lightly floured peel transfer the raw pizza into the forno to bake (aprox 3-4 minutes) crust should be baked through and golden on the edges.

6. Again using the peel remove the fully baked pizza from the forno oven. On the cutting board using the pizza knife cut into 8 equal slices, carnish with fresh basil and serve imediately.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9713" image="">Yield for peeled trimmed peeled carrots is approx 85%

22.7 kg = 50 lbs 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9778" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry
2.process as needed
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9779" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredents
2.Clean and slice
3.Label and fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-9782" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Wash and dry tomato
2.Cut by hand or if doing big amount then. Put together R2 with proper slicing and dicing blades
3.place insert and perferated pan under to catch the diced tomato and to strain excess liquid
4. once done lable and place in fridge
5. Clean R2 parts by hand and return to office.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:60g

Utensils needed:blue scoop</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-10873" image="">
Place chicken onto pans and bake or roast until well done. 

Some of the marinade can be drained off if it is excessively &quot;wet&quot;. Also, some of the liquid that comes out of the chicken whilst cooking can be drained off if that will make it excessively &quot;wet&quot;.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-13648" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Cut Bread in 1/4inch cubes

2.Toss in oil, salt and pepper. Coat Well

3.Bake on Sheet until golden and dry inside

**Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-14282" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-14480" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Chill bowl and whisk.

2. Whisk cream untul soft peaks form.

3. Add vanilla and sugar and taste for balance.

4. DO NOT OVERWHIP OR IT WILL TASTE GRAINY.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

ah huh whip it

whip it good

ah huh whip it

whip it real good</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-14703" image="">Mix together

Reserve for service</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-19175" image="">Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegetarian, made without gluten

Method:



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-22534" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-23950" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Cook and drain the bacon, and chop it. 

Caramelize the onions in a small amount of the bacon fat with the brown sugar. 

Once the onions are caramelized, add the chopped bacon, coffee, vinegar, rosemary and balck peppers and simmer to reduce to jam consistency.

Taste and add salt only if neccessary to balance the flavours. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-24157" image="">20g = 2 pc</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-24750" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-25761" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing blade.
3. Bring all other ingredients to a simmer and combine with onion


-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning: kettle, cambros, food processer

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-25993" image="">1) Combine and mix well

2) Place in appropriate sized container, lable and date.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26020" image="">1. Puree garlic in batches in robot coupe
2. Mix in garlic</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26022" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place apples, cinnamon, and brown sugar together in a pot.

2. Add water if needed (the frozen apples will purge some liquid, but be prepared to add some if it seems to not be enough) Bring to a boil and reduce to a simmer for  about 5-10 minutes

3. Make a cornstarch slurry and pour it in incrementally, while stirring the pot. Be careful to add a bit at a time, and check the consistency between additions, because once the sauce consistency has been acheived, no more slurry should be added. 

4. Spread out on baking tray to cool.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26048" image="">1. Combine balsamic vinegar,  dijon, garlic, maple syrup, salt &amp; pepper.

2. Begin blending with immersion blender till smooth add oil slowly and blend till emulsion
3. Store in appropriate vessel, label, date and refrigerate.

Allergens:

Mustard
Sulphite</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26054" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Combine everything and mix thoroughly 

Adjust water content as needed, make it pourable.

PLEASE DO NOT DOUBLE THIS RECIPE- A SINGLE RECIPE IS PLENTY</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26062" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1. Dice tomatoes and place in perferated insert to drain excess liquid. Ensure tomatoes are small dice.

2. Chop jalapenos in robot coupe until finely chopped.

3. Put tomatoes into an insert and add red onion, jalapeno, cilantro, kosher salt, black pepper and lime juice. Mix well using hands with gloves on.  

3. Adjust seasoning To taste.

-store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26067" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Heat canola oil over medium heat, add shallot and saute until soft and fragrant

2) Add cherries and heat until no longer frozen, about 3 minutes

3) Add remaining ingredients and bring to a simmer, stirring frequently for 30 minutes

4) Season with salt &amp; pepper. 

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26175" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Brisket


Allergens: 
Method:

1. Roughly crush cloves.  Add all ingredients in bowl and mix wel

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26181" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1) Pre heat rationale oven to 250F

2) Remove excess fat from brisket, score fatty side. Rub brisket in Berbere rub.  Set aside.  Brisket can be rubbed up to two days before.

3) Place brisket and braising liquid in deep 6&quot; hotel pan, cover with parchment and then cover insert with aluminum foil.  Fold aluminum foil back about half way so you can see meat and braising liquid.  

4)  Place insert over burners or on french top and bring to a boil.  

5) Place in rationale oven and cook for 12 hours or until tender.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26205" image="">1)  In a large saute pan or rondeau and working in batches, heat oil over medium high heat.  Add about 1/3 of the oil and allow to get hot.  Add an appropriate amount of mushrooms so as to not overcrowd the rondeau. Add some seasoning as the mushrooms are beginning to brown.  Taste for seasoning.

2)  Allow to cool on flat tray. Reserve for service or if using later, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26380" image="">1) Preheat oven to 300F.

2) Put almonds in oven, toast for 10 minutes.  Rotate pan and stiralmonds and toast for another 5 minutes or until golden brown.  Allow to cool.


Allergens:

Nuts/Treenuts</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26514" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. Pick leaves off

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26628" image="">
PREP RECIPE

Combine and mix, heat to a boil.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26631" image="">1. Assemble of of the ingredients.

2. Mix dry and wet ingredients together to make batter. - Don&apos;t over mix.

3. Using a 3oz ladle to scoop batter to make your pancakes.

4. Serve with the apropriate Sauce/Topping of the day/week/month.

5. Left over batter to be counted and wasted by weight. DO NOT RE-USE NEXT DAY.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26636" image="">
-chop parsley
-combined all ingredients in a mix bowl, with a paddle attachement, whip together
-store until needed


note: please leave garlic herb butter out the day before to ensure the product is soft enough to spread. When needed</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-26776" image="C:\Users\chefpain.HOUSING\Documents\Totem\Menus\Grill Photos\Classic Burger.jpeg">Method:

1.Grill burger until well done. (71C)

2.Toast bun.

3.Brush sauce onto both sides of bun.

4.Place burger on bottom bun.

5.Top with lettuce, tomato, and red onion. 

6.Put top half of bun on.

7. Use bamboo skewer to secure pickle and top of bun on burger.



 

.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-26786" image="C:\Users\chefpain.HOUSING\Documents\Totem\Menus\Grill Photos\Poutine.jpeg">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Fry the fries untill crispy and golden (aprox 3 mins)

2. Place fries in serving dish/bowl

3. Top fries with scaled portion of cheese curds.

4. Ladle the gravy over the fries and curds evenly.

5. serve immediately and with kindness.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-26788" image="">Allergens:
soy

Icons:
vegan, vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-26792" image="">Yield test results %85 by weight for cooked eggs

***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Add liquid egg to hotel pan and put in rational oven on 100% steam for 10-15 minutes until eggs have  cooked 95% and are still slightly wet creamy.

2. Add to vessel, season and serve.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-26800" image="">Allergens:
wheat, gluten, mustard, sulphites

Icons:
vegetarian, vegan(maybe need to confirm samosa dough)

Method:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-27423" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28232" image="">-cut english muffin in half, fry egg, cook sausage, 
-spread honey mustard on both sides, line a tray of them openfaced
-fill with  egg, sausage, tomato and cheese. bake for 2 mins
-close,and serve in hot hold </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28235" image="">-cut english muffin in half, fry egg
-spread aioli on both sides, line a tray of them openfaced
-fill with  tomato, egg, ham and cheese. bake for 2 mins
-close, wrap and serve in hot hold </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-28254" image="">



</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-28285" image="">1)  Combine pancake mix and water throughly.  Reserve for service.

Allergens:  

Gluten
Wheat
Gluten
Soy 
Dairy
Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32151" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-32259" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Use a box grater to shred the hard boiled egg into small chunks

2. Finely mince the celery and green onion

3. Mix the may with the seasonings for even distrubution and fold into the egg onion, celery mix.

4. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed. Reserve 
*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-32261" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Lightly toast the bread.

2. place the lettuce &amp;cucumber  on the bottom bun. Top with egg salad mixture. Season with salt and pepper.

3. Top egg salad mix with lettuce and close with top bread slice.

4. Cut on a diaganal and serve.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-32739" image="">1)  Chill can of coconut milk in fridge for 24 hours.  Ensure to store upside down.

2)  Chill bowl of stand mixer in fridge for an hour, or stick lots of ice and cold water in it to chill.

3)  Open can of coconut milk and scoop out fat and discard coconut water.

4) Place the sugar in the mixing bowl of the standmixer

5)  Beat until fluffy and smooth with stand mixer with whisk attachment.  Add vanilla and whisk some more to incorporate.

6)  Store in appropriate container.  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33208" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-33531" image="">1)  Cut wonton wrappers into thin strips and fry at 350*F fryer for 45 seconds - 1 minute.  Season with S&amp;P mixture and dry throughly on papertowel.  Transfer to air tight container and label, date refrigerate.

Allergens:

Gluten
Wheat
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-33887" image="">1)  Preheat oven to 425*F

2)  In a large mixing bowl, add beets, oil and S+P.  Combine well and put on parchment lined baking trays.

3)  Cover with aluminium foil and put in oven.  Roast for 45 minutes to 1 hour or until beets are fork tender, but not mushy.  

4)  Slips peels off of beets and chop into bite size chunks.  Toss with honey and tarragon and season to taste.  Hold for service.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34084" image="">1)  Tray bacon on baking sheets and place in oven preheated to 350*F.  Cook until bacon is fully cooked and slightly crispy, about 15 minutes.

57g = approx 2 slices of raw bacon

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34541" image="">
PREP RECIPE 

*** for yeilding purposes.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-34880" image="">1)  Blend the hell out of it.

2)  Label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35233" image="">ALLERGEN: SOY, MUSTARD, sesame, sulphites (sriracha)

-Combined all ingredients except oil into a cambro and mix well
-Slowly add oil as you immersion blend the mixture to form a thick dressing consistency 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35749" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a large bowl, mix all ingredients EXCEPT the Crispy Wonton skins, and toss until dressing uniformly covers ingredients.

2. Place into serving bowl.

3. Garnish with Crispy Wonton skins, and serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-35750" image="">
PREP RECIPE

-Take Caesar dressing and add sriracha
-Mix well</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-35751" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. In a mixing bowl; add kale, romaine and dressing. ensuring to evenly coat entire salad (do not over dress)

2. Garnish with parm and croutons (idealy these items do not go into the mixing bowl to keep it dairy and gluten free)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36066" image="">
Method:
1.Mix all ingredients in the blender untill smooth
2.Divide in togo cups with lids
3.Store in fridge right away

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36077" image="">METHOD
TURN OVEN TO 425
- peel squash
- cut into 3/4 &quot; dice
- toss with ouil, salt pepper.

Roast in oven for 12 min or until fork tender but not mush. 

remove from oven, do not cover, allow to cool
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36486" image="">Puree all inredient except oil. 
Add oil slowly to emulsify</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-36669" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Toast bread 

2. assemble ingredients on top

3. Serve with a kindness!

**A fried egg on top is an awesome add on to this dish, if the guest requests one

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-36815" image="">
Method:
1.Mix all ingredients in the blender untill smooth
2.Divide in togo cups with lids
3.Store in fridge right away

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-37297" image="">1)  Spray egg poacher cup with pan spray.  Place egg in egg poacher cup.  Steam for 7 minutes until cooked.

Allergens:

Soy, Egg</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-38248" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Toss red peppers, corn, black beans, quinoa, arugula and romaine in the avocado lime dressing. 

Place in a bowl and top with the cheddar, crispy tortilla chips and salsa.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-39135" image="">

PREP RECIPE


Combine and blend
 
Divide into portion cups with lids, store in fridge right away!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-41466" image="">1. Combine all ingredients in your pot

2. Turn to a low heat, avoid boiling!!!

3. Once it comes to a low simmer, turn down so that it barely bubbles and leave on the stove for about and hour or until the garlic fully developes flavor and tastes a bit sweet.

4. Once done, turn off and take off the burner let cool down before downsizing into your 16L Cambro.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-42353" image="">
Prep:

- Quarter Corn Tortillas. 2.5 Packages of Corn Tortillas will yield 2 Deep Hotel pans full of Corn Chips.

- Using Paper Towel, create a large pan or bowl for draining the excess oil off of the Tortilla Chips, after they&apos;ve come out of the Deep Fryer.

- At 350 Degrees (F) in the Deep Fryer, fry NO MORE THAN HALF OF A STACK OF CORN TORTILLAS (QUARTERED) at a time.

- Using a Spider, or Long Tongs - KEEP TORTILLAS MOVING AT ALL TIMES. 

- Depending on how dark the Deep Fryer oil is, fry the Tortilla Chips until they are brown (keeping in mind that they will cook for a little while longer once they&apos;ve been taken out of the fryer. 

- As soon as the chips are out drying, salt lightly using the Windsor coarse grain salt. The salt will only stick during this stage of production - be sure to catch it!

Label/Date/Store

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43206" image="">Put everything in the blender in the order that it&apos;s listed and blend until smooth!! 

*Keep mangoes frozen </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-43213" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-43243" image="">

PREP RECIPE

Puree chipotles

Combine and mix
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43637" image="">-mix ingredients in portion cup
-blend
-serve </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-43719" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Combine all well.  Put in fridge overnight to allow oats to soak up liquid.  Combine with other fruits/garnishes as indicated in recipes.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44309" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-44429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.  

2)  Set up a perforated insert to catch tomato and allow them to drain as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44823" image="">Allergen: Egg, Diary


-cut english muffin in half, fry egg
-spread mustard on both sides, line a tray of them openfaced
-fill with  egg, turkey, tomato and cheese. bake for 2 mins
-close, and serve in hot hold 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44828" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Build in this order; Pico on bottom bun, fried egg on top of pico (to anchor it in place) cheese on top of egg, spread guacamole on top bun.

2. Bake for 2 minutes

3. Close, and serve in hot hold 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-44876" image="">Allergens:
wheat, gluten, soy, milk, egg, sesame

Cook Pancakes on flat top

1 pancake = approx 80g ( 3 floz ladle )

Method:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44913" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Gather all ingredients.

2. Remove peels and pits from avocados.

3. Put all ingredients in a bowl and mash them together until fully combined trying to keep the avocado as chunky as possile

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-44964" image="">1)  Remove kale leaves from the tough woody stem by tearing or running a knife along the stem to remove leaves.

2)  Discard stem and process kale as dicated by recipe.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45047" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny,

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingedients
2.wash and trim
3.place in container, label and place in fridge
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

Allergen:

n/a

Icon:

vegan, vegatarian, made without gluten</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-45077" image="">Method:
slice bagel
spread thin layer of mayo on top and bottom
cook fried egg
place slice of lettuce on bottom, then tomato then egg, then bacon
close sandwich
hold hot
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45255" image="">Allergens:
gluten, wheat

Icons:
N/A

Method:
 70 pcs average per case

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-45879" image="">
-Combine and mix well
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-46336" image="">1 portion = 1/2 tomato</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46501" image="">Method:

Combine ingredients and mix</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46546" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WI Johnny
TH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1. Drain the cheese
2. Crumble with your hands into small piece
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-46862" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY RECIPE WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Method:

1.Cut stem side top off wasting as little tomato as possible
2. Save tops for soup/sauce
3. Slice tomato slice 2mm thick
4.store in an insert with parchment paper lining, label and rotate with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-47518" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Dressed arugula

Allergens: Mustard, Sulphites

Method:

1. Mince shallots, add apple cider vin, alt &amp; pepper &amp; mustard.

2. Whisk together, continue whisking while adding the oil

3. Taste for seasoning, adjust as needed

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
 </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48495" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Chop the cilantro on cutting board until desired size
3.  

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed: Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Stretch out the dough to 16&quot;

2. Spread the pesto evenly across the base of the dough leaving a half inch border for the crust.

3. Evenly spread the mozza across the dough covering the pesto. 

4. On top of the mozza spread out the artichokes, sauteed mushrooms, and chicken, try not to overlap the ingredents too much so all aspects are visual to the guest.

5. With a lightly floured peel, scoot the raw pizza into the forno oven and bake for 3-4 minutes (longer if needed) Crust should be cooked through and golden.

6. Again using the peel remove coocked pizza from the forno placing it on the cutting board, using the pizza knife cut into 8 even slices.

&amp;. Serve imediately and with kindness.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48870" image="">Combine and mix thoroughly.

Tray up Chicken and Bake/Roast until cooked to well done. 

Use immediatly or chill rapidly and stor for later use. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48933" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***

Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients and tools
2. Trim the ends and/or rotten pieces
3. 
 
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:Cutting board, knife, insert
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48995" image="">Allergens:

Icons:

Method:
- roast all vegetables separately
- combine together in large bowl
- toss with apple dijon vinaigrette
- hold for service
- </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48996" image="">Allergens:

Icon:
vegan, vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
- trim fennel stocks and root end
- cut fennel head into 3/4&quot; pieces
- combine oil, salt, pepper, thyme, syrup
- toss fennel with marinade
- place on parchment lined sheet pan - single layer
- roast at 400f for 8 - 12 min or until colored &amp; tender but not too soft
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-48997" image="">Allergens:

Icon:
vegan, vegetarian, made with out gluten

Method:
- trim &amp; peel parsnip
- cut parsnip into 3/4&quot; pieces
- combine oil, salt, pepper, thyme, syrup
- toss parsnip with marinade
- place on parchment lined sheet pan - single layer
- roast at 400f for 8 - 12 min or until colored &amp; tender but not too soft</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-48998" image="">Allergens:

Icons:

Method:
- Roast all vegetables as per recipe
- toss together, dress with vinaigrette (reserve 25%)
- add arugula and toss together
- place portion into serving bowl
- drizzel remaining vinaigrette over salad
- top with balsamic glaze &amp; goat cheese
- serve</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-49035" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Mix all ingredients in the blender untill smooth

2.Divide in togo cups with lids

3.Store in fridge right away

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:measuring cups, measuring spoon, blender
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-49036" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.
2.
3.
-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
togo smoothies cups</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50429" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 






</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50488" image="">1) Unwrap smoked brisket, place on meat slicer, and cut to 1/8&quot; slices.

2) Place in an appropriate sized container, label, date, refrigerate.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50490" image="">

To make oat milk simply add all ingredients to a high-speed blender and blend on high for 30-45 seconds. Then strain through doubled up cheesecloth in a fine china cap.

Reserve and Label
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50495" image="">Mixed in a cold water before used. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50533" image="">







***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.  Lightly coat bottom of flat bread in pesto and mozzarella cheese, then place chopped marinated artichoke heart pieces and  evenly across flatbread.

2. Evenly place halved grape tomatoes around flatbread,

3. Place in forno oven for 3-4 minutes. Until bottom is crispy and top cheese starts to melt and brown.

4. Once cooked, cut, sprinkle arugula and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.

5. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

 



4) Once cooked, cut, sprinkle arugula and drizzle balsamic reduction over top.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50567" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the thickest parts of the stems (reserve for stock if necessary/possible)

2. using a sharp knife, lightly roll the parsley together in a bundle and slice through (chiffinade) continue this until parsley is fine. always use a slicing mottion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

3. Store in an apropriate size insert/cambro with a pice of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50587" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. core out stem 

3. Quarter tomato, remove soft flesh and seeds, reserve for other uses.

4. Small Dice tomatoes for recipes.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50622" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Raspberry chocolate pancakes

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all your ingredients.

2. Heat your raspberries slowly untill they simmer - once simmering, turn up the heat and bring to a boil.

3. Boil for 4 minutes. Stiring constantly. 

4. Add in your sugar, salt, and black pepper. Stir constantly, because your mixture will expand so be careful. Boil for another 4 minutes.

4. Add lemon juice and take off heat.

5. Taste and check for balance.

**Serve warm on TOP of pancakes. Do not mix into pancake batter. Pancake garnishes always served on top.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50632" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

One order is 2 pancakes, topped with 90ml of compote. 

***Please note that this batter is a straight up buttermilk pancake without any &quot;mix-ins&quot;

The guest can choose to self serve with additional syrup if they like. 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50633" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Place peaches in large pot.  Stir in sugar, orange juice, water, cinnamon, nutmeg, salt. 

2. Bring to a simmer over med / high heat and reduce by approx 20%

3. Make corn starch slurry and wisk into peach mixture, stir constantly until sauce thickens slightly.

4. Remove from heat.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50634" image="">Method:
- prepare pancakes as per recipe
- top with peach topping
- top with whip cream &amp; maple syrup
- serve

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50636" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens

Method:

1. Gather all Tools and ingredients
2.
3.

-cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 


Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50655" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cook burger on flat top, toast bun.

2. Top cooked patty with sauteed mushrooms then swiss cheese and melt to secure mushrooms on top

3. Spread feast burger sauce on top and bottom of bun
place burger on bottom bun.

4. Top burger with lettuce, tomato &amp; red onion
close burger with top bun. secure with skewer.

5. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50665" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crisps and golden brown.

Take the two slices of bread for the sandwich close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50668" image="">

PRODUCT RECIPE

Pre-drain the pickled jalapeno slices. 

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crisp and golden brown.

Take the two slices of bread for the sandwich add the well drained jalapeno peppers and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50669" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the outsides of the sandwich.

Lay cheese slices on what will be the inside and grill the outside, until it becomes crips and golden brown.

Add guacamole and bacon to the inside of the sandwich and close it up. 

Cut in half once, going corner to corner. 





</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50675" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Remove the leafs from the thick stems, discard stems

2. Using a sharp chef knife place the leaves together and lightly roll together

3. Using a slicing motion mince the mint into thin strips (chiffanade) turn the other way and repeat until mint is rough chopped. Always use a slicing motion rather than a chopping motion on soft herbs to prevent bruising.

4. Store in an apropriate sice insert/container with a piece of paper towel at the bottom to wick away any moisture.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50696" image="">Combine and mix.

Label, date and store.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50697" image="">Method:

1.Grill burger until well done. (71C)

2.Toast bun.

3.Brush sauce onto both sides of bun.

4.Place burger on bottom bun.

5.Top with cheese, lettuce, tomato, and red onion. 

6.Put top half of bun on.

7. Use bamboo skewer to secure pickle and top of bun on burger.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50703" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-50704" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Cook burger, toast bun, cook bacon. 

Assemble a buger with all of the listed toppings in the proportions indicated.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50705" image="">Method:
- heat flat top or pan over med-high heat
- add oil, ensure to coat bottom of pan
- crack egg into hot pan
- season with salt &amp; pepper
- once egg has cooked 60%, flip over gently
- cook for 20 sec until white is fully cooked
- serve
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50706" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Grill the burger on the flat top, melting the cheese on it when it is close to done.

Toast the bun. 

Fry the overeasy egg on the flattop

To build the burger, put the bacon jam on the bottom bun. 

Place the patty on the bottom bun and top with the egg, add the lettuce and tomato slices and put the lid on the burger. 

Secure with a skewer and serve.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50709" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-50801" image="">1.In a 350F pre-heated oven.
2. Lay flat pumpkin seeds on a sheet pan.
3.Roast pumkin seeds for 5-8minutes or until turns a bit brown but not burnt.
4. Take it off from oven.
5. Let it cool and transfer to a dry container.
6. Store in a dry place until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-50858" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

On a prebaked flatbread, spread pesto and sprinkle veggies and olives

Bake until toppings and bread are hot and cheese is slightly melted. 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-50923" image="">1.Slice olives to 4mm thick.
2. Properly store in a container, label and keep in fridge until needed.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51192" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cook pancakes

2. Garnish with raspberry topping ( do not mix into pancake batter!)

3. Serve with syrup on side

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-51206" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-51535" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Chef Johnny


Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:
1.Gather ingredients
2.Wash and trim off stem
3. cut to correct size for what you need

- store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-52027" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-52043" image="">Method:

Lay out almonds on a sheet pan in a layer not exceeding half and inch 

Bake in a 325 oven, shaking or stirring every 6-7 minutes

Bake for 10-20 minutes or unitl golden brown.

Please use a timer, almonds are expensive and burning them is preventable. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53056" image="">average roma tomato weighs approx 90g

this recipe makes 26 x 1/2 tomatoes

1 portion = 1 tomato 1/2&apos;s or 1 whole tomato</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-53360" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Make pancake batter as usual and add diced bananas.

Cook pancake batter with banana pieces included as usual. 

Top the pancakes with 20ml of caramel sauce in a nice zig zag or swirl pattern. 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-53361" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Peel and dice bananas.

2. Make pancake batter as usual.

3. Mix banana pieces into batter.

4. Cook pancakes as usual.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54079" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the exterior of the sandwich with garlic butter and lay slices of cheese and deli meat in the center portion. 

Grill on flattop until bread is goldwen brown and crispy and the cheese is melted. 

Cut in half once, corner to corner. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-54358" image="">
PREP RECIPE

**MAKES 3**

** Add water as needed to get it to blend and make the portion. 

Check flavour and ensure that it is tasty please. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54386" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Top dough with measured volume of sauce

2. Add Chese and bacon

3. Crack egg in centre of pizza (this will cook in the forno)

4. Bake until the bottom is a mottled golden brown and cheese is bubbly and melted. 

5. When finished baking place on cutting board and cut into 10 equal slices.

6. Serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-54762" image="">
PRODUCT RECIPE

Butter the exterior of the sandwich with garlic butter and lay slices of cheese and deli meat in the center portion. 

Grill on flattop until bread is golden brown and crispy and the cheese is melted. 

Cut in half once, corner to corner. </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55098" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

VEGAN PRODUCT

Allergens: 
Gluten 
Wheat
Soy

Method:

1. Make overnight oats as per recipe.  

2. Combine remaining ingredients (EXCEPT OATS) in a large cambro container and blend well with immersion blender.  Mix well into overnight oats and let stand in the fridge overnight.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-55117" image="">1) Place oats in bowl.

2) Top with sliced banana, coconut cream &amp; toasted almonds.
 
Utensils needed: White Scoop for the Oats
                          Black Scoop for Coconut whip.</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55129" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="R-55132" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Put roasted beets, arugula and onions in mixing bowl, toss with dressing to coat evenly

2. Place in base of serving bowl and garnish with goat cheese and grapefruit sections

3. Serve with Kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-55669" image="">Toss chicken breast with oil, salt &amp; pepper
place on char broiler and grill mark
remove from grill and place on sheet pan
bake in 375f oven until internal temp of 168f
remove from oven and allow to rest ( carry over cook temp to 172f
place chicken in cooler and hold for packaging
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-56090" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-56334" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Steam potatoes till fork tender, Dice into 1/2&quot; cubes. Reserve.

2. In a large rondeau add oil over medium heat.  Add in the cubed potatoes and spread them out into an even later. Cook for about until browned. aprox 4-5 minutes

3. Add in the onions garlic, bell peppers, beyond meat, and old bay,salt and pepper and continue cooking until the potatoes are cooked through, about 8-10 minutes.

4. Mix in the kale and black beans. Allow it to cook for 2 more minutes or until the kale has wilted and the beans have warmed through.

5. Remove from heat and adjust seasoning as needed. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently!</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56398" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda


1.Small dice pickled jalapenos and tomatoes. mince cilantro.

2. in a bowl combine all ingredents. mix well keeping chunks visible in the mixture. check for seasoning.

3. Ready to use or store in apropriate size cambro with seran wrap directly contacting the surface of the guac as well as a lid on the container (to stop oxidization)

LABEL/DATE/REFRIGERATE</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56430" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Blueberry Pancakes

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Boil water, sugar, and lemon zest in a 1-quart heavy saucepan, uncovered, 5 minutes.

2. Discard zest. Stir in blueberries and simmer, stirring occasionally, until blueberries begin to burst (aprox 3 to 5 minutes)  Remove from heat and stir in lemon juice. Serve warm or at room temperature. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56543" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Chopped thai Salad

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

METHOD:

1. Puree all the dressing ingredients in a food processor until smooth. Taste and adjust for seasoning. Ready to use or put in apropriate cambro with lid

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56544" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

1. Cook the edamame by blanching it for 3-5 minutes in a pot of boiling water. Drain and allow it to cool. Meanwhile, slice up the kale, julienne carrots, peppers, chop cilantro leaves, and slice green onions.
  
2.  Place the cooked edamame in the food processor and pulse 4-5 times to get a minced texture. Transfer to a bowl reserve.  Repeat the same process for the toasted cashews, reserve. 

3. Toss the kale, carrots, peppers, cilantro, green onions, and edamame together until well combined.

**Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56714" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1)  Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.  

2)  In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, apples, brown sugar, cinnamon, salt and vanilla.

3)  Simmer mixture for 7-10 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still just a little chewy. Add maple syrup.

4)  Hold hot for service, or if preparing in advance, chill in blast chiller and label, date, refrigerate.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56762" image="">Method:
- drain and rinse artichoke allow all excess moisture to drain off
- toss artichokes with olive oil, oregano &amp; basil
- hold for service
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56851" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Kale&amp;Quinoa/Green salad

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Scale out all ingredients

2. In a vitamix Add Dijon, Honey &amp; lemon juice

3. Emulsify by slowly streaming in oil while vitamix is on.

4. once fully emulsified add in fresh thyme and blitz quickly on a short pulse ( do not blend to hard at this point the thyme will turn the dressing green)

5. Taste for seasoning and adjust as needed.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-56939" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Italian Hoagie

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Scale out all ingredients

2.in large mixing bowl fold together all ingredients untill they become homogenous

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57005" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Put 45ml of burger sauce on each side of bread.

2. fold each slice of smoked meat in half (to give more height to sandwich) and place on one side of bread.

3. Add saurkraut to the top of the meat and place cheese on top of kraut (cheese will melt and help kraut stay in place) 

4. Place top piece of bread on sandwich and grill/toast on panini. Grill untill bread is nicely toasted and cheese has melted

5. Cut on a bias and serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57032" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:Buffalo Chicken Sandwich

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Scale out all ingredents

2. Finely mince chives/Green onions

3. In a large bowl fold all ingredents together untill thuroughly combined.

*Cool, store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57046" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Spread measured volume of sauce across the base of pizza leaving a 1/2 inch boarder for crust.

2. Top with 4 slices of ham and drained pineapple

3.  Place scaled volume of cheese across the top and place in forno on well floured peel

4. Bake uptil crust is golden brown and bottom is fully cooked

5. Cut into 10 equal pieces and serve with kindness!


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57080" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Evenly spread  sauce across dough. leaving a 1/2 inch border around the edge for the crust.

2. Start with the spinach first (so it is protected by other ingredents and doesnt burn) then top with marinated artichokes, peppers, mushrooms, onion and mozza.

4. Transfer to forno oven on a well floured peel (prevents sticking) bake in forno oven turning several times for even baking. pizza is done when crust around edge is dark golden brown, cheese is bubly and melted, toppings are heated through and bottom of pizza is crisp and golden.
(aprox 3-4 minutes)

5. Using peel top remove pizza from oven place on cutting surface and cut piza into 10 even slices. Serve with kindness.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57087" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

2. evenly spread sauce across dough. leaving a 1/2 inch border around the edge for the crust.

3. Evenly distripute the cheeses around the sauced area

4. Transfer to forno oven on a well floured peel (prevents sticking) bake in forno oven turning several times for even baking. pizza is done when crust around edge is dark golden brown, cheese is bubly, golden/caramelized and melted, toppings are heated through and bottom of pizza is crisp and golden.
(aprox 3-4 minutes)

5. Using peel top remove pizza from oven place on cutting surface and cut piza into 10 even slices.

6. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57092" image="">Remove core and trim tips of &quot;rusty&quot; or undesirable pices of romaine. 1 head trimmed and prepped yields aproximately 1.5 pounds</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57143" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools
2. Cut stem off
3. mince and discard the seeds

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57144" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1. Gather all ingredients and tools

2. Cut stems off

3. Rough mince(sliceing motion not chopping; slicing will prevent brusing the delicate cilantro leaves)

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently </Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57152" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Gather all ingredents. Using a larger pot than you think you will need (caramel expands and foams up once you add the cream to the hot sugar mixture) Caramel is a fast process and you cannot walk away from it. if you don&apos;t work fast once the sugar is ready, it will burn.Scale out all ingredents make sure the butter is cubed and cold.

2. Add Water and sugar to a heavy bottom sauce pan. turn on medium high heat DO NOT WALK AWAY. This recipe needs undevided attention.

3. Allow sugar to fully disolve. As the sugar melts, stir vigerously with a whisk or wooden spoon (nothing plastic or it will melt!) reduce heat once the sugar has fully melted.

3. once the sugar has melted stop stiring (you can swirl the pan but do not stir with a utensil)

4. As soon as the sugar turns to a dark amber colour, remove from heat and ad the cold butter, whisk until the butter is melted. Once butter is fully melted, add the heavy cream (using caution as hot steam will happen and the cream will foam up considerably) Whisk until smooth and homogenous(well blended) Let Cool! once cool enough to pour into a cambro do so, but let sit out without a lid until reaches room tempature. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57158" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Toast the foccacia.

2. Divide the Pesto mayo equally on both sides of the bread. Edge to edge coverage.

3.Slice the bocconcini into 1/4 inch rounds and shingle on to the bottom bun. top with sliced tomatoes. Top with  arugula

4. It is imprortant to place the tomatoes between the cheese and arugula to protect the integrity of the bread as to not allow it to go soggy!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57284" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Preps used in this Product recipe:

Allergens: (To be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Cut ends off carrots and peel thinly. Discard

2. Slice, Dice and shred carrots as needed for recipe use.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57344" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: 
Method:

1. Soak oats overnight by placing appropriate amount of oats in a large cambro and covering them with water.  

2. In large sauce pot or rondeau, combine soaked oats, almond milk, squash puree, brown sugar, cinnamon, nutmeg, salt and vanilla.

3. Simmer mixture for 25-30 minutes, stirring frequently until oats are cooked through and pallatable, but still just a little chewy.

4. Hold hot for service, or if preparing in advance, chill in blast chiller and label, date, refrigerate.

-cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently.

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-57345" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. 


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57499" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Related Products this prep gets used in:
 
Method:

1)  Set up robot coupe slicer with 1/4&quot; dice attachment.  If you don&apos;t know how, ask chef or a 1st cook.
OR cut by hand if small amount  

2)  Set up an insert to catch onion as they come out of the robot coupe.

3)  Label, date, refrigerate, or reserve for making recipes or service.

Allergens:

No known prioirity allergens.
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-57639" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Johnny

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Method:
1. Gather All Ingredients
2. Slice onions with food processor slicing &quot;S&quot; blade
3.store, label and rotated this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61823" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.

2.

3.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61827" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Blue Bacon Burger

Allergens: Dairy

Method:

1. In a kitchen aid with paddle attachment fold together the blue cheese and cream cheese untill thuroughly combined. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61828" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: gluten, dairy
Method:

1. Toast bun, grill burger

2. Assemble burger as follows: blue cheese spread on both sides of bun, burger patty, bacon lettuce and tomato.

3. Close burger, skewer and serve with pickle garnish 

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61829" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Spread sauce evenly across base of dough leaving a half inch boarder for the crust

2. Place mozza evenly across sauce

3. Top with 90g of peperoni evenly spaced to provide even coverage.

4. pn a well floured peel, place in forno oven and bake until golden crust, fully cooked on the bottom and cheese is bubbly.

4. Remove from oven, place on cutting board and with the pizza kinfe cut into 10 equal pieces and serve with kindness

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61838" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Grilled Cheese

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place spinach and red onion in mixing bowl and toss lightly with dressing to coat

2. Place dressed spinach in base of serving bowl

3. Garnish with chopped cooked bacon, tasted almonds, goat cheese and hard boiled egg on top

4. Serve with Kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61845" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1.Mix all the ingredients in a cambro until well combined.
Keep in the fridge overnight (or for at least 8 hours.)


2. If it’s too dry you can add more almond milk to adjust consistancy.

3. Store the bircher muesli in the fridge in a sealed cambo in the fridge for 2 to 3 days.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61846" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place portioned amount of Bircher mix at the bottom of a small slope bowl.

2. top with fresh blueberries and almonds


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61854" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens:Gluten, Dairy
Method:

1. Toast bun

2. Dijon mayo on both sides of the bun

3. Top the bottom bun with sliced turkey, brie, sliced pear and lettuce. Close bun (toast in panini if the guest requests) cut in half.

4. Serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-61905" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Peel and Sice the Sweet potatoes into 1/2 inch cubes. Toss in oil, salt, pepper, garlic and Paprika; add to a parchment lined baking sheet. Roast in oven untill soft inside and golden brown on outside. Reserve

2. Dice red peppers, and onion same as potatoes, toss with sliced mushrooms and chili peppers in oil, salt and pepper and place on parchement lined sheet. Roast in oven untill tender and slightly blistering. Reserve.

3. While the potatoes and pepper/onions/mushroom mix is still warm toss wiith prosessed kale and sliced tomatoes to wilt. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-61906" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. This Dish is concidered a vegan option untill the addition of  eggs and Holly; please keep that in mind the base is to be kept vegan and eggs and holly are added on top to complete!

2. Place portioned amount of hash base at bottom of bowl.

3. Top hash with  2 medium poached eggs and 60ml of hollandaise.

4. garnish with fresh minced green onion and serve with kindness!

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62042" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. spread sauce at base of flatbread\

2. Evenly place garnishes across flatbread ensuring even coverage.

3. Bake until cheese is blubbly and golden


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently

</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62051" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place chopped salad in mixing bowl with dressing 

2. Toss together to coat

3. Add tossed salad to serving bowl &amp; garnish with roasted cashews and fresh cilantro.

4. Serve with Kindness

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62283" image=""/>
	<Recipe id="P-62305" image="">there is an 18.5% loss on a bartlet pear</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62306" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place eggs into a perforated hotel pan IN A SINGLE LAYER, do not stack or crowd the pan or they will not cook evenly

2. Place into steamer for 10-12 minutes 

3. After eggs are done in the steamer run under Ice cold wtaer to stop the cooking process, keeping in mind slightly warm eggs are easier to peel. 

4. Reserve.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:


</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62388" image="">this is just a yielded ration, not a recipe</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-62547" image="">Slice the grape tomatoes in half length wise</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-62685" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in:

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)

Method:

1.
2.
3.

*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently 

Portioning:

Utensils needed:
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-67844" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Fry chicken strips untill fully cooked. Toss in hot sauce (1.5 pices should cover the bun end to end)

2. lightly toast bun on flat top. spread bluecheese dressing inside both sides of bun.

3. place lettuce and tomato on one side add sauced chicken strips. garnish with minced green onion.

4. Serve with kindness


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68029" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Take your cooked and thuroughly cooled chicken stir fry and toss it in 100g of pesto

2. Ensure all chicken is evenly coated.

3. Reserve for service.


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="P-68034" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: Classic Reuben

Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Drain Bocconcini

2. Toss with pesto, ensure evenly covered, let marinate 

3. Reserve for service. Shelf life 3-4 days


*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
	<Recipe id="R-68919" image="">***COOKS AND CHEFS, PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE RECIPE BEFORE BEGINNING- THIS IS A RECOMMENDED STEP WITH EVERY PRODUCT WE EVER PRODUCE- THANK YOU***
Amanda

Related Products this prep gets used in: 
Allergens: (to be filled out by nutrition)
Method:

1. Place 2 pancakes on serving plate

2. Top with blueberry compote. DO NOT MIX BLUEBERRIES INTO PANCAKES! always keep the base nuetral.



*Cool, store, label and rotate this item with older product correctly and diligently
</Recipe>
</Recipes>
